Seeker: [knocking] It's almost in the tooth.
DM: What's what?
Seeker: Contribution of the pilot lights.
DM: [coughs] I don't know.
Unknown: Probably small.
DM: Compared to like gas leaks, it's gotta be pretty small.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Okay. So we pick up
DM: as you
DM: all collapse into the late afternoon sun
DM: on the summit of the mountain in the middle of the circular island.
DM: Um,
DM: sitting in the sunshine, you begin to forget the
DM: webs of shadow that have reduced Seeker to being like somebody else has to carry your backpack 'cause you can barely even lift your arm with a three strength,
DM: and
DM: reduced many of you to quite a high level of exhaustion.
DM: And as you... So it's only been now, at this point,
DM: something like
DM: 15 minutes since, or maybe 20 minutes since you left the company of Ra'ghemdros,
DM: made your way through the Cloudspinner's prison, and managed to rescue her now, her now in your portable hole.
Seeker: [clears throat] After defeating the fiend.
DM: After defeating the fiend.
DM: So at this point, you know, things seem quiet on the island, although there must be some activity down in the...
DM: Oh, actually you'd probably be able to see, it's only like six or seven miles away.
DM: You can see the,
DM: um,
DM: the circ- the shape of the, of Ra'ghemdros kind of flying around agitatedly, seemingly
DM: talking to, you know, stopping occasionally, like talking to some people,
DM: talking to the chimeras maybe, and then disappears back into her lair.
Unknown: We should, [clears throat] get under cover sooner rather than later.
DM: Yeah. You-
Delwath: Go into the temple
DM: ... go into the temple.
DM: Um-
Seeker: We teleported
DM: ... or you teleported into the temple.
Seeker: Directly inside the temple.
DM: Okay. So you're in the temple.
DM: [clicks tongue] Um, Dimitar,
DM: you hear the start of a, "Who dares..."
DM: Oh, wait. And he steps out from behind the statue.
DM: It's you. [clears throat]
Unknown: We've, um, we've stirred up some trouble, Dimitar.
Unknown: A little bit.
Unknown: But it's good for you in the long run.
Wellby: I think you're gonna like it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Not in the short run. You're gonna like it.
DM: Uh,
DM: tell me more.
Unknown: Well, well, we, we
Delwath: broke, um,
Unknown: Ra'ghemdros.
Unknown: Well, first of all, we made a deal. We made...
Kenzo: We, we, we broke like a, like 100-year-old, uh, f- uh, curse and prison thing.
Delwath: It, Ra'ghemdros is quite matted and is probably looking for us to try to kill us.
DM: And you came here because?
Unknown: It felt safe and cozy and home-like.
Wellby: You could protect us.
Delwath: And we thought maybe your fireballs would be helpful.
Kenzo: Hey, great news.
DM: I think you've misjudged the situation.
Kenzo: Dimitar, great news.
Kenzo: And, uh, Kenzo pulls out the staff.
Unknown: We got the last piece of jade. Rise hand.
Unknown: Isn't that great?
DM: Oh, that's nice.
DM: Uh,
DM: it would be more useful if you weren't bringing death down upon us.
Kenzo: That's just like a minor detail.
Wellby: You've lived with your death for a long time.
DM: She's never had a reason to scry me.
DM: She's gonna scry the entire island now.
Wellby: Oh, fuck. Top. [laughs] Urgently pulls it out and starts spinning it.
DM: Di- Dimitar's staring at it and it's spinning.
DM: What's that?
Wellby: It's a top.
Delwath: Um, hey, Dim. By the way...
Unknown: Wait, did I do see invisible?
Unknown: Did I do see invisible?
Seeker: When?
Unknown: Like,
Delwath: uh, when we started combat.
Delwath: No, I didn't. I'm gonna say it wasn't.
DM: You did it with the... You only did it in the-
Unknown: I mean-
Unknown: ... vests
Delwath: ... it only lasts for an hour,
Unknown: but I can see a scrying sensor.
Seeker: Oh, I didn't know that that was a thing.
Unknown: Yeah. It's just a, it's like a eye.
Unknown: Right.
Kenzo: It's just an invisible eye. If you can see invisible, you can see the scrying sensor.
Unknown: Wait, does the top still spin?
Unknown: Yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna see invisible.
Kenzo: Is the top still spinning?
DM: Dimitar's looking at it.
Unknown: Is there a-
DM: What's it supposed to do?
Unknown: Is there an eye?
DM: No, there's not an eye.
Unknown: Wait, wait. It's supposed to
Wellby: s- spin if we're being watched?
Unknown: It spins if anybody's watching.
DM: It spins if it's being watched, but everybody has to turn their back and wait for it to fall down.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: Dimitar doesn't quite get the picture.
Wellby: Y- you gotta clo- close your eyes, Dimitar.
Wellby: It, it detects if we're being scried.
DM: Wait, why? It seems like it spins on its own.
DM: I'd call it something like a always spinning top.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah, but only if you look at it.
Delwath: If you walk away, it'll fall over unless somebody else is looking.
Seeker: If anybody's looking at it, it keeps spinning.
DM: Okay, let's all do a test.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Everybody turn their back. I'll close my eyes and we'll see what happens.
DM: Listen for it.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It keeps spinning.
Wellby: Are your eyes really closed, Dimitar?
DM: No. [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah, they were.
Wellby: Yeah, Dimitar, actually close your eyes this time.
DM: He closes his eyes. It falls down.
Unknown: No, all, all the way.
DM: It falls down.
Delwath: But I can see there's no scrying sensor.
DM: Then he opens his eyes a peek.
DM: Oh, wow. It stands up on its own.
DM: Do, do, do you need this?
Unknown: [laughs] Yeah.
DM: Really?
Kenzo: We'll give it to you later after we kill Apollyon.
Kenzo: It's yours. Promise.
DM: Okay.
Seeker: We've, we've been spies for so long.
Wellby: He's not in power to make this deal-
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: ... on behalf of all of us.
Unknown: After we kill Apollyon.
DM: Why not? He looks like the strong one.
Unknown: Uh.
DM: Or maybe him.
Unknown: I mean
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Huh. Huh.
Unknown: I think Kenzo deserves to make decisions about the top.
Kenzo: Look, the point is, Dimitar, we were successful in bringing together the hand of your former friend and ally.
Kenzo: Um, we completed a very, very complex quest to get this thing done.
Unknown: Also-
DM: That seems awesome for you.
Unknown: Huh?
DM: I said that seems awesome for you.
Kenzo: For us. For us collectively, as you share in a similar goal and vision.
Kenzo: Uh, also, um,
Kenzo: we, uh, we, we freed, uh, or we, we have a, a giant crystal with a, uh
Unknown: Cloudspinner person inside. Yeah, an ancient archfey.
Wellby: Yeah. Who's been imprisoned for millennium.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Oh.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: What?
DM: That makes sense now.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, she's here.
DM: Oh, she's gonna be so pissed.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. But she's here. Remember when we...
Unknown: Weren't you listening earlier?
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
DM: You didn't know about the Cloudspinner earlier.
Unknown: No, no, no, no. When we came here, starting by saying the dragon is really bad.
DM: Oh, yeah. Ha ha, this guy gets it.
Delwath: Um, here, uh,
Delwath: I'm gonna scry Ragemptus.
DM: Uh, it doesn't work.
DM: She went into her lair.
DM: Scrying across planes.
Unknown: But how can she scry across planes?
DM: Her lair is magic.
Unknown: [snapping fingers] Anyways, uh, so there's probably
Kenzo: like monsters, maybe hordes of monsters headed here.
Unknown: Um...
DM: I mean, it's not gonna be instantaneous.
Kenzo: Yeah. We're, that's... We're gonna rest, right?
DM: She's gotta scry the whole island.
DM: She can't just see it all at once.
Kenzo: Exactly. So we have time.
Seeker: Should keep an eye out through the window just in case the chimeras do fly straight for us at some point.
DM: Um...
DM: What's like maybe highest?
DM: I'm gonna suggest maybe sleeping in the tunnels.
Unknown: I like this idea. That's a great idea.
DM: I mean, I never sleep out in the open.
DM: Only fools do that.
Kenzo: [laughs] Yeah, we weren't thinking about doing that.
Kenzo: Um, [clears throat] that's a great idea.
Unknown: Why don't we go do that?
DM: It's a little tight.
DM: You'll, you two will be fine.
DM: How do you feel about tight spaces?
DM: Any claustrophobia?
Unknown: It's fine.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um-
Kenzo: As long as I don't have to cuddle with the elf, I'm fine.
DM: Oh, no. You can all be in a row.
Unknown: All right.
DM: But, uh,
DM: hmm.
Unknown: Where's the entrance to these tunnels?
DM: This is the trap door behind the statue.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: Should someone be keeping lookout?
Delwath: I might wait out here.
Delwath: A, I don't actually need a long rest.
Delwath: And B, I only need four hours to get a long rest.
Unknown: Awesome. Whatever you like.
DM: It's up to you.
Delwath: I mean, it's a little tight, right?
DM: I mean,
DM: yeah, but when she scrys you,
DM: what do you think she's gonna do?
Unknown: But can she not scry in the tunnels?
Kenzo: But when she does, she just sees a bunch of tunnels.
Unknown: Unless she-
DM: I mean...
Delwath: If she can scry us physically, specifically us, it's not gonna take her any time.
DM: Uh, no, she can scry the island.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. That's what I said.
DM: Any location on the island.
Unknown: But can she scry-
DM: That was what Dimitar was saying.
Delwath: Yeah, no, I got that. But can she scry inside the temple?
DM: I mean,
Unknown: probably. She's aware of it.
Unknown: So, so-
DM: She might not be aware... Dimitar doesn't think she's aware of its tunnels.
Delwath: So she probably can't scry inside the tunnel.
Unknown: Let's all go in the tunnels.
DM: Yeah, let's go in the tunnels.
Kenzo: I like it. Yeah. [clears throat] That feels like a great thing to do.
Kenzo: Hey, you seem to say, seem to know something about the person, uh, trapped inside the, uh-
DM: No, I don't, but it all clicked into place.
DM: I knew the story.
Unknown: Which story?
DM: That Shemut
DM: captured some powerful archfey who refused to give him the secrets of divinity that he wanted to use to
DM: kill the gods, and that Apollyon wanted to use to become a god.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: And they fought over what it, whoever this was,
DM: and Shemut won,
DM: but Apollyon got away with some magic item.
DM: I don't know what it was.
DM: That must have been what
DM: Ragemptus has been guarding this whole time, the thing that
DM: Shemut was trying to use to learn how to kill the gods.
Unknown: Hmm.
DM: What did you say? Who did you say it was?
Unknown: Cloudspinner.
DM: I don't know who that is.
Delwath: Who it was. It's the person.
Delwath: It's her name.
DM: That's her name. Ah, okay.
DM: That's a good fey name.
Kenzo: So why did Ragemptus use Cloudspinner for herself?
Kenzo: I mean, Shemut's been dead for hundreds of years.
Kenzo: Like, why is she still, why is she still, why she been still guarding it this whole time?
Kenzo: For what purpose?
DM: I don't know.
Seeker: Perhaps it's a curse upon her.
DM: I mean-
Kenzo: I can ask her when she, she shows up.
DM: Maybe she is unable to disobey Shemut's command.
Delwath: Oh, that's interesting. What's the theory of why we would be here when she shows up exactly?
Unknown: What do you mean?
Delwath: Like, why wouldn't we just teleport away?
DM: After you long rest?
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: Wait, you're gonna leave me to be slaughtered by a dragon?
Kenzo: You're coming with us. You're coming with us.
DM: You're gonna leave the dragonets to be slaughtered by a dragon?
Unknown: Why would she kill them?
Wellby: 'Cause they brought us to her and like vouched for us and-
DM: Have you never fought like a dragon before?
DM: She's gonna kill everybody on this island if she doesn't get the Cloudspinner back.
Unknown: Uh.
Delwath: Uh. [sighs] I guess we have to be heroes.
DM: I mean, how many people can you teleport?
Unknown: Eight.
DM: Oh, well, that's useless.
Unknown: Why is that?
DM: I mean, there's at least
DM: 50 I'd wanna rescue.
Kenzo: [clears throat] This is gonna make the airship really fun later.
DM: There's a, there's a-
Unknown: Well, not if we kill the dragon today
DM: ... there's like 100 we could just let die.
DM: That'd be fine.
Kenzo: Wait, but what about the ones that are loyal to her?
Unknown: She's gonna kill them too?
DM: She might. Have you ever seen a really, truly pissed dragon?
Wellby: Yeah.
Kenzo: I mean, yeah.
Unknown: We've killed a couple.
DM: Oh, that's great, actually. Then you're definitely staying.
Seeker: [sighs] [clears throat] Smaller ones.
Seeker: We've killed mostly slightly smaller ones.
Kenzo: Where do you think we should fight her?
DM: Well,
DM: it's always time to step up in the world, right?
Kenzo: So Dimitar, where do you think we should fight her?
Kenzo: We meaning the four, the five of us together.
DM: Wait, can you fly?
Kenzo: Yeah.
DM: All of you?
Wellby: Yep.
Unknown: Ish. Sort of.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Close enough.
DM: Um, 'cause, you know,
DM: she's probably not gonna land.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Air combat, huh?
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: Oh, I have a rules question, Tim.
Seeker: I thought I saw something about
Seeker: long rest while waking, while being able to do things that require being awake,
Seeker: like a special ability.
DM: Like what?
Seeker: That I could have a long rest while being awake.
Unknown: Oh, simulacrum.
DM: Oh. Um, no, you can't have a long rest unless...
DM: What special ability is this?
Seeker: Something that I was reading a lot of stuff on my character sheet, and I remember seeing that, but maybe that was a spell.
DM: I don't know.
Delwath: You might have a potion or something that lets you do that.
Delwath: Oh, you... I think you might have.
Unknown: Go check your, check your character sheet.
Delwath: Tim might have something there as a-
DM: You have a potion of watchful rest.
Unknown: That's what it is.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah. But simulacrum takes 12 hours.
DM: [chuckles]
Unknown: How long is a long rest?
DM: Eight hour... I mean, if you start right now, you might have a chance.
Seeker: That's why I wanna raise the question, might be useful thinking about this upcoming conflict to have another
Seeker: one of us or something.
Unknown: I can make another dimitar. That's not a good-
Unknown: No. Making the simulacrum cast spells?
DM: Yep.
Delwath: And it can't, but it can't regain slots, right?
DM: It can't re-- it, it can't benefit from a rest.
Seeker: So like if we had another, what would it be?
Seeker: Delwath 'cause it can cast fly on itself.
Delwath: It could cast fly on it and me and you.
Seeker: And it could then also cast some attack spells that are things that the dragon might be vulnerable to.
Delwath: I mean, it's tough to do
Delwath: concentration, like fly is a concentration spell, so it cuts into ability to do other concentration spells.
Unknown: Mm.
Delwath: But there's other spells.
Unknown: I mean...
Seeker: Or would it be better to have another Kenzo or Wellby?
Delwath: But another Kenzo or Wellby would have a hard time flying.
DM: They'd have a hard time flying 'cause they can't duplicate magic items.
Kenzo: Can you make a resilient?
DM: No, they have to be there.
Unknown: I mean, I think a du- Delwath would be pretty useful.
Delwath: Like it could just rain...
Unknown: It could, it
Unknown: could-
DM: I mean, really what it should do is cast fly and then hide.
Unknown: That's what I was gonna say.
Seeker: I guess if only we had another ladder.
Seeker: If we had another, [chuckles] if we had another Seeker.
DM: You could make another-
Seeker: It could do another animated-
DM: Seeker could make another ladder, that's true
Unknown: ... it could do its own animated performance and ride that ladder.
Delwath: No, but honestly-
Seeker: It's just really slow. It's a 30 foot ladder
Delwath: ... casting fly
Unknown: on-
Seeker: Well, what's fly speed for a cast of fly?
DM: 60.
Seeker: 60. Yeah, so
Unknown: that might be better.
Delwath: But the nice thing about casting fly and, uh, simulacrum Delwath who casts fly and then tries to stay out of combat, try and stay far away, and uses,
Unknown: um,
Delwath: metamagic to cast 240 foot range eldritch blasts or something like that.
Unknown: It would have to drag, I think if it wants to do-
Unknown: Yeah, no, I can, I can drag Delwath.
Seeker: Delwath Prime.
DM: Well, I mean, there's no guarantee you're, you're gonna have 12 hours.
DM: That's the only problem.
Seeker: And it, it burns a high level spell slot if it casts it.
DM: It burns your seventh level slot, and if you,
DM: if you get interrupted in the middle of casting, it's just wasted.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: It'd be super useful, but I don't think we know the timeline with enough confidence.
Delwath: But when are you gonna use just that level spot slot in combat form anyway?
Wellby: You also wouldn't be able to-
Unknown: 'Cause, because it doesn't...
Delwath: I mean, you're not gonna use your eighth level slot on animal shapes.
Unknown: You have no other eighth level spells for you.
DM: Unless... Right. All it means is you would have to-
Unknown: Sure
DM: ... like even if, instead of what you...
DM: You would have to save your eighth level slot-
Unknown: For teleport
DM: ... for teleport because you don't wanna take another long rest on the island.
Unknown: But we don't have to teleport to get off the island.
DM: Oh, that's true. You can just sail.
Delwath: I mean, I'm gonna send a message to, to our, to Milo again.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: To say, um-
Kenzo: Yeah, stay here now. [laughs]
Delwath: Right. Uh, imminent danger.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: expect us to be,
Unknown: um-
DM: Do you tell him what the imminent danger is?
Delwath: Yeah. Dragon, imminent danger.
Delwath: Dragon,
Delwath: uh, rampaging on island.
Delwath: But I'm gonna tell him... I don't need to do...
Delwath: 'Cause it's not, it's not Sunday.
Unknown: I don't need to-
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Um, there's a dragon that we've, um, angered who is ranging, uh, raging across the island.
Delwath: We have agreed to stay to kill it or, um, die trying.
Delwath: Expect, we expect this will be resolved shortly after dawn at the latest Um, be prepared to keep an eye on things.
Delwath: We're probably doing this in the air, so you might even be able to see it.
Unknown: Um, if you see the dragon dive, come to shore and be prepared to board us.
Delwath: Uh, if the dragon seems to not dive, flee.
Wellby: Isn't the dragon gonna spot [clears throat] Milo in the boat and kill them
Wellby: as it flies around the island?
Unknown: Mm. [clears throat]
Unknown: Oh, my computer wasn't charging.
Delwath: They gotta, yeah, yeah, I mean, they gotta hide, yeah, but they gotta get somewhere.
Wellby: I think they gotta hide.
Kenzo: They gotta hide. Yeah, yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
Delwath: I'll send them a warning. What?
Delwath: I'll send them a warning. I'll tell them our plan is we're probably gonna fight the dragon at dawn,
Delwath: and it's raging in Cross Island and is pretty pissed, and stay away until,
Unknown: like,
Unknown: noon.
Seeker: So I do have the potion of water walking.
Wellby: We could also just tell them to sail out 'cause we can-
Unknown: Ah
Wellby: ... rainbow bridge from the prison or the lair.
Delwath: Oh, that's an interesting idea.
Delwath: We could just tell them to leave.
Unknown: But we...
Delwath: Oh, no, we're pretty confident that rainbow bridge will work from an extra-dimensional space.
Delwath: The problem is my, my messengers can't cross
Unknown: water.
Seeker: We've used it from other dimensions before.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Okay, let's tell Milo to just flee.
Unknown: I think that's safer.
Kenzo: Wait, but then what if the extra-dimensional thing doesn't work?
Unknown: Then we're stuck.
Wellby: Yep.
Kenzo: If we can't rainbow bridge out of here, then there's no way out.
Unknown: Why don't we just have him wait? 'Cause we're worried the dragon's gonna kill him.
Wellby: 'Cause I think the dragon's gonna... Yeah.
Wellby: I think the dragon's gonna kill him.
Unknown: Even if he hides?
Unknown: Where would he hide, though, in the open ocean?
Delwath: I mean, he could sail far away.
Delwath: I think we should just tell him to leave. I think that's safer.
Delwath: We don't even...
Unknown: Yeah, I, that just feels safer.
Wellby: Well, he could hide, like, in one of the temple complexes at one of the statues,
Wellby: but that's, like, a numbers game because if the dragon is systematically, like, looking everywhere on the whole island through scrying...
Kenzo: But aren't his, aren't the dragon's dragonette, like, uh, hen- henchlings gonna, like, see a fucking boat, like, out in the ocean and-
Unknown: Probably
Kenzo: ... immediately wanna go kill it?
Wellby: I mean, are they on the ocean right now?
Unknown: I don't know where he is right now.
Unknown: You don't know where he is right now.
Unknown: Uh-
DM: You don't see him at the moment.
Delwath: I'm gonna send a message.
Delwath: Tell him... I'm just gonna tell him what's coming down and, and-
Wellby: Good luck
Unknown: ... he can respond to the message.
Kenzo: Yeah, they can decide for themselves. I mean-
Delwath: Yeah, he can decide for himself, right? Like-
Kenzo: Like, open ocean is likely death, but, you know.
Delwath: I will te- I will send, I will send the links to him-
Unknown: Okay
Delwath: ... with a letter explaining that the dr- that we've pissed off a dragon, we've agreed to stay and kill the dragon.
Delwath: We expect this will be no later than tomorrow morning.
Delwath: The dragon is looking to kill anything and everything, so keep yourself safe.
Kenzo: Yeah, either flee to the mainland or hide.
Delwath: Don't worry about us. If you think the wisest thing to do is just flee, do it.
Delwath: Like, we'll be okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Flee or hide.
DM: Um, shortly, the message comes back and says, "Message received.
DM: Crew are hiding.
DM: We're coming to hunt a dragon."
Unknown: Oh. [laughs] Okay.
Wellby: Awesome.
Kenzo: Dude, they're fucking badass.
Seeker: They've got... They've, they've taken things, matters into their own hands.
Unknown: I like it.
Unknown: They're like, "This is the way."
Delwath: Um, I didn't tell them... I guess I would have said what...
Unknown: I guess I should [clears throat] I guess I should send the bad things back to say, um-
Unknown: Wait, how many times can I... Can I use this as many times as I want?
DM: No, I think it's... I don't know, but I don't think it's unlimited.
Delwath: I thought it might have just been limited by,
Delwath: by the fact that it can't go that often, that it can't go that fast.
DM: But the fast speed is only once a day.
Delwath: I thought it could go up to two hours.
DM: Well, whatever. It doesn't matter.
Unknown: I don't know.
DM: You could have, you can have told them where you are.
Unknown: Fine.
Unknown: It's fine.
Kenzo: So, Dimitar, where do we want to fight these guys, fight the dragon?
Kenzo: Is there any way to get, get it closer to ground?
Delwath: So I think the simulacrum is potentially worth the risk.
Seeker: What time of day is it right now?
Delwath: It's like, what, 4:00 in the afternoon?
DM: Like 5:00. It's like the hour before sunset.
Seeker: So I could have it ready by dawn.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Do black dragons like to attack in the middle of the night?
Unknown: Probably.
Wellby: Can we do it from inside a tomb?
Seeker: So I need to be near Delwath all, the entire time.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: I need a pile of snow.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Snow?
Seeker: And a lot of rubies.
DM: You need a lot of rubies. Do you have any rubies?
Seeker: Oh, I thought we still had a bunch
Seeker: in the hole, don't we?
Unknown: Uh, we can go check.
Seeker: I believe that we determined that we're gonna be able to do simulacrum at least one more time.
Unknown: I think you're right.
Unknown: And I do have the-
DM: But, but you also tried to restock on rubies and couldn't because the, uh-
Seeker: We had consumed all available rubies.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Because Rizvan had consumed all available rubies.
Unknown: Oh, Rizvan had.
Delwath: Remember to make, to make Uz-Kakar
Unknown: forever safe from undead.
Seeker: Right.
Seeker: There should be giant statues of us in that city, or at least of Rizvan.
DM: There's a giant... There is a giant statue of Rizvan.
Unknown: Yeah, they built one. Oh, right.
Seeker: That's good and appropriate.
Delwath: But the dragon will probably have some rubies
Delwath: once we kill it. We can restock here.
DM: Oh, yeah. No, that's right. You have-
Wellby: And then go back in time and create the simulacrum.
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: You have the rubies from the elemental forge.
Seeker: Amazing.
Delwath: None of the materials in the divine forge were useful for this kind of-
DM: No, it was all metal.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: S- So
Unknown: And purely out of
Seeker: strategic concern for our own future wellbeing and not out of vanity, Delwath, you think it is a good idea to make another Delwath?
Delwath: Yeah. 'Cause Fly, I mean, honestly, just having a Delwath literally doing nothing except casting Fly and hiding is very
Delwath: useful because the problem with...
Delwath: When I cast Fly, that's fine, but if I fail a concentration check, we plummet to the ground.
Seeker: Everybody. Wellby and you at least.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: And these guys-
Delwath: They can fly on their own
Seeker: ... have endless flying.
Delwath: Yeah. But also by not, if I'm not using
Unknown: Fly to fl- if I'm not using my concentration to fly, I can use my concentration to do other stuff.
Seeker: And Fly affects-
Delwath: If I cast at 5th level, it's three people.
Seeker: 'Cause then we could get the, um, construct flying too, which would be pretty cool.
Delwath: Either the construct or the...
Delwath: I mean, the other thing is the, the second Delwath could cast Fly on himself,
Delwath: Delwath Prime and Seeker,
Delwath: and then could-
Seeker: It gives us some options, basically.
Delwath: Right. But also could throw spells from long range.
Seeker: Which might even be more important.
Delwath: Right. But to, to stay away so that, like, the dragon doesn't...
Seeker: There needs to be a way to position these, the character figurines.
Delwath: Oh, man. A second Delwath could cast Scatter also.
Seeker: Cast what?
Unknown: Scatter.
Unknown: Ooh, yeah.
Unknown: Two Scatters.
Seeker: Yeah. [clears throat] All right, we should get to work on that.
Delwath: Let's do it. I mean, you can't make one of yourself, can you?
Seeker: I could-- I can, it's just not obviously better than the Delwath version.
Delwath: Yeah, I think Delwath, I think the Delwath version is good, is a good plan.
Seeker: Just because of the Fly spell.
Unknown: That's what-
Delwath: Yeah, I think Fly plus Scatter is pretty useful.
Seeker: So the one remaining question being
Seeker: if Dimitar has an ice machine anywhere.
DM: Uh, Shape Water can freeze water.
Seeker: Oh. Oh, oh, I can... Yeah, yeah.
DM: Yeah, you have an ice machine.
Unknown: On top of the canter. I am an ice machine.
Unknown: Ice water. [chuckles] Shape Water.
Seeker: We only need to run it-
DM: Eat a little bit on the side.
Unknown: What's that?
Seeker: [chuckles] Snow cone, yeah.
Unknown: Delicious.
Seeker: All right, so...
Delwath: I, I think we hide in the tunnel.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Let's try it. I mean,
Delwath: if we get attacked at 3:00 AM before the simulacrum is ready, then we do.
Seeker: Yeah. It's worth a try.
Delwath: But also, like,
Unknown: it's unclear exactly what the mechanism of...
Unknown: What's she gonna do? Can she even fit in the temple to sit?
DM: She could probably crack the roof.
Seeker: Right. Or flood the tunnel with acid or something.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: But she won't be able to get by the ladder.
DM: She's quite a bit bigger than the ladder.
Unknown: That's true.
DM: Be a little bit less of a-
Seeker: Right. [chuckles] Um, all right.
Unknown: So Seeker
Seeker: begin-- drinks the potion of watchful rest.
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Begins the process of...
Seeker: Oh, that's interesting.
Seeker: There's this sort of like
Seeker: rules situation here.
Seeker: Do I have a spell slot that I can use to cast simula- simulacrum?
DM: Oh-
Unknown: Or the-
DM: Oh no, you don't have any spell slots.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: You don't have a 7th or 8th level slot, do you?
DM: No, you don't.
Seeker: Circle of Power can't fix that, can it?
DM: No, it can't.
Unknown: No, we can't do this.
Unknown: Fuck.
Seeker: It was such a good idea.
DM: You used it for Teleport, so y-
Seeker: Oh, I was like, "I have a 7th level slot."
Seeker: No, we just teleported.
DM: You used it to teleport.
Unknown: We just teleported.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So that doesn't work, unfortunately.
Unknown: Ah.
Seeker: No Delwath Prime. Sorry, buddy.
Unknown: That's all right.
Wellby: I think we should long rest, like, immediately.
Unknown: Yeah, that's probably-
Unknown: So we're ready to go at 3:00 AM.
Unknown: Yeah, I think you're right.
DM: Okay.
DM: You all go to sleep.
Wellby: Vision, Jay, Han.
DM: Take... Yep. Take turns-
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Take turns watching.
Unknown: Yep.
Delwath: I'm gonna set, um, my links out too.
DM: Oh, yeah. Just set your links to guard instead of you actually watching so she doesn't see anything.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Maybe.
Wellby: It's awesome.
DM: So close.
Unknown: It does. It's so good.
DM: Keep it in mind for another time, maybe for the Apollyon fight.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Or-
Seeker: The thing is,
Seeker: do one that wander around the ship.
Seeker: The simulacrum can just hang out.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: It doesn't like-
DM: Right. But it doesn't heal, so it...
DM: And it can't really gain spell slots, so you gotta, like, be judicious about when you actually use it.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Yeah, but you could prep- prepare one on the ship and...
DM: Yeah.
DM: Okay, so as you drift off to sleep, um, you all find yourself in a shared dream.
DM: Um, you are,
DM: uh... The first thing you see is something you've seen before.
DM: It's the,
DM: um,
DM: standing on top of a high mountain pass, this massive shadow dragon above you, and then Rai, like, everybody fighting.
DM: I don't remember what everybody was doing.
DM: Bar- Beryl had a quarterstaff, right?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay.
DM: You know, Beryl's fighting with a quarterstaff.
DM: I, I think Aaron had, like, some weird shadow dagger.
DM: Something like that.
DM: Um,
DM: and then the moment when Shamut dies and there's this, like, silent flash that goes across the world, and then suddenly you're yanked
DM: as Rai teleports to Drankor.
DM: And you see what you haven't seen before, which is that, um,
DM: standing right outside this, there's this elaborate tomb,
DM: a structure, um, in which you gather Apollyon is buried, and there's a dagger flying towards the door.
DM: And Rai
DM: grabs it in his hand moments before it strikes the door
DM: and stands there.
DM: And time flashes forward, and you are
DM: in Rai's mind as he probes these bindings, trying to understand what he's grabbed onto.
DM: And he reaches through the various tangles and twists and knots of Cha'mutte's magic,
DM: of
DM: the essence of the plane of Limbo, the plane of chaos that Cha'mutte was close to,
DM: woven in knots into a net
DM: that hel- that holds
DM: Apollyon in place.
Seeker: This is like one moment that Kong should not be asleep.
DM: Are you good?
Unknown: I'm still awake.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: All right.
DM: Um,
DM: and this net wraps all the way around the tomb, and it's woven tightly, but there are,
DM: uh, still small holes where
DM: something could, could pierce through and could penetrate.
DM: But Rai realizes as long as the dagger is held,
DM: Apollyon has no power to do anything.
DM: And time passes, and Apollyon seems to grow weaker every year in which he cannot
DM: feed on souls, cannot strengthen himself with his dagger.
DM: He must have been-
Kenzo: And Rai's just standing there outside of Holian?
DM: Yeah, so far. He must have been weak to begin with and grows weaker and weaker.
DM: [laughs] I have to look at that later.
DM: Isaac just texted me, "Our session notes are better than yours."
Seeker: Oh, geez.
DM: Um,
DM: grows--
DM: feels him grow weaker and weaker as the,
DM: um, as he grows, the years pass and the connection to
DM: the souls trapped in this dagger grows dimmer and dimmer over decades, until Rai eventually decides
DM: standing here
DM: is maybe not the best place to be, the dagger so close, and of course, he can't move except by teleporting because he's all jade.
DM: He teleports
DM: to
DM: a-- an-- the one area in Dranikor that seems not cursed by
DM: sh- by the pla- by the echoes of the plague and the,
DM: uh,
DM: dark energy of Apollyon and all of the many, many, many people who died here.
DM: It's the grand-- it's a grand, huge domed building, a temple to the eight divines.
DM: Eight sort of alcoves stretching out, um, to create these separate spaces for eight, uh, eight gods to be worshiped around this giant
DM: central dome.
Seeker: It's the same as the pantheon on this side.
Unknown: It's the same as the eight gods.
DM: Uh, it's the same eight gods.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah. The, the architecture is a little different, and you actually recognize this as where you saw
DM: Kenzo had a dream where the, um, the awakened soul monks found Rai, and this is the building.
DM: And Dimitar is there as well.
DM: Um,
DM: and over the years,
DM: a hundred years pass, and Apollyon seems to grow weaker and weaker, but this
DM: net of chaos,
DM: this
DM: fragment of Limbo that's wrapped around the temple seems to grow stronger and stronger.
DM: And it seems like there's tendrils from it reaching out across the world.
DM: And as Apollyon grows weaker and the chaos of Limbo grows stronger, Rai makes a decision
DM: that perhaps the only way forward-- that if he does nothing,
DM: then this curse that Cha'mutte left behind may grow too strong.
DM: And so he leaves the dagger
DM: in what he thinks is the one place it will be safe under the protection of the divine.
DM: Maybe it's still there, maybe it's not.
DM: And vanishes.
DM: And that's when you wake up.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: Hey, Tim.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: I can long rest in four hours, right?
Delwath: So in-- I'm gonna long rest, wake up, cast Aid, and then short rest.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um-
Unknown: So we get the bonus hit points.
Unknown: Which I completely understand.
Unknown: So,
Unknown: Cha'mutte dies.
Unknown: Rai teleports to Dranikor.
Kenzo: There's a dra- there's a dagger flying towards the tomb.
Kenzo: Catches the dagger.
Kenzo: Stands there for like a few decades, and then is like, "What?
Unknown: Is that what he decided to do?" He goes to the temple.
DM: He goes to the temple.
Unknown: To the temple.
DM: Apollyon keeps getting weaker every year that he's disconnected from his phylactery.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So Rai feels that Apollyon has gotten so weak that he doesn't have to stand guard anymore,
DM: goes to the temple
Unknown: Which temple?
DM: The Temple of the Eight Divines in Dranikor.
Unknown: Ah, okay.
DM: Which is the only place that isn't full of the-
Unknown: The red plague
DM: ... plague death.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Waits.
DM: Sh- Apollyon's getting weaker, but this Limbo chaos that Cha'mut has used to
DM: imprison,
DM: the f- the fragments of Limbo that Cha'mut has used to imprison Apollyon are growing stronger, and they're connect- They're like...
DM: There's like a net of Limbo stretching out across the world that Rai is getting worried about.
Unknown: Mm.
Unknown: And then what he does?
DM: Then he decides he needs...
DM: The vision ends with him, like, putting the dagger in the temple and
DM: deciding to go do something about the
DM: Limbo chaos.
Unknown: Wait, but doesn't... So what does his hand get pulled to bits?
DM: Presumably he fails to do something about the Limbo chaos, and his hand explodes into bits.
Unknown: Yeah, we... No, but we knew that, right?
DM: You knew that, yeah.
Unknown: We saw the b-
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So but he, he's off with the monks trying to get rid of-
Unknown: Right, right, right
Seeker: ... and that's when his hand explodes.
Seeker: So bit, that probably happened in Isengard.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: And he's, throughout this time,
Seeker: he's jade.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Yeah. I mean, he's, we don't know.
Delwath: He could have the whole, his whole body could have exploded, right?
Unknown: We don't know if it was just his hand.
Unknown: Do we?
Seeker: Yeah, where is the rest of him?
Seeker: Must be in Isengard.
Unknown: In Isengard. Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: So we think he's been in Isengard for the past 40 years.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: But the dagger is in this temple in Dranikor.
Unknown: Well, unless it moved.
Unknown: But it's a good starting spot.
DM: It's a good starting spot.
Unknown: Oh, we could help with there.
Seeker: Having seen it.
DM: Could.
Seeker: We could try anyway.
Unknown: Worth a lot.
Unknown: All right, cool.
Seeker: Sort of raises the question, do we...
Unknown: Wait,
Seeker: can we not teleport from here to there because of the-
Unknown: Anti-magic
Unknown: ... anti-magic?
DM: Anti-magic.
Kenzo: We have to get back to the ship.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: I guess we fly there anyways.
Unknown: We'll have the ship with us.
Seeker: We don't, we don't have time, probably.
Wellby: How far is it from here to there?
Unknown: We're, we're close to Dranikor right now, right?
Unknown: Maybe two hours.
Unknown: It'd be a couple hundred miles.
DM: Yeah, you're pretty close to Dranikor.
DM: I mean, this was a-
Seeker: We do want the ship with us.
DM: You're like, um, you're probably no mo- You're definitely no more than 200 miles.
DM: That's 20 hours.
DM: That's less than a day.
Seeker: Also, like, Vindristjarna versus
Seeker: vast domed structure, we could probably take it.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: Puncture the dome and shit.
Delwath: I mean, the first thing we're gonna have to do is defeat our own doppelgangers.
Delwath: But wait, they can't level up.
DM: Right.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: It's true. They don't have eighth level slots.
Unknown: Nice.
Seeker: Are there a lot more of those, we think?
Delwath: There's one of each of us.
DM: There's one of each of you.
Unknown: Remember, they all have eighth level-
DM: Oh, but Seeker's the only one who has eighth level slots, so...
Unknown: But none of them have eighth level slots.
Seeker: And, uh, they haven't been destroyed.
Delwath: No, they all died once, and then we start this again.
DM: They all wear some amulet, so when you fight them, you have to take the amulet off them before you kill them, otherwise they just reform again.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Oh, man.
DM: Well, that's for another time.
Unknown: Yep.
DM: So,
DM: uh,
DM: okay, let's see what happens.
DM: Um,
DM: at about...
DM: So what happens if the lynx is triggered?
Unknown: It's alarm spell.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: So it's, it's mental currently.
Unknown: I can choose whether it's noise or mental, but it's mental.
DM: So at about,
DM: um,
DM: maybe
DM: 1:00 in the morning,
DM: um, the alarm spell is trig- You don't, do you know what triggers it?
Unknown: I think so, but I'm not sure.
Unknown: I may, probab- I don't know, maybe not.
Wellby: 1:00 in the morning is a full long rest, right?
DM: Uh-
Unknown: Starting at what?
DM: 5:00 to-
Unknown: Only four hours.
Unknown: 5:00 to 1:00? Yeah, that's...
DM: No, that's not eight hours, is it?
Unknown: Yeah, it is.
Unknown: I don't know.
DM: Oh yeah, it is eight hours. Yeah, that's a full long rest.
DM: Um...
Delwath: It doesn't tell me who's-
DM: It doesn't... So, okay, at about 1:00, you've all completed a long rest, but the spell is not finished,
DM: and
DM: the spell still needs another four hours.
DM: The alarm is triggered.
Unknown: What spell?
DM: Some arc- Oh no, you're not doing some arcane cantrip.
Unknown: We can't do it.
DM: Okay, 1:00 AM.
Unknown: What spell is it?
DM: I forgot. 1:00 AM, the spell, the alarm is triggered.
Seeker: Just at the moment we could have started doing something.
Unknown: Like, we got like eight hours of sleep, right?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: We long rested.
Delwath: But it's probably Tilly and Milo, not, uh, Frank, we hope.
Wellby: Can we see what triggered it?
DM: You can climb out of the tunnel.
Wellby: I climb out of the tunnel very carefully.
Kenzo: Is Dimitar in the tunnel with us this whole time?
DM: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: Huh?
DM: No, he sleeps curled up in the statue.
Wellby: There's a, there's a people out of the tunnel.
DM: Out of the statue, that's right. You can go out into the, um-
Seeker: You can see into the temple at least
DM: ... um, there is a pair of dragonets
DM: that are just kind of sitting in the temple,
DM: kind of curious about just keeping an eye.
Unknown: Wait, Dimitar-
Unknown: It'd be really funny to use the god's voice.
Unknown: Do you know them?
Delwath: I... Does Dimitar know these dragonets?
DM: Nope.
Seeker: Can we hear them if they talk?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Can you Soul Sight them?
Unknown: Sure.
Unknown: That's free, right?
DM: Yeah.
DM: Um-
Seeker: We're keeping very quiet
DM: ... they're, I mean, they're just, they're watchful.
DM: They're sort of bored.
Unknown: What's CR?
DM: Two.
Wellby: Do we just sleep?
Seeker: That's what I'd like to suggest.
Wellby: Yeah.
Unknown: Going to sleep.
DM: I think that's like a wisdom save.
Unknown: No save.
DM: No, the spell changed.
Delwath: Oh, come on. The new s- the new sleep spell is the dumbest...
Wellby: What is it?
Delwath: It's literally the worst spell in the world.
DM: Oh, well.
DM: I would assume you'd use the existing sleep or whatever.
DM: I didn't read the new sleep spell.
Unknown: The new sleep spell's stupid.
Delwath: It's like literally an idiotic spell that you would never take.
Seeker: Why does it work?
Delwath: Well, the old sleep spell is super fun because it's all about hit points.
Wellby: Right.
Unknown: It's like designed to knock down.
Delwath: The new sleep spell is just a wisdom save or nothing happens to you.
Unknown: It's-- And even if you make your wisdom save, you don't even fall asleep.
Wellby: Hmm.
Unknown: It-
DM: Well, I mean, it's the same.
DM: I mean, sleep, the sleep spell doesn't last, it doesn't make you fall asleep, but it still only lasts for a minute, the old sleep.
Unknown: It does make you fall asleep.
DM: But you wake up when the spell ends.
Delwath: You wake up when the spell ends, yes.
DM: So it's the sa- it's the same thing.
DM: It's just too safe. It's useful in different contexts.
Delwath: It's a double save.
Delwath: But so what I always liked about the sleep spell is that it, the whole point of the sleep spell is it doesn't require a save.
DM: I, I don't really care which way or the other.
DM: No, I much rather keep the old sleep spell.
DM: I mean, there's no way that a CR two creature is making two wisdom saves against a...
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It has the roughly the same effect.
Delwath: No, but it's much more useful.
Delwath: Like the situation I actually used sleep was to-
DM: Is when you take down enemies right at the very end.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: It was taking on Kagdurs. It was taking on Kagdurs that-
DM: That would be harder to do.
Delwath: That's much harder to deal with.
Unknown: I, I do not like the new sleep spell.
Unknown: I forgot about it.
DM: Yeah, it's not even a... Oh, it's a sorcerer spell.
DM: Right.
Unknown: Well, I have it for free from the Neswat, from the Neswat.
DM: Yeah,
DM: yeah. Uh, they fall asleep for a minute.
DM: [thudding]
Delwath: Well, I... Hold on.
Delwath: We need a plan before we cast sleep.
Wellby: Um,
Wellby: tie them up and release them at dawn to go report back.
Wellby: I think so. Right.
Wellby: So we can fight in the dark.
Delwath: I think we drag them into the tunnels and tie them, yeah.
DM: Okay.
DM: You drag them in, you tie them up and drag them into the tunnels.
Delwath: Ask them and interrogate them a little bit.
Delwath: I'll try and scare them.
DM: Okay. Let's... Hold on one sec.
DM: [paper rustling] I mean,
DM: they're, you know, they're kind of...
Delwath: I just want them to tell me what their orders were.
Delwath: I don't, they don't need to betray the dragon.
Delwath: They don't need to do anything. Just what do you do?
Delwath: Why'd you come here? What are you doing here?
Delwath: We won't kill you. [paper rustling]
DM: Um.
Delwath: But you're not going anyf- anywhere for a while, and you got to spell why you came here.
Unknown: That's it.
DM: Uh, what language are they asking then?
Delwath: They only speak, uh... Oh, I'd probably have to have to cast tongues.
Delwath: Um, they don't speak Common, do they?
DM: They don't speak Common.
Delwath: I can, I, I'll just cast tongues.
Unknown: It's fine.
DM: Okay.
DM: One sec. I'll be right back.
DM: [sighs] [coughs] I mean, they're, they're like a bit freaked.
DM: It's like everybody's up in arms.
DM: All the dragonets have been sent
DM: everywhere across the island.
DM: We're to keep watch
DM: and report back ev- in two hours if anything shows up.
Delwath: And they don't report back.
Delwath: So it's okay. Maybe it's okay if she just comes here in two hours.
Delwath: What are we waiting for?
Wellby: Are there any others posted to this area of the island, like this sector?
Wellby: Where, where are the nearest ones?
Wellby: Can we move to other buildings in this complex?
DM: She was very mad. I don't know.
DM: They're everywhere.
Delwath: Did you fly over here with any, anybody else?
Delwath: You guys come here and split up or just the two of you?
DM: Ten of us.
Delwath: There's probably ten covering the top of the monastery.
Unknown: There's eight temples. Well, great.
Wellby: In two hours, everybody else flies back.
Wellby: We can move to one of the other buildings.
Unknown: Why do we want to move to another building?
Wellby: So she doesn't just come and breathe acid through the roof
Wellby: and kill us while we're all waiting inside.
Unknown: I mean, like
Unknown: these people
Delwath: think we're... We...
Unknown: Yeah, sure.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I, I will, I will, uh, thank them for their honesty and tell them, um-
Delwath: So are you, uh...
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I'll ask them if they know either of our two f- Gresh- Gresher.
Delwath: What's her name? M-
DM: Megren?
DM: Yeah.
DM: No.
Delwath: Are you, um,
Delwath: are you one of the true believers?
Delwath: Are you just scared of her?
DM: Who?
DM: Looks kind of confused by the question.
Unknown: True believer.
DM: We all believe she's the queen of the island.
Delwath: When she's dead, are you gonna be happy or sad?
DM: Surprised.
Unknown: [laughs] I mean, as an aside, why don't we just tell these people to tell her we're waiting
Unknown: for her here?
DM: Sure.
Unknown: And then not be here.
Unknown: Wait. Uh,
Kenzo: would we want to fight her, though?
Delwath: Well, somewhere around here, but, but...
Kenzo: What's our plan?
Delwath: Well, we have two hours. We'll make it in a minute.
Delwath: Okay. Um-
Kenzo: And put some music.
DM: Oh, yeah, yeah.
Delwath: So I'm gonna, um, I'm gonna tell them we might have more to say in a bit.
Delwath: You know, we'll go away from them.
Unknown: Siri here. Let me know if I can help.
Delwath: Um, I'm gonna
Delwath: reset... I mean, I'll reset the links.
DM: Uh, I don't think your...
DM: Is your thing on?
Kenzo: Uh, Schwartz, want me to pass away? Should be.
Unknown: [gentle music]
DM: There we
DM: go. Reset the links?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And you're going back into the tunnels?
Delwath: I think, well, we're gonna talk for a little bit.
Wellby: Do we have heroic inspiration again after long rest?
Unknown: Yes.
Seeker: Oh, nice.
Delwath: We'll cook... That with a cooked breakfast.
Unknown: And plus 20.
Delwath: Midnight breakfast.
Unknown: Yeah, I... Yes.
Unknown: Midnight breakfast.
Delwath: Yeah. Midnight snack.
Unknown: Nice tasty midnight snack.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: man, that's a good feat. I'm glad I took that feat.
Seeker: Heroic inspiration. Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: We're using it a lot.
Kenzo: Oh, man. It's fucking so useful.
DM: It's huge. I mean, so is alert.
Delwath: Alert is also great.
Unknown: Alert's been incredibly useful.
Delwath: Oh, my God. Yeah, also good. What did you take as your origin feat?
DM: Crafter.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: Which is very Seeker.
Delwath: That'll be good.
DM: He's gonna get a lot of use out of it later.
Delwath: That'll be good when we go and make all the magic items at the forge.
Seeker: Oh, yeah, we can make stuff.
Delwath: Um, so I think the plan is to send these folks back
Delwath: to honestly report that we're here in this place,
Unknown: and then move.
Kenzo: How do we move?
Unknown: We just walk to another building.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: But we should decide where we want to be.
Wellby: I like fighting her from the lighthouse.
Unknown: Highest point on the island.
Delwath: Like go up to the top?
Unknown: We're gonna need the air. Yeah.
Wellby: Maybe there's a way to turn it on.
Seeker: Is that helpful? It's broken.
DM: Oh, it's broken?
Seeker: Yeah, it's cracked.
Delwath: So remind me of the setup at the top of the mountain.
Delwath: There's the eight temples around the central lighthouse.
DM: There's the eight temples around a courtyard, and then there's this, the lighthouse in the middle that has a bell and then a cracked lighthouse mechanism on the top.
Unknown: Mm.
Wellby: I mean, maybe... I don't know. Maybe we can put a drift glyphs in there or something.
Wellby: Like it'd be nice not to be in total darkness fighting her,
Kenzo: which may not be- It's 1:00 in the morning right now, right?
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: It's like midnight.
Wellby: 3:00 they all report back?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Kind of want to know where Tilly and Milo are.
Kenzo: I'm sure they're doing great.
Delwath: Yeah, but if they're coming here...
Delwath: Well, we'll see what happens, I guess.
DM: So what are you doing at the moment?
DM: Just waiting?
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: I think so.
Seeker: Oh, I should do long rest.
DM: Yeah. Everybody should long rest.
Unknown: Like,
Delwath: I mean, let's, let's, uh, wait two hours
Delwath: and then send these dragons back.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: I mean, we could even send them back...
Delwath: They might not pass it along, but we could tell them, you know, tell, uh,
Delwath: tell Ra'ghemdros that, you know, we don't think she's, can hurt us, and we're leaving, you know.
Delwath: We... I don't know, try and piss her off and make her come after us unstrategically.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: something like...
Unknown: Like... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: I don't know what the message would be.
Unknown: You know, we're, um...
Wellby: We're resting now, but we'll be ready to meet with her at dawn.
Unknown: There you go.
Wellby: If she'd like to come to see us then, this is where we'll be.
Delwath: Yeah. We took, we, we took, we took what we believe is our fa- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Delwath: We took our fair payment
Unknown: from her.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: And, uh, we're resting in the Sibyl's temple, which is an, you know, a sacred space, and we expect that she won't violate it,
Delwath: and we'll be prepared to meet her at dawn, uh, outside the temple.
Wellby: She should come to us then.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah. She should come meet us at dawn here.
Wellby: And we freed her from the burden of having to, uh-
Delwath: Right. Yeah
Unknown: ... keep her prisoner trapped.
Unknown: We... Right.
Kenzo: And she'll thank us. So much, she has so much gratitude for us.
Delwath: Yeah. We did her a favor.
DM: Okay So you're gonna just wait the two hours and let them go with that message?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um, about an hour later, 2:00 in the morning, um, you see
DM: Tilly and Milo walking up the path,
DM: like looking around for you.
DM: You're not... Are you hiding still in the tunnels?
Delwath: Yeah, we're back in the tunnels, right?
Unknown: Okay. Well, so the-
Unknown: Nobody knows. Watching out
DM: ... the links, the links triggers another alarm then.
Delwath: So we'll walk out again.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Yeah.
DM: Dimitaur is, "The..."
DM: Wait.
Unknown: Shh, shh.
DM: She doesn't say anything.
Unknown: [laughs] Shh.
Wellby: Uh, we'll reach out to them telepathically.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: There you go.
Unknown: And say where we are and...
DM: Uh,
DM: I hope you're ready to fight an army.
Unknown: An army?
Wellby: When you say an army...
DM: You can see her up in the sky.
DM: She's flying around with about 15 dragonets and four chimeras.
Seeker: Yeah, we should anticipate that.
Unknown: Oh, that's...
Delwath: Ah, this is when-
Wellby: Nothing that the fireballs can't solve.
Delwath: Wow, but hold on.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: we should... It would be...
Delwath: Wait, hold on, hold on. I gotta look at my actual...
Delwath: Um, hold on one second. I just want to look at my w- my messenger one more and see what it actually, the actual name.
Seeker: Just by raw firepower, that's not,
Seeker: not a situation we want to be in, I don't think, is it?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Uh, so when you summon the links, it can...
Delwath: It's an action to summon.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: It can do... It can travel 50 miles an hour for two hours per day.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Right? But going 50 miles an hour to and from the coast-
DM: Yeah
Delwath: ... is only taking...
Delwath: I can do that five times.
DM: Yep.
Delwath: And I've only done it four times.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: So
Delwath: send a message to Ghesh and...
Delwath: Right? Last ditch, Kenzo, what, what are you gonna say to them to convince them to come help us?
Unknown: Um, tell them that, um...
Kenzo: Oh, well, they, they also don't know that all of us are here, right?
Kenzo: Or they do, they know... Oh, yeah, they know that they're...
Kenzo: I've got, like, magic animals or something.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Yeah. I'll tell them, um, you know, we conquered the, uh, uh, we conquered the dangers in the west.
Kenzo: We, um,
Kenzo: we freed, um, the, the dragons captive,
Kenzo: uh, that's been held captive for hundreds of years, and now we're gonna kill the dragon.
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: we've
Kenzo: killed several of the dragons.
Kenzo: Uh, [laughs] you should have total confidence in our success.
Unknown: No, uh...
Delwath: I think something like, um,
Delwath: you've expressed displeasure about Ra'ghemdros's rule before.
Delwath: She's coming to fight us now with the true believer dragonets, and we're gonna kill her.
Delwath: And any help you could provide
Delwath: will inc- like, I don't know.
Kenzo: No, I think it's also just like, like, look, um,
Kenzo: you don't like the dragon.
Kenzo: We don't like the dragon.
Delwath: N- this is your chance.
Kenzo: We're gonna kill the dragon for sure.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: And, um-
Delwath: But, but we need your help
Kenzo: ... we need your help.
Kenzo: Um, and the... what... all we need you to do is to, uh, just hold off the other, the other-
Delwath: Yeah, just hold off the true believers.
Kenzo: Hold off the true believers. We'll handle the dragon.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: And after, by noon tomorrow, the whole island is gonna be yours.
Delwath: Yeah, we're, yeah, we're gonna give the island to the dragon.
Unknown: The whole-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... uh, the whole island will be the dragonets' free of a dragon
Unknown: by-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... by, by noon tomorrow.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: By later. By... And all you have to do-
Delwath: And we'll give you your first pick of the thing from her, non-magical item from the horde.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: First choice.
Unknown: Yeah. First-
Delwath: Everybody, everybody who fights.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
Delwath: Anybody who fights.
Kenzo: Anybody who fights. Well, actually, we'll, we'll say anybody who fights, um, um-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... gets, gets-
Delwath: Well, no. Ghesh and
Delwath: Ma- Magen, Magen?
DM: Megren.
Delwath: Megren get first pick.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: But anybody who fights gets something from the horde.
Kenzo: Get something from the horde.
DM: Something shiny from the horde.
Unknown: Something, something good.
Kenzo: Some- something shine, something shiny from the horde.
DM: Really shiny.
Kenzo: Yeah. Really shiny.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: And all they have to do-
Delwath: And spread the word. Any dragonet who fights against-
Unknown: Spread the word. Yes, get something from the horde.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: We'll take the dragons.
Delwath: And any leader, any tower commander who fights can get their first pick of something from the horde,
Delwath: as long as it's not magical.
Wellby: And as long as we all get to pick before them.
Delwath: No.
Unknown: Yeah. What do you mean? We're gonna, we're gonna let them pick non-magical stuff.
Delwath: Who cares?
Wellby: But the throne.
Wellby: I guess we can't take it anyways.
Unknown: Yeah, like, who cares? No.
Unknown: No, but just, just... Well, the...
Kenzo: We'll, we'll promise them some sweet items from the island.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Just, you know.
Delwath: But I think Ghesh and...
Delwath: They deserve first pick.
Unknown: Yeah, that's fine. Yeah.
Unknown: Right? Ghesh and Magen- Magenda.
Unknown: We can give them, we can give them great stuff.
Kenzo: They'll, they'll get some cool stuff.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So I'll send 50 miles an hour.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: So it would... Six miles, right?
Delwath: Or something like that.
DM: It's like...
DM: No, it's like 15 miles from the coast from here.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: Um, well, ask Milo how far out-
Delwath: So I probably don't have enough to get a message response.
Delwath: No response.
DM: How far out are the dragons?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: I mean,
DM: not so close.
DM: They're in the east now.
DM: She seems to be doing a circle around the entire island.
DM: I think you got two hours, if you're lucky.
Delwath: So when these guys leave, I think, I think the next step, we sent our message to-
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... hopefully something comes of it Um,
Unknown: I mean,
Unknown: should we tell these people to spread the word?
Wellby: Which people?
Delwath: The two who were kidnapped.
Seeker: We want them on our side too.
Wellby: They, no, no, they left.
Unknown: They haven't left.
DM: They haven't left.
Delwath: Toil came back first.
Wellby: Oh, wow.
Seeker: And it's like factionally are they loyal to-
Delwath: Who knows? But like can we, should we just tell them?
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: We want them.
Unknown: We want-
Seeker: The most loyal could probably be swayed by enough treasure.
Delwath: Look, we tell them.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: It's easier if Kenzo does it so I don't have to cast another spell, 'cause then I can't speak Draconic.
Delwath: But tell them,
Delwath: give the message to-
Kenzo: Spread the word.
Unknown: Sp-
Kenzo: Spread the word far and wide that the last, the dragon's last night is tonight.
Delwath: And that anybody-
Unknown: That by...
Kenzo: Anybody that participates will get part of that shiny thing from the treasure.
Kenzo: It's your opportunity to be free.
Kenzo: The island will be yours.
Unknown: By, by, by laying low the dragon.
Unknown: And we pull out some examples, like this is the kind of shiny thing you can get.
Delwath: Yeah. But like we have to see them in the sky.
Unknown: We're not messing around. [laughs]
Delwath: We have to see them in the sky in the battle.
Delwath: They can't just like fly.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: But they don't have to fight the dragon.
Kenzo: They do not have to fight the dragon.
Delwath: They only have to fight other dragonets.
Wellby: Yep, yep.
Unknown: Right? They can-
Kenzo: But tonight, but tonight is the last night-
Unknown: Right
Kenzo: ... of Raghemldros' rule.
Delwath: Yeah. That's actually, we should put this in the scrolls too.
Delwath: The deal I think we should make with the dragonets is any dragonet who shows up in the battle
Delwath: who fights other dragonets, they can run away as soon as there are no-
Wellby: Yeah
Delwath: ... dragonets still fighting for Raghemda.
Wellby: Good.
Delwath: Right? But they have to show up and fight in the sky.
Unknown: We have to see them.
Wellby: Okay.
Delwath: And if they, they do that, they get something from the hoard.
Kenzo: And they get to be part of this, this future without Raghemldros.
Unknown: Right.
Delwath: We'll tell them to. I mean-
Wellby: All right
Unknown: ... be interesting to see how do they react.
DM: Um,
DM: make an insight check. Or Kenzo.
DM: Kenzo's the insider. Or Well- do you have insight, Wellby?
Wellby: Mm-hmm. I have great insight.
DM: Okay. Both of you can make an insight check.
Kenzo: I have extremely good. 20 something, 25 I think.
Wellby: Uh, 23 for me.
DM: Yeah. They're...
Kenzo: 25, I think.
DM: They're, uh, they're definitely curious.
DM: I mean...
Unknown: Just tell your friends
DM: ... they're, they're trying not to let on anything, but they're kind of like, "Um, okay."
DM: So an hour passes.
DM: Two o'clock.
Delwath: I mean, we should climb up to the tower at some point, right?
DM: Um-
Seeker: How, how am I gonna...
Seeker: If I'm gonna fully prep,
Seeker: I will activate the ladder.
Delwath: It, it's hard to know.
Delwath: Those are pretty fast to do, right?
Seeker: The ladder is an action.
DM: The spell's an action. The ladder's an action.
DM: If you want to do a construct on the ladder then.
Seeker: Yeah. But the construct isn't able to fly, does it?
DM: So, right, maybe you pick something else.
Unknown: Yeah. Well.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I mean, it would be nice if we could...
Delwath: Is there any way we can think of to get...
Delwath: I mean, it's gonna be, in theory, we should be able to see her coming, although not if it's dark.
Wellby: It'll be getting close to dawn though, right?
Wellby: It'll be 5:00 by the time she gets there?
DM: Well, the dragonets are gone at 3:00.
DM: You still got like an hour till like pre-dawn twilight, and two hours till dawn.
Wellby: I think we should go see if we can turn on the...
Delwath: Let's go tinker with the thing.
Wellby: Might as well.
Delwath: I mean, we may as well climb up there, right?
Delwath: Like that, we want that to be our-
Wellby: If nothing else, it would be deeply epic.
Delwath: It would be, to get the lighthouse on.
Seeker: Hell yeah. And what does this even do?
Seeker: Yeah, I should go. I can identify again today.
Kenzo: Yeah, iden- d- Dimitar.
Kenzo: Dimitar's been living here for like 40 years.
Kenzo: How does it work?
DM: I mean,
DM: there used to be
DM: something in the center,
DM: some sort of crystal that generated light, I think.
Unknown: Like you climb up there, you poke around.
DM: I don't-
Delwath: We just try putting a driftglobe in and see what happens
DM: ... flies so well anymore, but there's like a, it's like hollow in the middle.
DM: Some of the crystals are broken.
DM: I think it used to ha- you know, shine precisely.
Seeker: Precisely where?
DM: I don't know.
Delwath: Let's go investigate it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: Is it just like eight faceted?
DM: Yeah.
DM: So you climb up.
Unknown: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
DM: And so it's, it's, it's eight faceted, and like Seeker is pretty good at this sort of stuff.
DM: You'd think the way it would've normally worked is like it could have shined along the paths of the pilgrim roads, and it would
DM: splinter the light so it would shine across the, all the pilgrim roads at night so that they would have-
Seeker: To light their way.
DM: Yeah. Right.
Wellby: That's really cool.
DM: But two of the, two of the facets are broken, and there's clearly, like there's clearly supposed to be something big in the middle.
Seeker: So it'd be much more powerful in a dr- driftglobe.
Unknown: But...
DM: Well, maybe not in daylight.
DM: Definitely way more powerful than a lantern.
Delwath: But daylight lasts for an hour.
Wellby: Lasts for an hour, and we have two driftglobes.
Wellby: We can do two dope.
Delwath: But, but before we do any, like can Seeker futz about and see if you, see if it would even...
Delwath: Before we trigger daylight, just use the regular light and it, does it, does it, is it weak, right?
Unknown: Does it do anything?
Unknown: Oh, let's-
Wellby: I think we don't want to turn it on because as soon as we turn it on-
Seeker: We telegraph our position a little bit.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Oh, that's true. Well-
Seeker: But didn't we tell them where to meet us anyway?
Unknown: True.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Why do-
Wellby: Can you figure out... So it, it shines in these like spotlights, but will it give ambient light around the top of the tower?
DM: I mean, the, the, the way that-
Unknown: That's a good question
DM: ... the way that you imagine it-
Seeker: We could set it up a different way than it was before
DM: ... well, the way you imagine it would've worked is the whole top of the mountain would be glowing with light.
Unknown: And the beams would come down. Cut
DM: And then there would be beams coming down.
DM: Now, it's cracked.
DM: Two of the panels are broken entirely and definitely could not be repaired, and a third panel is like shifted out of place and is misaligned.
Delwath: I mean, if we could just get enough light to give us...
Delwath: I mean, the ideal goal here is really to get enough light to- We'd love to have three rounds notice before she's close enough to do anything, 'cause then you could cast your stuff.
Delwath: Like there's a bunch of stuff you can do to prep.
Seeker: Mm-hmm.
Delwath: Cast Fly, cast-
Seeker: Oh, so the light might actually help see her-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... from longer range.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: I can also start shooting at 270 feet now.
Seeker: Oh, that's nice. Wow.
Wellby: Which is a long way.
Unknown: That is.
Seeker: So can I use Mending on the broken part?
Unknown: Um,
DM: so you could... Mending?
DM: Yes. The ones that are like shattered, there's too much-
Unknown: Mm
Unknown: ... material missing.
DM: But the one that's just like cracked out of place you could fix with Mending, yeah.
Seeker: And then I suppose I could Performance of Creation like
Seeker: missing crystal chunks.
Unknown: Yeah. Why not?
Seeker: That would ruin my Performance of Creation.
Seeker: I don't usually need that for anything else w- when I'm animating the ladder.
DM: And you can do two things, right?
Unknown: So two, two chunks.
Unknown: Two chunks.
Seeker: It's probably worth doing.
Delwath: I mean, you took the craft feat.
Delwath: You may as well craft something.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right.
Unknown: You paid 60 gold. [laughs]
Unknown: I will set about fully repairing.
Unknown: Hell yeah.
Unknown: I like it.
DM: Let's go.
Unknown: Awesome.
Delwath: And yeah, we have daylight to power it, right?
DM: It takes some tinkering to get it w- it's probably gonna take you about half an hour to get it working.
Seeker: Oh, and then this, the repaired piece only lasts for five hours.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: That's okay
Unknown: It's not a permanent repair, but yeah.
Unknown: Five hours.
Wellby: You'll need it during that very fight.
Unknown: One way or other, this'll be over in five hours.
Unknown: That's true.
Unknown: Probably.
Delwath: Or it'll also be dawn and then we won't need it. [laughs]
Unknown: Or it'll be dawn.
Unknown: It'll be light out.
DM: It's gonna be dawn in two hours.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Uh, you probably have... Now with Seeker's tinker, you probably have half an hour before like the expectation of when she'd arrive.
DM: But I was like,
DM: "So what's the plan?
DM: I mean, I know we're not big on plans, right?
Unknown: But..."
Delwath: Okay. Can you fly?
DM: He takes out a potion.
DM: I mean, yeah.
Delwath: How long does it last?
Unknown: An hour.
Delwath: Good enough. Uh, and can Tilly fly?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: But
DM: he looks at Delwath.
DM: Do you have a bow?
Unknown: No.
DM: I'm not one to, you know,
DM: hide from a fight,
DM: but maybe it would make more sense for me to shoot arrows from cover.
Unknown: Sure.
Unknown: If you want to fly.
Unknown: Oh, hey.
Wellby: You have an extra bow, shortbow.
Unknown: I'll, I'll take that trade.
Unknown: You have a, you have a bow.
Unknown: No, he has a bow.
DM: Is it a good bow?
Wellby: Uh, it's a sh- sh- you know.
DM: But not magic.
Wellby: Uh, I have arrows I can give you.
DM: I, I'd take some arrows.
Unknown: I mean, uh, yeah.
Delwath: I think th- I think that's a good trade.
Wellby: Oh, shoot. Yes. I know what I'm gonna do.
Wellby: I'm gonna give him 20 of the honed accurate scare arrows so he also does not have disadvantage at long range.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: Anyone want ice cream?
Delwath: Yeah. I'll get some ice cream.
Delwath: I'll come serve myself in a minute. Oh, potion of heroism.
Unknown: What's that?
Delwath: I have a potion of heroism.
Delwath: It blasts. It's 1D4 to every attack roll.
DM: Tilly says...
Delwath: Who's that gonna be most useful for?
Unknown: I mean, I've...
DM: When the dragon comes-
Unknown: I like Kenzo
DM: ... how much warning do we think we'll have?
DM: 'Cause I can summon my own draconic spirit to fight it.
Delwath: Uh, we think...
Delwath: Well, look, so-
Seeker: Who's saying that?
Unknown: Tilly
Unknown: Tilly.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: if, uh, if our friend Seeker here can repair this light which we're working on, and he's quite, I'm quite confident in his abilities.
Delwath: We're almost there.
Delwath: We're hoping to shine a light.
Delwath: We expect it will be, I mean, what?
Delwath: It's gonna be at least 1,000 feet, right?
Unknown: We should have at least-
DM: Well, the ra- I mean, so the minimum range daylight is what?
DM: 60 feet?
Unknown: I think something like that.
DM: So your minimum is 60 feet, which wouldn't do you much good.
Delwath: No, it does no good at all.
DM: I hope that you'll be able to increase that by a fair bit.
DM: 300, 1,000.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: You don't know quite how much.
Wellby: 300, the dragon can probably-
Delwath: Uh, it's 120. Daylight's 120.
Wellby: Right.
Delwath: It's 60 foot bright, 60 foot dim.
Wellby: Dim. Dragon can probably move 120 per round.
Delwath: Yeah. And it's gonna have breath and things.
Delwath: We need, we need, we need five...
Delwath: To have a round, we need to see it at 500 feet I think would be my guess.
Delwath: If we can see it at 500 feet we can get spells off before it can close to us.
Delwath: That would be the ideal. That's our goal is I mean a thou- Like that would be my guess, right?
Wellby: If I was the dragon, I would also send in my minions first to soften us up and then
Wellby: come in myself second.
Wellby: Although the dragon may not do that.
Delwath: Um, okay. This is-
Unknown: W- we're, we're-
DM: ... not anywhere close to enough space so each square is gonna be 10 feet.
Delwath: Use the little mini... Um, uh, let's see.
Unknown: Do you want the ice cream out or put it away?
Unknown: Uh, put it a- put it away.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Um, don't they, there are no little mini squares on there too?
DM: Oh, yeah, yeah. So each mini square.
Unknown: It's hard to use our figures on the mini squares.
DM: Let's just say each, each square is...
DM: I mean, you're all gonna be flying anyway, so it's gonna be tough to track.
Delwath: That's true.
Unknown: Um...
Kenzo: The stack dice is nice, but each one represents 10, 10 feet.
Unknown: Who...
Delwath: Kenzo, do you have any useful potions?
Unknown: Potion?
Delwath: I'm thinking... So I have a potion of heroism which lets you add a 1D4 to your attack to your D20 rolls.
Unknown: Hmm.
Delwath: I'm thinking Kenzo might be the best to...
Delwath: 'Cause you make the most attacks.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: Make a lot of attacks.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So it gives you the most-
Wellby: That's good
Delwath: ... it's like, 'cause each attack you get an extra 1D4 to hit, so like it gives you the most.
Unknown: Oh, extra 1D4 to hit?
Delwath: Yeah. It's to your D20 checks.
Unknown: Oh, sick.
Delwath: Any D20 check. Not damage, but...
Unknown: For every D20 check?
Delwath: Yeah. You get, you add a 1D4.
Kenzo: That's pretty awesome.
Kenzo: Yeah. I would like that.
Delwath: And you also get 10 temporary hit points.
Wellby: I have a potion of Haste.
Unknown: You have a potion of Haste?
Unknown: Oh, fuck.
Wellby: Which feels like it could be a good thing, 'cause I could do two...
Wellby: Basically two sneak attacks per round,
Wellby: and I could start shooting-
Unknown: Teleport scroll
Wellby: ... like the chimeras.
Unknown: So-
Unknown: What's the Haste do again?
Unknown: Use that and grapple.
Wellby: An extra action.
Seeker: Well, we would've had to had the idea before.
Delwath: The four.
DM: Well, I gave you a free potion of Flying to make up for it, so.
Unknown: Yeah, I know.
Unknown: Oh, yeah, Haste would be awesome.
DM: But also, Milo and Tilly only level 10, so they're a little bit nervous of the breath weapon, which could one-hit them.
Unknown: They're level 10?
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: What class are they, druid and-
DM: Druid and rogue.
Wellby: Oh, sweet.
DM: This is the basic arrangement.
DM: These are the eight temples.
Delwath: But, but we're gonna be a...
Delwath: So I think our goal here is to-
DM: [laughs] This is gonna be a complicated fight.
Unknown: It's gonna be super complicated.
Kenzo: Oh, wait, I have a potion of Growth.
Delwath: I don't know if that helps that much. What does it do?
Wellby: Add one?
DM: It adds 1d4 to your... It makes you large, and it adds 1d4 to every damage.
Wellby: Oh.
Unknown: Wow.
DM: That's-
Kenzo: I mean, giant Kenzo is pretty...
Kenzo: That'd be pretty fun.
Kenzo: Giant flying Kenzo.
Delwath: What else do we have?
Delwath: Advantage on strength checks, enlarged weapons are on strength, meh.
Delwath: What does Haste do? It lets you make-
Wellby: +2 to AC, advantage on dex, and an additional attack action-
Unknown: While in Haste
Wellby: ... or death doesn't get you out of it.
Delwath: Um, do we have any other potions?
Kenzo: I have a bunch of healing potions.
Delwath: I have a bunch of healing potions too, and a potion of Heroism.
Kenzo: What does that do?
Delwath: That's the one that would give you 1d4.
Unknown: Oh.
Kenzo: I mean, what the fuck? I'll do the potion of Growth.
DM: Use it.
Delwath: I mean, you could just...
Delwath: Yeah, like why not?
Unknown: Well...
DM: Um, Tilly is gonna say
DM: she could also give you a few ex-...
DM: Oh, wait. You already have a-
Unknown: Yep
DM: ... you can't
Delwath: Ah, but, um, Seeker, the...
Delwath: She should cast Aid on,
Delwath: she should cast Aid on Wellby, herself, and Milo.
DM: Oh, yeah, okay. So Wellby, you get 15 extra hit points from Tilly.
Kenzo: Yeah, I get an extra 1, 1d4 extra damage.
Kenzo: Yeah, for sure. I'll be enlarged.
Delwath: You take the potion of Heroism too.
Kenzo: Wow. All right.
Wellby: 15 temporary hit points?
Unknown: No.
DM: No, 15... It's like a-
Delwath: Increase your hit point maximum by 15
DM: ... hit point maximum increased by 15.
Kenzo: Who said that that bonus 20 from you, uh, Wellby was?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: You don't have anything good?
Seeker: I don't have much that I can pull out for this fight.
Seeker: There's the scrolls.
Seeker: Teleport, Resurrection. Private sanctum.
Unknown: Oh, wrong.
Unknown: It's just not-
DM: Yeah, but it's not-
Unknown: For this situation
DM: ... yeah, yeah, yeah. No potions?
Delwath: Clairvoyance. I used the Watchful Rest.
DM: You should take that.
Kenzo: Oh, how do I do copy Kenzo again, Tim?
Unknown: Oh, we were gonna do that-
DM: Oh, right
Unknown: ... anyway.
DM: Of course.
Kenzo: Um, I, I opened... I, I restarted my computer.
DM: Oh, it's this one. Sorry, it's that one right there.
Seeker: And the Summon Construct is only useful if it can fly, and it's concentration.
Unknown: Ah, nice, nice, nice.
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: Uh-
Unknown: It's not gonna be able to do anything.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah. If it can't fly, it's not gonna be useful.
DM: Wait, it's medium, right?
DM: The golem is medium.
DM: Yeah.
DM: It can ride the, it can ride the ladder.
Seeker: And if I, if I flavor the ladder-
DM: With air, it gets a 40 foot fly speed.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: All right. All right. Yeah, actually-
Delwath: I mean, Quagga will ride the ladder.
Delwath: What, what, what do you want?
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: I mean, does Seeker really wanna ride the ladder into combat?
Seeker: Oh, but then I'll have no way to fly.
DM: You won't be able to fly.
Unknown: But that's okay, you hide.
DM: You hide on the ground with Milo.
Delwath: Our, our plan is to have a hiding group, which is Milo and you.
DM: All right.
Delwath: And Wellby, actually.
DM: Well, Wellby can fly as necessary.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah. And an attacking group,
Unknown: which is me and Kenzo.
Unknown: That's it?
Unknown: And what about the ladder?
DM: The dragon.
Unknown: And-
DM: And the dragon that Tilly summons-
Unknown: The, the dragon spirit-
DM: And the ladder
Delwath: ... and the ladder with the Quagga riding on top of the ladder.
Kenzo: Okay. Quagga on the ladder, we need them.
Unknown: Yeah, we definitely-
DM: Quagga on ladder, Tilly's dragon spirit-
Unknown: All right
DM: ... Kenzo as Dalith-
Unknown: Um-
DM: ... is the attack group.
Wellby: We got an army too.
DM: [laughs] Yeah, well, you're gonna need it.
Unknown: Holy shit.
Seeker: It's about to get crazy.
DM: So-
Kenzo: And w- wait, and Dimitar
DM: ...
DM: Dimitar is in the hide group.
Unknown: Hey, Mike.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Wand of Fireball and Mass Charge.
Unknown: I'm looking at the-
Wellby: What?
Seeker: There's a different construct st- approach, the stone one.
Wellby: Does either one of you have Divination?
Unknown: Tilly made a big difference in the last fight.
Wellby: Do any of us have Divination?
Seeker: But speed halved would make a huge difference-
Unknown: Oh, yeah
Kenzo: ... for the dragon.
Unknown: Yes.
Seeker: But it has to start its turn.
Wellby: This would be useful to know.
Unknown: No.
Wellby: Is the dragon gonna be in the first wave of the attack?
Unknown: When Tilly summons the spirit.
DM: Tilly starts the turn with 10 speed.
Seeker: So it's pretty unlikely that it would, but it could happen.
Unknown: Oh, we can ask Augur.
DM: Wow.
DM: Augur is just like, "Is this a good idea?"
Unknown: If the ladder managed to fly up right up to the dragon.
Delwath: I mean, but the ladder's gonna grab...
Delwath: No, the ladder flies up and grapples the dragon.
DM: [laughs]
Delwath: Hanging on for dear life while the golem pounds it with his fists.
Seeker: Yeah.
Delwath: And does that.
DM: I mean, the dragon is 30 feet from, and has, like, a 60 foot wingspan.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: The golem could just drop, jump on its back.
Unknown: Right.
Kenzo: Right. All right.
Delwath: Wait, is it huge?
Seeker: But, Tim, I was just thinking about using-
Unknown: Or gargantuan
Seeker: ... gargantuan. I was thinking about using this, the stony golem.
DM: Okay.
Seeker: The stone golem, 'cause that can still stay down.
DM: Oh, it can slow it. Yeah, yeah.
DM: I mean, you can also try Slow.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Do either of you have Divination?
Wellby: 'Cause it would be useful to know if the dragon will be in the first wave of the attack.
Unknown: Hmm.
Wellby: We do have a magic item, but it's a one use.
Wellby: I don't know if you want to use it.
Kenzo: Feels like a pretty good time though.
Kenzo: Although, first wave, I mean,
Unknown: why not?
Unknown: Does that really affect-
Delwath: Oh, that lasts 10 minutes.
Delwath: The Font of Moonlight lasts 10 minutes.
Unknown: That's the-
DM: Yeah, that's the idea. You can cast it 'cause it's an action, so you're supposed to is, for a moon druid, you change and you bonus action-
Delwath: Change and cast it
DM: ... change and cast it, like, when you're about to open the door.
Delwath: Yeah. But that means if we get any kind of...
Delwath: If we have any...
DM: That also sheds light.
Delwath: It sheds light in 20, in 40 feet.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: But the cool thing is if I take damage, it's a, I can blind creatures.
DM: Right.
Delwath: Although it uses my reaction, which is massively over subscribed as it begins with.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Yeah. You might wanna save your reaction to not die.
Seeker: I guess I need to-
DM: It's probably more valuable for shield than for-
Seeker: ... get a new napkin for my now dirty napkin
Delwath: Well, not if the dragon is fleeing breath weapons.
DM: If the dragon is running. [laughs]
Delwath: Like, if I get hit with a breath weapon-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... it's any damage.
DM: Right.
Unknown: Oh, oh, okay.
Delwath: It's not a melee attack.
DM: Right. Right, right.
Delwath: Immediately after you take damage from a creature.
DM: Um,
DM: Tilly will also hand out two goodberries to everybody.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: And say, "If anybody drops, feed them a berry."
Unknown: Nice.
Unknown: Yep.
Delwath: Wait, didn't we say Kenzo? Kenzo has goodberries now too.
Delwath: I think I have goodberries.
DM: Oh, you can do that too.
Kenzo: But the goodberries are only, like, one hit point.
Unknown: Yeah, but it'll bring you back-
DM: Yeah, but if you're at zero, it brings you up
Delwath: ... if you're at zero it brings you up to one.
DM: So it's a good way to not die.
Seeker: That sometimes matters.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um, let's see.
DM: I don't think Tilly's got any other prep, unless you want to hide.
DM: She can cast Pass Without a Trace, but your strategy is the exact opposite of hide.
DM: You're trying to get as much bright light as possible.
Delwath: I mean, Tilly and Milo
Delwath: should look for... Wait, is Dimitar gonna come fight with us or is he gonna give-
Wellby: He's in the hide group
Delwath: ... the wand of fireballs to somebody?
DM: No, no, he's in the hide group.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: He's gonna shoot the wand of fireballs.
Unknown: And then run. Yeah, fine.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: How many people can be in your telepathy at once?
DM: I think it's... Is it eight or six?
DM: Eric?
Seeker: Uh, the Telepathy 3 is...
Unknown: Sorry, I was doing hit points.
DM: No, no, that's okay.
Seeker: Is, uh...
Seeker: I thought it was eight, but let me check.
DM: Teleport is eight. I can't remember.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Uh, eight.
DM: Okay. So you can get Dimitar, Milo, Tilly, and the four of you.
Unknown: Yep.
Wellby: Perfect.
Delwath: Okay. So the potion of fly's an hour?
DM: It's an hour.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: So the real thing, I think...
Delwath: Is there any reason not to just-
Wellby: Light the light and get going
Delwath: ... light the light and get going?
Wellby: What are we waiting for?
Wellby: Once everyone's in position, once they've got in good hide spots.
DM: Yeah. So Dimitar, I don't, we don't need, don't have good tokens for all these people, but that's okay.
DM: 'Cause,
DM: okay, Dimitar,
DM: Dimitar is gonna... Dimitar is staying in his Temple of the Civil.
DM: Um, he's actually gonna be on the roof of the Temple of the Civil.
Delwath: I'm just thinking the more warning we have before they appear, the better off we are.
DM: Are you using divination?
Kenzo: Oh, we can start using long range weapons and shooting at stuff.
Delwath: And casting... Like, I have
Delwath: two spells that I could,
Delwath: two prep spells that I could cast.
Delwath: One to give me bonus insights-
DM: [coughs]
Delwath: ... and one to,
Delwath: uh, give me extra damage.
DM: Right.
Delwath: And, like, you have all these potions, but they only last an hour.
Delwath: It's hard to know when to drink yet.
DM: Yeah. Right.
DM: So we should do a-
Delwath: How long does the potion of growth last?
Delwath: Is it an hour or 10 minutes?
Kenzo: Um, is...
Kenzo: It's, it's, it's a bunch of hours.
Seeker: I'll do the construct at sixth level,
Seeker: which gives it AC-
Unknown: 1d4 hours. No concentration required.
Delwath: 1d4? That's unusual.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Oh, yeah. [laughs] That's kind of random.
Kenzo: Eh, I mean, whatever.
DM: Okay. Here's Tilly the panoramic spirit-
Unknown: I'll just be huge for a while
DM: ...
DM: when it gets summoned.
Kenzo: Oh, 10 more temporary hit points. That's nice.
DM: Um-
Unknown: A bless spell
DM: ... nobody needs d4s, so I'll just use these d4s as Milo and Tilly.
DM: They're gonna be in... Milo's gonna be
DM: hiding. Where's, where's Wellby gonna be?
Wellby: Middle.
Delwath: Like on the top of the thing?
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: So Well- Milo's got the arrows now, so I think he's gonna just...
DM: I mean, he does... The more spread out everybody can be, the better off you are.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: So he's gonna hide in the doorway.
Wellby: He should be on whatever side is...
Wellby: No, it doesn't matter. Yeah, cool.
DM: And Tilly is gonna be here.
Kenzo: Don't we have, like, little, little, little fucking dudes miniature ones?
DM: Yeah. If anybody can find little dudes.
Unknown: Where the, where the little...
DM: I mean, I'm gonna have to use dice for the-
Seeker: I'm sure this isn't it but we'll-
DM: ... the 50 million. Some of this is gonna have to be a bit theater of the mind, 'cause we're not gonna actually be able to track every single minion.
Wellby: No, you've, you've got a ton of little minions in there.
Unknown: There's a lot, there's a lot of creatures.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: You've got six fiery dwarves and six something else's.
DM: Okay. Yeah.
DM: Can somebody just throw some, put some of these onto stands?
DM: I don't need a dragon.
Wellby: You don't need a dragon?
DM: Nope.
Kenzo: We had, we found a really good one. We found a, we had a, we had a black, giant black dragon.
DM: Yeah. Where did that go?
Wellby: It's right here.
Kenzo: Uh, this can, this can be, uh, one of the-
Wellby: Here's a... This is not quite a Dimitar, but that could be a Dimitar.
Wellby: It's got wings anyway.
Unknown: This is, uh... What, what are these guys?
Unknown: These two travelers right here? What are these?
DM: I don't know. We don't have any gargantuan beasts.
Delwath: Tilly and-
Wellby: That's, yeah, Milo and Tilly
DM: I need like a base that's like...
Wellby: I have a bunch of little bases, like a bunch of little one slot bases.
Unknown: These, this kind or this kind?
Wellby: Uh, the flat kind.
DM: This is not big enough for us.
Unknown: Yeah. This one doesn't seem to be compatible with the- Yeah, there's two different types.
DM: The, the, the wiggly ones use the one slot base, and the hard plastic ones use the three slot base.
Unknown: These, these. Oh.
DM: Okay. So are you gonna turn on the daylight?
Unknown: Oh, there we go. Or are you gonna use divination, or are you gonna...
Wellby: I don't think we need the divination.
Wellby: Too much can change with the divination answer.
Delwath: I, I think we turn on the daylight as soon as we can,
Delwath: right? Like what are we waiting for? Are we waiting for anything?
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Do it last maybe.
DM: Eric, roll a D20.
Seeker: Ooh, that's an 11.
DM: Okay. Um.
Kenzo: Oh, you have, you have all the Yeah ...
Delwath: sets. Take what you need. Well, I just, I don't know if there's anything good, but keep, keep talking.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: so...
Wellby: I have more little big space space blockers.
Unknown: Where should Seeker be? Mm.
Seeker: We're gonna spread out basically.
Delwath: Yeah, we wanna be as spread out as we can, for sure.
Seeker: Right. Well, I'll start over here.
Seeker: But I think ladder construct team should start up high somewhere.
Delwath: Okay. Yeah, I mean, as soon as we have, um, indication that they're coming, we can start...
Delwath: We need... Like ideally we have like two or three rounds where we can start to position ourselves and cast spells and things.
Delwath: But it's gonna be hard to know exactly how many rounds we have.
DM: Uh, you got it. Yeah, you gotta just turn on the light.
Delwath: Well, no, I mean the point is we're gonna, we're turning on the light as soon as we can.
DM: Okay. You can turn it on now.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what we did. I thought that's why you had Eric roll a D20.
DM: Yeah, it is. But I didn't know if you were ready to do it.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Light shines out,
DM: illuminating the entire temple complex in this brilliant daylight and stretching about 600 feet in every direction.
Wellby: Awesome.
Delwath: Uh. That's kind of... That could be a- Wow, that's pretty solid ...
Delwath: it's not ideal, but do we have a, do we have a Tilly?
Delwath: Wait, what is Tilly, a druid? She's a druid.
Kenzo: Uh, I made... This is a, this is for a, one of the Tilly or, or-
Wellby: That's a Milo
Kenzo: ... Milo.
Delwath: I mean, this is not really great, but if-
Kenzo: What's that one?
Seeker: It's, that could be Tilly. Ladder construct team.
Wellby: Tim, how many chimeras are there?
DM: Uh, Milo said there were four.
DM: That was an hour ago.
Unknown: This is great.
Delwath: So do we see anything within 600 feet?
Unknown: Nope.
Seeker: There's nothing stone golemy is there, or stone constructy?
Seeker: Mm. Give me more stats.
Delwath: What about that?
Seeker: Oh wow, that's awesome.
Unknown: Uh.
Wellby: Can I have bases for these, Mike, for, for this?
Delwath: Uh, is it this size or is it this size?
Wellby: I don't think it matters 'cause I, I think smaller because of the map scale is different.
Seeker: So that's too big to be the stone construct, but it's stone at least.
Delwath: Oh, it's one square. It's fine.
Wellby: Cool. I took three more of that kind of base when you have a chance.
Seeker: Ladder will just be a die, I guess.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: Oh, that's a gray clay golem. Or is that a stone golem?
Seeker: Yeah. We're doing stone this time.
Kenzo: Dude, that's perfect.
Unknown: So...
Wellby: Oops. Actually, Mike, I need the other kind of base.
Unknown: This kind?
Wellby: The squiggle. Yeah.
Wellby: Uh, two more after this.
DM: Okay. So just before the combat starts, um,
DM: Milo and Tilly want a quick ch- you know, chat.
DM: Like what's our plan here?
Unknown: Right.
Wellby: This is a scroll I think.
Delwath: So when you hit dragons hard enough, long enough, they fall dead.
Seeker: [laughs] It takes some persistence, doesn't it?
DM: [laughs] Tell me something I don't know.
Kenzo: Stay away from their breath weapon.
Unknown: Uh...
Delwath: I think-
Kenzo: Try not to be scared.
Unknown: Uh...
Delwath: I mean, do we have a plan? We should probably...
Delwath: We gotta take out the dragon.
Wellby: [laughs] Yes.
Delwath: Yes. Gonna have a swarm of other things.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: This is what I'm wondering, should we
DM: divide and conquer? If we get swarmed by dragonettes, it's not gonna go well.
Delwath: We're hoping
Delwath: that we have,
Delwath: we're hoping that we have, um, some dragonette help,
Delwath: but it's not clear.
Delwath: I think... So Kenzo I think should just, you just punch the dragon.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Kenzo's job is dragon puncher.
Unknown: Right?
Delwath: Like nothing but dragon punching.
Delwath: Try and stun it, whatever.
Delwath: Saltite it and then whatever.
Delwath: But you get five attacks, you're enlarged.
Kenzo: And I'm blessed.
Delwath: And you're blessed.
Delwath: You might want to get his claw.
Unknown: Oh yeah.
Delwath: 'Cause then you'd be D10- So that means you do- ...
DM: plus D6 plus D4 ... 1D6 plus 1D10 plus 1D4 with every attack.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Well, and, and I, and I roll a D24.
Unknown: Or a D20 plus D4.
Delwath: And you roll 1D24.
DM: D20... Yeah. Right.
Kenzo: For every, every attack roll.
Seeker: Yeah. And the ladder will just be there.
Delwath: And I think the ladder should back up Kenzo.
Delwath: Yeah. Delweth is either gonna dragon or if...
Delwath: I think we need multi firepower on the dragon.
Kenzo: I think so too. I, I think maybe me and you on the dragon and everybody else take out everybody else that's around.
DM: I mean, Mavi's pretty good at taking out minions 'cause he can shoot through three of them or four of them at once.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: I think that's what, um, what I and Milo should do.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: 'Cause we both have sneak attacks.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: But-
Delwath: Do a bunch of damage
Unknown: ... but
Delwath: dragons have crap dex saves generally
Wellby: Uh, did we see what its immunities were though?
Delwath: Oh wait, we already told you.
Unknown: We already told them.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Immune to acid and necrotic.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Immune to charm, frightened, para...
DM: But it has, it has true sight, so blind is not gonna affect it whatsoever.
Unknown: Ah.
Wellby: And it's immune to poison?
DM: It's immune to poison, stunned, petrified, paralyzed, frightened, and charmed.
Wellby: I can't do anything to it then.
Seeker: What if you hit it in its sunset scar?
DM: That might piss it off.
Kenzo: Hitting it in its... I think aiming for the sunset scar is the way.
Delwath: I mean, I think we also want to try to...
Unknown: That is totally the way.
Delwath: Wait, dragons have like a fright aura too, don't they?
Unknown: Yep.
Kenzo: And that's why you gotta stay within 30 feet of me.
Seeker: So I have this sunset thread.
Kenzo: That's why you and I gotta stay close and-
Delwath: Yeah, I mean, that's gonna-
Unknown: ... go melee
Delwath: ... a breath weapon. That's gonna make us...
Delwath: But what can we do?
Kenzo: We'll fly around.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Try to dodge it.
Delwath: I mean, we can try and be 30 feet... Ideally, we're 30 feet on either side.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Right? Ideally, we come at it like this.
Delwath: And we're da, da, da, and it's in between us, so it can't hit us both.
DM: So the... Kenzo's thing is e- he's immune to fear, but everybody within 30 feet-
Delwath: 30 feet has advantage
Unknown: ... everyone has advantage.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: And you have cleansing touch if...
DM: If necessary.
Seeker: Tim, the, the sunset thread said it was spun by the Cloud Weaver.
Unknown: Should that be-
DM: That should be the Cloudspinner, yeah.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: I mean, she goes by many names.
Seeker: I wonder if like...
Delwath: That's a blinding one, but extra 2d6 damage
Unknown: ... make that into
DM: Now, the chimeras are probably not immune to any conditions.
Unknown: Right.
Kenzo: Taking those out would be useful. Focus on those.
Wellby: I, that's what I'm thinking too.
Unknown: Yeah. Focus on those.
Unknown: Are you guys?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Yeah, okay. So the, the flying strike team goes at the dragon.
Delwath: Everybody else keeps anything from...
Delwath: Kills everything else.
Unknown: And then what should I-
Kenzo: Focus on the chimeras first 'cause they're gonna be the...
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: What should I be doing from the ground?
Delwath: Do you have any area effect damage spells?
Unknown: Probably not.
Delwath: I mean, that's the one thing I was thinking is Synaptic Static is pretty good at clearing the field with...
Delwath: But it's better... I'm gonna be better off with Frank.
DM: I mean, something like Rune of Psychic Disruption against chimera is not gonna do much to the dragon, but against chimeras it's quite strong.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Right? Like...
Seeker: And that's 120 foot range.
Seeker: I could always... I have a couple of charges for boosting range.
Unknown: And you...
DM: If they fail the save, you take them out for a whole round.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: But, but can you... Are you, uh...
Kenzo: Can... It's 20 feet?
Unknown: It's 120.
Unknown: 120.
Unknown: 120 feet. Then I see-
DM: And you can make it 240 or
DM: optionally-
Seeker: Flavor it
DM: ... fla- no, go for double that to 4...
Delwath: To 500, 480.
Unknown: 480.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: But then you gotta make your check.
DM: You might fail.
Unknown: Right.
Kenzo: All right. That sounds great.
Seeker: It'd be nice to be able to hit one of those chimeras far, far away actually.
Unknown: That's interesting.
Wellby: We should get at least two rounds of arrow attacks on it.
Delwath: Don't... What's your ra- I thought your range was 270.
Wellby: 270.
DM: Depends on how fast they fly.
Delwath: I don't think we'll get two rounds.
Wellby: I think they have a flight speed more than 60.
Unknown: Might be 90.
Seeker: I love that we lit up the ball field.
Seeker: We're like playing night baseball.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: It's great.
Unknown: It's epic.
Wellby: Could be even one round would make a difference.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay, um, I'm almost ready.
DM: I just have to have like 12 tabs open, so give me one sec.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Tim, I have four chimera tokens and 13 minion tokens.
DM: Awesome.
DM: That should be about right.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: let me
Unknown: just use that. [sighs] I wonder if...
Unknown: Absorb Elements.
Delwath: Oh, Absorb Elements.
DM: That could be useful. Tilly also has that.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: So...
Unknown: That's my breath weapon save.
Unknown: Uh, okay. Okay.
Delwath: Man, my reaction is so oversubscribed.
Unknown: Mm.
Kenzo: [laughs] Too many things to re- that you can do?
Delwath: Yeah, 'cause I... Absorb Elements gives me resistance to acid damage.
Unknown: What?
Delwath: Just against the triggering attack.
Delwath: I mean, it's until my n- it's just like I use it as a reaction when I get hit with the breath weapon.
Kenzo: I mean, that's useful.
Delwath: It's super useful.
Kenzo: Wait, hold on, hold on. Let's think for one second here.
Kenzo: Just in terms of rings. You got the acid resist...
Kenzo: Like, I feel like I should have that.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Right?
Unknown: You should take that.
Unknown: You know what I mean?
Delwath: Can, can we swap that?
DM: You can swap that.
Kenzo: Yeah. This in the prep.
Delwath: You have to give up something.
Delwath: What are you giving up? Your...
DM: Oh, but it's tough. He can't-
Unknown: Don't give up the cloak
Delwath: ... he can't take-
Unknown: Oh, no. You can't.
DM: He can't give up the cloak. He can't give up the tattoo, and he can't give up the staff.
Kenzo: No, I can give up the tattoo.
DM: No, don't you want to use the tattoo?
Kenzo: I mean, Langau's, you know...
Kenzo: I mean, honestly, right?
Kenzo: For, for fucking 50% damage on acid.
Wellby: Do you have a slot?
Seeker: There's gonna be some acid.
DM: Honestly, you're almost better off giving up the staff.
DM: I mean, you can still fight with it.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: You just can't use the heal staff.
Kenzo: Oh my God. Totally give up the staff.
Kenzo: That's crazy, but yeah.
Unknown: Oh, you, you just can't talk to me.
Delwath: But you're not even gonna fight with it if you have Langau's Claw.
Unknown: You're just-
Kenzo: No, I'm, I'm, I'm totally-
Unknown: You're going staff, right?
Kenzo: That's unbelievable.
Kenzo: Yeah. I, I'm going giant Kenzo feral throwing fucking massive like jaguar punches.
Unknown: I mean, I could-
Kenzo: Holy shit
Delwath: ... trade out Almarka's thing.
Delwath: But the plus one to its spell DCs is actually pretty useful.
Kenzo: I, I think this is the way.
Delwath: And resistance doesn't stack with resistance, right?
Unknown: Yeah, it doesn't.
Delwath: So I can, I can absorb...
Delwath: There's actually no point in me taking it 'cause I'll just ca- I mean, yeah, it means I could use my reaction.
DM: Yeah, we don't have an item for it, but just remember you're resistant to...
Kenzo: Holy shit. That's so crazy.
Kenzo: 'Cause it's like, yeah, I'm gonna have this ultra magic b- powerful staff I'm not gonna use.
Unknown: Tim.
Seeker: I'm gonna...
Seeker: I, I could reattune the binding stones, but they're still...
Seeker: I'm like looking at it. I'm like,
Seeker: is there anything in that that I could use actually?
Kenzo: Can you, can you do the if we're getting really fucked, just like roll a bunch of dice and then see if you can find the dragon?
DM: The thing is, if you're casting the, if you're casting the construct at sixth level, that's your concentration, right?
Seeker: So-
Seeker: Right. So that's-
DM: Watery Sphere could be useful
Unknown: ... but then the concentration
DM: Like, you could trap a bunch of mini- minions in that or a chimera, but it's concentration.
Delwath: The construct's pretty powerful
DM: I think a sixth level construct-
Delwath: We still have the
DM: ... a sixth level construct makes three attacks, right?
Seeker: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: So
Delwath: I, I would focus on the c- I'd construct and then support spells or psychic disruption thingy.
DM: All right.
Delwath: Right? I mean, do you have any, like, good...
Delwath: I mean, you can always Healing Word us.
Unknown: Like, you know, you have...
Seeker: There's not much else. I can't do Telekinesis, Wall of Stone.
Delwath: Oh, 'cause everything else is concentration.
DM: How many hit points does the construct have?
Unknown: Uh, 70.
DM: Okay.
DM: That's a lot. I mean, that's a-
Delwath: That's the Erupting Earth
DM: ... bunch of tanky stuff
Delwath: Wait, does Erupting Earth pull it to, pull something to the ground?
DM: Well, the problem is it has to be close to the ground to begin with.
Delwath: It has to be close to the ground. What about your Grasping Hand?
Unknown: That doesn't pull stuff to the ground either, does it?
DM: No, we swapped that out for Telekinesis anyway.
Unknown: Okay. Yeah.
DM: And Telekinesis is quite good at that sort of stuff.
Unknown: But it's a construct
Unknown: But it's concentration.
Delwath: It's a construct. I mean, you've got us those catapults too.
Seeker: That's 60 feet, so I feel like this is gonna be a,
Seeker: these are large playing fields.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But you can, remember, you can double it.
Unknown: You can double it.
DM: The nice thing about catapults-
Seeker: But I used the three charges to get the-
DM: Oh, so you only have two doubles
Unknown: ... air attack on the ladder.
DM: So you only have two things you can double.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But catapult, the nice thing about catapult is if it misses the first target, the next thing in the line still has to make the save.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: Right?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay, so
DM: about 15 minutes later,
DM: you see coming into the edge of the light a wave of four chimeras and
DM: 13 dragonets flying behind them in like a formation
DM: flying towards you.
Seeker: That's at 600 feet?
DM: That's at 600 feet.
DM: They're moving 108, uh, 120 feet a round.
Unknown: 'Cause they're dashing and-
DM: 'Cause they're dashing
Unknown: ... yeah, I get it.
DM: 60 feet flying.
Delwath: I mean, we're all at the top of the tower right now, right, I assume?
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Well, I didn't put Delwath on.
DM: No, well, the fly team is, but-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... but Tilly-
Unknown: No, no, no, sorry. When I said-
DM: Tilly summons her dragon
Delwath: When I said I'm gonna drink the potion of flying and cast, um, the radiant spell.
Unknown: Where did the Del- what Delwath do?
Unknown: Well, where's the dragon?
Kenzo: The dragon's not here.
DM: The dragon's not here.
DM: You don't see it yet.
DM: Dragon's coming from the direction
Delwath: But my spell lasts 10 minutes.
Kenzo: Should I eat the potions?
Delwath: You should eat the potions.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: They both last more than an hour.
Kenzo: Yeah. All right, I'll eat the potions.
Kenzo: Holy fuck.
Unknown: This is gonna be bad.
DM: Um, this dragon is also gonna be in, on the fly team, Tilly's dragon spirit.
Kenzo: Oh, this is not a... You're, where the fuck is the dragon then?
DM: Oh, it hasn't shown up yet.
Kenzo: I know, but the b- I thought this was, this was a-
DM: No, no, that's, that's Tilly's dragon.
Delwath: That's our good guy dragon.
DM: What?
Kenzo: There's a bigger dragon? Where's the big dragon?
Unknown: I wanna see the big dragon.
DM: I thought, I thought this was the-
Delwath: So wait, I have fly.
Delwath: Let's just fly for an hour
DM: ... the big dragon.
Delwath: Normal fly spell, but it lasts an hour.
DM: Uh, it's your speed.
Unknown: Oh, not-
DM: Is the only downside
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... but it's not concentration.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah. So it's only f- ooh, 30 foot.
Delwath: That's a, that's rough.
Delwath: I'm gonna have a hard time keeping up with the dragon is the only problem with that.
DM: Do you have any way to boost your speed?
Delwath: Anybody have any way to boost my speed?
Wellby: I'm about to drink a potion of haste [laughs].
Delwath: How much, what does it do for it doubles your speed?
DM: Well, wait, do the boots of speed require attunement?
Wellby: Boots of speed do require attunement.
DM: Do you have an attunement slot you can swap that?
Delwath: I'd have to give up my
Delwath: rod.
DM: Right.
Delwath: I can't really give up my shield or my sword.
DM: Yeah, yeah. That one, yeah.
Delwath: I could give up my rod.
Delwath: It, it's not that useful actual- I mean, it's good, but, like,
Delwath: but I mean, I could just drink the potion of haste.
Unknown: You want it?
Wellby: I think so because it lets me do two sneak attacks a turn.
Unknown: Right.
Wellby: It doubles my damage output.
Delwath: Yeah. I mean, it's-
DM: It increases your damage by 25%
DM: ... 25% and yours by 100%.
DM: And you get high acc.
Delwath: No, no, it's more useful for, 'cause I already get three attacks.
Delwath: A fourth attack isn't...
Delwath: I could, I mean, the problem is with, I didn't realize the fly was not 60 foot.
DM: But is it, I mean, would you prefer 60 foot of concentration?
Unknown: No, not at all.
DM: All right.
Delwath: It's way better. No, no, no, but I think we were just playing for this is what I'm saying.
DM: Yeah, yeah. No, you're right. I'm, I'm happy to let you swap out the, for the boots.
Delwath: And what does it give my movement to?
Wellby: Doubles it.
Unknown: 60.
DM: So it would be a, it would be a 60 foot.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: It would be the same as the fly speed, but no concentration.
Delwath: I just think the dragon's gonna move either 60 or 90.
Delwath: I'm gonna really struggle to keep up with it-
Wellby: Agreed
Unknown: ... without
Delwath: that. I think, I think it's bet- I, honestly, I'm not gonna be casting a lot of spells
Delwath: on it. I mean, I lose the ability to get back a slot with an action, but-
Wellby: So you're gonna take the boots
Unknown: ... but I think I'm gonna take boots.
Kenzo: I've got, I've got 60.
DM: I think the, isn't the whistle double your speed?
Wellby: It is double your speed, yeah.
Unknown: Oh, great, so I got 130.
DM: So you've got 130 foot [laughs] speed.
Kenzo: Well, and also, wait, since I'm enlarged, does that do anything?
DM: That does.
Wellby: That's an interesting
DM: ... your speed.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
DM: The one thing about the whistle is if you take damage, you have to make a save, and you fall if you fail the save.
Unknown: That's fine.
DM: But it doesn't matter if you fall.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But you only have three charges, so if you fall three times, then you're out.
Unknown: That's fine.
Seeker: So the ladder team is only gonna have move 40.
Seeker: Is it just gonna be, is it gonna be able to engage at all?
DM: Ladder team needs to get on the dragon's back.
Delwath: Ladder team's gonna grapple the dragon and get on its back.
Seeker: All right, we just have to get there somehow.
Unknown: All right.
Delwath: I mean, I think it's gonna come at us.
Delwath: It's gonna try and kill us.
Unknown: Fair.
Seeker: Right [laughs].
Seeker: But it has ranged attacks, huh?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: 100 up to
Delwath: But its bigger attacks are its wings, its claws, and its bite, right?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: I mean, Kenzo can also try and grapple it.
DM: Oh, no, Ken- oh, wait. No, you're, you're enlarged Kenzo.
Unknown: Okay, it can't work.
DM: You can only grapple things-
Unknown: No, but even enlarged, it doesn't matter
DM: ... no, it's gargantuan. Yeah
Unknown: ... it's large versus gargantuan.
DM: Can't grapple. Actually, the ladder can't grapple it.
DM: It's too big to grapple.
Delwath: But I was thinking the ladder's not gonna grapple it.
Delwath: The ladder's gonna wrap itself-
Delwath: The ladder can hang on to it
Delwath: ... the wrapple, the ladder wants to wrap itself around the dragon to provide an attack platform for
Delwath: the golem.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Right.
Delwath: Right? So that it can't... The whole idea of the ladder grappling would be that the dragon can't shake the golem.
DM: There's a big difference bet- yeah, so it's not grappling.
DM: It's holding on.
Unknown: Yes, yes. Yes, exactly [laughs].
Kenzo: What size are we right now?
Seeker: Kind of grappling yourself
Delwath: You're large. The rest of us will be-
Kenzo: I will be large.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I haven't drank the potion yet.
Delwath: No, no, no, no. You drank the po- well s-
Kenzo: Well, I, I wanna... Uh, for dramatic effect, I'm gonna drink the potion in a second 'cause I'm gonna double in size.
Unknown: I c-
Unknown: It's gonna be epic
Unknown: I get
Wellby: I have an open attunement slot. Is there anything that would be useful for me to attune to?
Kenzo: You have an open attunement slot?
Unknown: Oh my goodness.
Delwath: Well, 'cause he gave me the boots of speed.
Kenzo: I gave up my 1 for something.
Unknown: You should attune to something. Yeah.
Seeker: If I extend an unlock?
Unknown: No.
Kenzo: Let's see. Cloak of the Manor.
Unknown: I don't know.
Unknown: That's not so useful.
Unknown: Uh, let's see.
Delwath: You could attune to the dagger of blind sense.
Unknown: I don't know how useful that is.
Wellby: Let's look at that. It's only 30 feet.
Unknown: 30 feet. That's not that useful.
Kenzo: Ring of jumping? I have a ring of jumping, a ring of, uh, fire resistance.
Seeker: Imagine jumping from the tower onto the back of the dragon.
DM: The jump lets you jump 30 feet.
DM: That's not terrible.
DM: Fire resistance probably isn't gonna be that useful.
Kenzo: Well, the ring of jumping?
Unknown: Although-
Wellby: I can fly.
Unknown: Yeah, you can fly
DM: ... chimeras might have fire breath.
Unknown: I'd say get a ring of fire protection.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: All right. Fire resistance boom.
Unknown: Yours.
Kenzo: You have one too, right?
DM: You're, he's fire and acid.
Unknown: What? I thought I had-
Unknown: No, I mean you're fire and-
Kenzo: I'm, I'm acid. No, I just-
Unknown: And fire.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: You can attune to both.
Unknown: You attune to both.
DM: Attune to both.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: Or you can pick, um-
Unknown: Cold
DM: ... cold. But fire is probably more useful.
Unknown: That's... Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: I got fire and acid.
Kenzo: You got fire.
Unknown: Guys, we're ready.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: We're gonna, we're gonna do great.
Kenzo: Kenzo, uh, like-
Delwath: You should hand out a hero- a bardic inspiration.
DM: Mm.
DM: Yeah, 'cause you might be out of range.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: 'Cause you're probably gonna be out of range.
Seeker: Out of range. So we'll give them to...
Delwath: You... I would just... I mean, you may as well j- I would give out one to everybody.
Unknown: I have, I have five.
Delwath: I mean, you could just hand out all five.
Delwath: It's just who to give them to.
Kenzo: But if you do them at, as reactions, does it have to be within your range?
Delwath: He is, has to be within, what? 60 feet.
DM: Every-
Unknown: 60
DM: ... he always has to be within 60 feet.
Kenzo: Can you give more than one to one person?
Unknown: No.
Kenzo: Ah. Oh, then just do fucking three, one to each of us, and then one to maybe the two halflings?
Kenzo: Or one to the-
Delwath: Or one to the wa- the ladder bardic inspiration.
Delwath: Or the golem.
Kenzo: Yeah, that would be very useful actually.
Unknown: Um.
DM: Yeah, you can give it one. They're creatures.
Delwath: You can give them inspiration.
Kenzo: Yeah. I think that feels right 'cause-
Seeker: Try the...
Delwath: I mean, you could give one to Tilly, who's more likely to use it 'cause they're dragon.
Unknown: Well, or-
DM: I mean, m- probab- like, just tactically, Milo is a one hit.
Delwath: Oh yeah, give one to Milo.
DM: Right. So having the ability to-
Delwath: Milo, either the golem or the ladder.
DM: Although actually, no
DM: ... and then the peach
DM: ... Milo says he doesn't need it.
Unknown: He's gonna have steady-
DM: He's pretty lucky by himself
Unknown: ... uh, hands.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: So I'll give one to the
Seeker: stone construct.
DM: But I mean, Tilly would take it.
Unknown: Yeah, give one to Tilly.
Delwath: And give one to Tilly.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: That's all, all of them.
Kenzo: Kenzo, uh, like knocks back this like really gross looking potion and drinks it, and as he's like drinking it, like starts getting bigger and bigger and bigger.
Kenzo: And now he's like 12 feet tall
Kenzo: and double in size.
Delwath: Delweth also starts to glow.
Kenzo: And, and staring down at you all.
Delwath: As, as the... As soon as the chimeras are like...
Unknown: Right
Delwath: ... as soon as we see the chimeras in the distance, Delweth-
DM: Okay. So let's, let's just...
DM: So you know how many shots you can take off of them, can we just go into initiative right now?
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: While you do your actions.
Unknown: We're just describing.
Delwath: I mean, we could roll initiative, and then these can be our first turn.
DM: Yeah, exactly.
Seeker: 17.
Unknown: 20.
Unknown: 21.
Wellby: 26.
Unknown: Nice.
DM: Okay. 20 Delweth.
DM: What was... 26.
Unknown: 26.
Wellby: You want me to roll for Milo or Tilly?
DM: Uh, yeah. Give me-
Kenzo: Oh, wait, no. I get to roll extra D4s to both of these.
Delwath: You do. Not to both.
DM: No, no. Just to one.
Unknown: Just the one?
Delwath: But blessed applies to all D20 checks, right?
Kenzo: All D20, yes. Yes.
Delwath: Yeah, it's only attack rolls?
DM: It's just attack rolls.
Unknown: Oh, attack rolls.
Kenzo: No, no. It's anything with a D20.
Delwath: No, no, no, no, no. What does blessed do?
Unknown: I forget.
Kenzo: It's attack rolls at saving-
Unknown: Oh, attack rolls or saving throws
Unknown: ... and saves.
Delwath: That is not initiative.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Milo. Roll a D20 for Milo.
DM: He's plus eight.
Wellby: Uh, I rolled a four. That's 12 total.
DM: Okay, 12 for Milo.
DM: Uh, Tilly's only plus four.
Unknown: 10.
DM: I rolled a one.
Unknown: I rolled-
DM: For Tilly. Oh.
Delwath: I, I was rolling for Tilly.
DM: Well, the one rerolls to a two.
Unknown: So 14 total or 6 total?
DM: That's great. You got it.
Unknown: 14 or 10?
Delwath: 14.
DM: Okay. 14 for Tilly.
DM: Sorry, what was Seeker? 17?
Seeker: 17.
DM: And what was Kenzo?
Unknown: 21.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Okay, so let me just get all the...
DM: Let me just get everybody on here so I have everything.
DM: Mike, do you wanna run-
Delwath: It's so complicated
DM: ... Tilly and I'll run Milo?
Delwath: Yeah, I'll run Tilly. Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: You run the construct.
DM: Yeah. So, so Milo...
DM: Here, let me... I can se- I actually have characters
Wellby: There's twice, twice as much of you to run.
Unknown: [laughs] Right.
Wellby: Or, or actually eight times as much of you to run, right?
DM: The, uh... Can you ac- I just texted you.
Unknown: That's Milo.
Seeker: Even though we're all running extra characters, Kenzo still has more attacks than anyone.
DM: [laughs] Yes.
Seeker: Although actually I'm gonna have-
Unknown: I can't... I-
DM: You know
Delwath: ... I, I... My computer's not on my-
Unknown: Five total.
Unknown: Yeah, I have five.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: It's-
DM: I don't know if I can-
Seeker: Just 'cause of the con- construct has three. It's great
DM: ... can I email it to you?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Um.
Delwath: Or I can just look at... Oh, I don't have access to this page.
DM: Oh. Uh.
DM: I don't know how to do that.
Delwath: Just on the My Characters, you can change...
Delwath: Click the Edit.
DM: Char- oh, character settings?
Unknown: D6, D4.
Delwath: Yeah, if you click Edit, and then there should be a privacy somewhere.
Kenzo: D6, D4, D10 plus 5.
Unknown: Wow.
Delwath: Um, if you scroll all the way down to Character Privacy at the bottom.
DM: Oh, yeah. Okay.
Unknown: And you can change it to public.
DM: Oh, I had it campaign only, but I didn't change it.
Delwath: They're not in the campaign.
DM: Yeah. Oh, I... Let me just put it on the campaign.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: It'll make it so much easier.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Oh, and I get 10, 10 extra hit points too.
Unknown: That's nice.
Delwath: Yeah, you have 10, 10 hit points.
Unknown: Cool.
Delwath: Oh, and you got eight. You got eight from Tilly, right?
DM: Yep, I got my 15.
Unknown: Okay.
Kenzo: Wow. [sighs] Okay.
Unknown: That's exciting.
Delwath: All right. So Eric's running three characters.
Seeker: Yeah, that's fine.
Delwath: I'm running two. Schwartz is running two.
Unknown: You're just running Kenzo.
Kenzo: Time attack. Double attack.
Unknown: You still have more attacks than anybody else.
Unknown: Imagine if we had a Delweth prime.
Unknown: I know. That would've been good.
Unknown: Another time.
Unknown: Another time
DM: Okay. I think I just successfully-
Delwath: I mean, you put it in the campaign-
DM: Oh
Unknown: ... I should just be able to
Seeker: Somebody's gotta do Dimitar also.
Delwath: Uh, Tim will run Dimitar too.
DM: I'm running Dimitar, yeah.
DM: Are they... Did I get them in the campaign successfully?
Unknown: Yes.
DM: Okay. So Milo only has his, um, has his rapier, but it's gonna be the same.
Delwath: Wait, did Tilly cast Aid?
DM: T- Tilly cast Aid.
Delwath: On herself as well as-
DM: Yeah. It's, it's on there already. It should be.
Unknown: Oh, wow. Okay.
DM: Um-
Unknown: Oh, I...
Unknown: Huh,
Unknown: can I actually tick things off?
DM: Here, here. Hold on. They're now...
DM: I'm, I'm unassigning them.
Delwath: I can't, I can't, I can't.
DM: Yeah, you can. Go, go claim the character.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I have to go into my campaigns.
DM: Schwartz, I unassigned Milo so you can claim Milo.
Wellby: Do I need to claim Milo? I can just open Milo.
Delwath: Yeah. But you can't-
DM: You can't tick off hit points
Delwath: ... you can't tick off hit points or anything-
Wellby: Ooh
Delwath: ... unless you claim.
Wellby: Uh, okay. Okay.
DM: Do you have enough slots to claim him?
Wellby: Uh.
DM: It's okay if you don't. I can tick off hit points.
DM: You just run him and I'll keep track of his damage.
Wellby: Yeah. Good. Good, good.
Unknown: Yeah. Okay.
DM: But you got Tilly.
Unknown: And I'm set.
DM: Okay. Tilly's more important 'cause Tilly has to kee- you might have to keep track of spell slots.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um-
Delwath: Wait, what is the draconic thing?
DM: It's the Summon Draconic Spirit.
Unknown: Fifth level?
DM: Yeah. I, it's fifth level.
Delwath: Ah, okay.
DM: It just... It's like a stat block like Eric's stuff.
Unknown: Yeah, okay.
DM: But it's just the default. Is it fifth level?
Seeker: I recommend if you wanna look at that draconic spirit thing, just open it in a new tab.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Seeker: Because it's so annoying to, like, go to a tab-
DM: Okay. Sorry. I was trying to get, um-
Seeker: ... then see it on D&D Beyond, scroll down to the thing, open the thing-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
Seeker: ... and then scroll down to the other thing-
Unknown: How do you open a new tab?
Seeker: ... to find out anything. Oh, you'll just have to find another version of that somewhere.
Delwath: Oh, I just have to open the spell in another tab.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I see.
DM: Um-
Seeker: And presume it's gonna be the same information.
DM: Okay. So that's-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
DM: ... that's 21 for dragonets.
Delwath: Okay. And I need...
Unknown: And I'm just gonna use notepad for...
DM: Okay. Do you wanna swap anything around
DM: for initiative?
Kenzo: Ooh, good question. Um...
Delwath: Oh, can cast a wrath weapon.
Kenzo: Yeah. 'Cause right now it's, uh...
Kenzo: I mean, I think this is good, right?
Kenzo: 'Cause we want you first. You know me second is still good.
Delwath: Wait, which kind of dragon is it-
DM: Uh
Unknown: ... that she summoned?
Delwath: Chromatic or gem?
DM: I don't know. I didn't read the spell.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Heck.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: I want the one that's resistant to acid.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Okay. It can be resistant to acid, but deal cold...
Delwath: This thing's not d- The black dragon is not cold, right?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: You can do resistant to acid and cold.
Delwath: So it's a, it's a chromatic.
DM: Okay.
DM: Cool. Um,
DM: uh, okay. Did I... I got dragon one, two, three.
Kenzo: Wow. This is, this is the craziest battle we've ever had.
DM: Oh, I didn't roll initiative for Dimitar.
DM: Dimitar-
Delwath: Oh, Tilly has resistance to acid too.
Unknown: That's nice.
DM: With those bard elements.
Unknown: Not-
DM: Oh, from her sea prim.
Unknown: From-
Delwath: Yeah, yeah.
Delwath: No, from Draconic Spirit.
DM: Oh, okay.
Unknown: When you cast-
DM: But she also has a s- the sea animation, which lets her, gives her a fly speed, but is she...
DM: It's-
Unknown: Oh my God
DM: ... you go to... Here, I'll send it.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: She's very complicated.
Wellby: [laughs]
Wellby: Now I know.
Seeker: To get through the first round.
DM: No, no, no. Once it starts, it's gonna be fast.
Seeker: 'Cause we're all gonna be immediately plastered with acid, you know?
DM: Oh, I don't know.
Unknown: I don't think so.
DM: The effects of this don't really matter.
DM: She just has a fly speed.
Delwath: Ah, okay. But, but the draconic spirit lets you gain the-
DM: The resistance
Delwath: ... resistance of one of its types.
DM: Yeah.
DM: Yeah. She has a 60 foot fly speed.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, okay. I've got everybody.
DM: Okay. So you see Wellby is the first one who spots, um, the dragons coming in.
DM: I mean, the chimeras and the dragonets coming in, currently 600 feet away.
DM: I don't think you can hit them at that range.
Wellby: No.
DM: Okay. Um, Kenzo drinks his potion.
Kenzo: I drink both my potion potions.
DM: You can only do one a turn.
Delwath: Oh, okay. No. Can you, uh, can you bonus action one and regular action one?
DM: Well, you can only drink one potion a turn.
Unknown: Ah, okay.
DM: I don't care whether you do it-
Unknown: Whatever
Kenzo: ... bonus or regular.
Kenzo: Fine. Enlarge. Yep.
DM: Kenzo enlarges. Delwath casts his first spell.
Delwath: Yeah. And drinks the fly potion.
DM: Okay.
DM: Seeker casts...
Seeker: Well, at this range...
DM: It's 600 feet. You probably can't do anything.
Unknown: No.
DM: Um, Tilly-
Delwath: Wait. Huh.
Unknown: I actually can do something, but I don't know if I want to.
DM: Um,
DM: Tilly and Milo aren't gonna do anything but send the flying, spread the flyers out in a row to meet...
DM: I mean, you guys can all move to get the first move.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um,
DM: they move 120 feet closer, so they're now 480 feet away.
DM: Um, still just waiting, aeronaut ready to shoot.
DM: Anybody else doing anything while they're 480 feet away?
Delwath: So hold on. Uh-
Wellby: Waiting to 90.
Delwath: W- I'm, we're flying.
Delwath: So I think Kenza, you and I should probably fly away, like, so that we're not...
Delwath: I dunno, we wanna stay 30 feet away.
Delwath: We should s- we should parallel track 30 feet.
Unknown: Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah, we are always parallel tracking.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Right.
Kenzo: Can chimeras... Well, I guess we'll learn about chimeras in a second, but-
Wellby: Uh, I wanna move to a position where I can hit them at the absolute edge of my range in the next round.
Wellby: So-
Delwath: Are there any... There's no ally dragonets showing up, are there?
DM: Nope.
Unknown: Okay. So-
Wellby: How many feet away are they right now?
DM: Right now they're 480.
Unknown: So-
Wellby: They're gonna move 120 closer?
DM: Yep.
Wellby: 360.
DM: So they'll be 360.
Wellby: So I'll move
Wellby: 90 feet towards them.
DM: Okay. Wait, you got...
DM: Oh, right. 'Cause bonus action dash, right?
Seeker: So at this range I could hit with a rune of psychic disruption if I use both charges.
Delwath: I wouldn't use both your charges.
Seeker: I was just thinking about it. Am I gonna really do it twice though at 240?
DM: You're- Remember these are only 10 feet so it's only...
DM: So 120 is only 12 squares.
DM: It's entirely possible that there could be quite a lot of the battle happening more than 120 feet from you.
Seeker: All right. All right. So-
DM: Yeah. But it's up to you. Totally up to you.
Delwath: I would... You're b- you're much better off doing two, using it twice with two charges to get two-
Unknown: All right
Unknown: ... two spells.
Unknown: All right. That's-
DM: So wait, how many squares is it from the center there to
DM: the edge?
Unknown: One, two, three, four, five, six.
Unknown: 12.
DM: So that's 120. So they're now 240 feet off the edge.
DM: So like right here.
Delwath: Wait, 'cause are we flying? Are we gonna...
Delwath: Are we waiting or flying towards them?
Kenzo: Great question. Um-
Delwath: I mean, we're probably better waiting, right?
Kenzo: I, I think so.
Delwath: 'Cause over, all of our-
Kenzo: All the air, all the-
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... the support air power is over-
Delwath: We wanna stay around the top.
Unknown: We do. We do.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: We wanna, we wanna stay so they can k- they get shot at with missiles.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: I mean, they're coming to us right now.
DM: Do you have a-
Unknown: This is-
DM: Um,
DM: they, so this-
Wellby: No, no, no. Never mind, I got it.
DM: Yeah, we'll stay here.
Kenzo: Yeah, we totally wanna stay here. We, we wanna keep them all within range of like fire- fireballs, like all of our rifle weapons.
DM: Yeah, so the start of the third round, they're 240 feet away.
DM: They've moved to... Oh, no.
DM: The start of the-
Unknown: Second round
DM: ... well, the only one that really matters is when the round that they start 240 feet away-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... right? 'Cause that's Welby's range.
DM: Right.
DM: So we'll just skip to the round where they start 240 feet away.
Delwath: Yeah. It only matters with the number of prep-
DM: With the number of preps that you got
Kenzo: ... mm-hmm. And I've drank two potions.
DM: You've drunk both your potions.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So they're 240 feet here.
Unknown: All right.
DM: Four chimeras, 13 dragonets in a row.
Unknown: Hold.
DM: Hold.
Unknown: Every- There's like, [whooshing].
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: You can see the dragon heads starting to sort of puff up-
Unknown: Hold on. I gotta look at Tilly's-
DM: ... into chimeras.
Wellby: So I'm gonna bonus action-
Delwath: So she only has a fourth-
Unknown: ... drink a potion of haste
Unknown: ... check dot too?
DM: She cast aid at fourth level.
Unknown: Ah, okay. Aid.
Seeker: And they're, the chimeras are-
Delwath: Does haste only last a minute?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Lion-
Seeker: Okay. So you don't have to
Seeker: ... goat and dragon.
DM: Okay. So-
Wellby: Okay. So bonus action, drink potion of haste.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: And she gets aid so that's good.
Wellby: Take steady aim and shoot one.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: And then when it's turn, I'm gonna make my next-
Unknown: Do we have chimeras?
Wellby: ... action contingent on-
DM: Uh, yeah. Where were the chimeras?
Unknown: Oh, here are four. They're not-
DM: I mean, four creatures
Wellby: ... well, they're different creatures, so.
DM: Yeah. So they're-
Kenzo: And Kenzo and, uh-
DM: They're here
Unknown: ... who's all the
Wellby: And the-
Seeker: Those are kind of hard to blind, but they each have 50 hide.
DM: Uh, yeah. They might be difficult to blind 'cause they have three heads.
Wellby: I'm just gonna dump damage on these guys instead.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: The dragonets are like a little bit behind.
DM: The chimeras are like in a,
DM: uh, in a row.
Wellby: So for that second action, Tim, like to say my-
Kenzo: This is Welby. All right. This is, uh-
Wellby: ... I'm gonna shoot the same creature when it comes turn-
Wellby: ... this is Delweth
Wellby: ... is that the way that works? So like-
DM: No, it's you'd say like when it moves 10 feet closer to me.
Wellby: Awesome. Yeah.
DM: Or something like that.
Wellby: Cool, cool, cool.
DM: Which will be on its turn, right?
Wellby: Awesome. All right.
DM: So you're aiming for, let's say, this chimera here.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: They're 240 feet away now.
DM: Welby's turn, this is the beginning of-
Wellby: Well, 270 from me, 240 from the edge of the map.
DM: Right. It's the beginning of this round.
Delwath: There's a, Delweth and Tilly both have 300 foot spells, so don't skip us in the initiative.
DM: I'm not going to.
Seeker: Oh, 300.
Wellby: That is, uh, 23.
DM: So this is, this is round four, but you drank the haste potion the last round, right?
Wellby: No, I drank it in round four.
DM: In round four. Okay.
Delwath: As a bonus action.
DM: So round 14 it ends.
DM: I don't think we'll get to round 14.
Delwath: Wait, they're, they're-
DM: I'm gonna keep hit points for all these
Delwath: ... they're 240 feet from the edge?
Unknown: They're 240 feet from the edge of the map.
Delwath: Okay. So 270, 10, 20, 30.
Delwath: Okay, so you'd have to be here
Delwath: to ice storm. Tilly's still way too far away.
DM: I mean, she can move closer in the previous rounds.
Delwath: Actually, she's gonna move over to this.
Delwath: Can she move over, she could be on this roof?
DM: Yeah. She can fly.
DM: She has a 60 foot fly speed.
Unknown: Ah, okay.
DM: One, two. This is all on one, both hits on one chimera.
Wellby: Yep. So the first is 41.
DM: Its AC is 15, by the way.
Wellby: Awesome. So the first is 41 damage.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: Is it bloodied?
DM: Uh, nope.
Wellby: All right. The second with advantage because of haste.
Unknown: Yes.
Seeker: We're gonna need to scatter.
DM: Are we?
Wellby: Actually, tell me when it's time to shoot the second one.
Unknown: Or it would help to get the golem onto the dragon-
DM: Uh, yep, I will
Seeker: ... which would half its speed.
Wellby: Oh.
Kenzo: Once, once the dragon shows up.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah. Once the dragon shows up.
Delwath: The golem just has to stay. So Kenzo-
Unknown: That's awesome. That's awesome
Delwath: ... Kenzo, Delweth, and the golem have to stick within 30 feet of each other.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Delwath: 'Cause then I can scatter.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Delwath: I can scatter, I mean, I could scatter me and the golem to be right next...
Unknown: And Kenzo.
Unknown: Yes.
Seeker: We all clap today. We could put the golem in the dragon's face.
Delwath: To be right in the dragon's face.
DM: So, s- uh, sorry.
DM: So Welby went.
Unknown: Like well positioned right now.
DM: Sorry, how much damage did you do?
DM: The first arrow of the battle was 41, I think you said.
Wellby: Yes. Yeah.
DM: 41 damage at this chimera here.
Unknown: First blood.
DM: First blood. The arrow strikes and it seems totally somewhat unbothered as they keep just beating their wings, flying in rage towards you.
DM: Uh, after Welby is Kenzo.
DM: You're just waiting till they're cl- till they're 90.
Kenzo: I'm waiting till they're 90 to soul seven, yeah.
DM: Okay. Um, dragonets are flying with them.
DM: Delweth is up.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I'm gonna save my spell slots.
DM: Okay. Seeker Tilly's up.
Delwath: Tilly is gonna fly 30 feet this way and cast ice storm.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Uh, at fourth, is it a f-
DM: It's a fourth level.
Unknown: It's a fourth level.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Is it this round?
Wellby: They are presently 270 feet, uh, excuse me, 240 feet-
DM: 40 feet from the edge
Wellby: ... from the edge of the map.
Delwath: It's a, ice storm is a 20 foot
Delwath: cylinder.
Delwath: 20 foot radius, 40 foot high cylinder.
DM: That's gonna get two of them.
Delwath: So I might just try and wipe dr- can I get one and a bunch of dragonets?
Unknown: Can I do that?
DM: The dragonets are flying in a line like 10 feet behind, sort of in two li- this is like a formation, right?
Unknown: Ah, okay.
DM: Everybody's spaced like 10 feet from each other.
DM: The dragonets are like this.
Delwath: Um,
Delwath: I'm gonna go-
DM: So-
Delwath: I'll hit, I'll hit-
DM: So you can hit two chimeras or you can hit five dragonets
DM: Or you can hit...
DM: You can hit two chimeras and two dragonets, or you could hit, like, five dragonets.
Delwath: Actually, it doesn't do that much damage.
Delwath: Five dragonets might be better, 'cause it'll probably be more likely to wipe them out.
DM: The dragonets are minions.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: So if they fail the save, they die.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: If they succeed the save, you have to do more than their hit points worth of damage.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Delwath: Um, chimeras for now.
DM: Okay. What's the save?
Delwath: DC 17 dex.
Delwath: And being the one he hurt, plus-
Kenzo: But how are we gonna kill the dragonets then?
Unknown: Next turn.
DM: They both fail.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: All right. Nice.
DM: So rain of ice pours down.
Delwath: Actually, it's not bad damage, 'cause it's four...
Delwath: I didn't see the 4d6.
Delwath: Where's all the d6 at?
Wellby: Wellby needs all of these.
Delwath: Uh, 7,
Delwath: 17, 22, 21 damage.
DM: Okay.
DM: The ice rains down on
DM: the,
DM: um...
DM: Uh,
DM: she also has resistance to cold, thunder, and lightning.
DM: I don't think that'll come up.
DM: Um,
DM: okay. So they'll-
Unknown: And then she's gonna retreat back to the roof
DM: ... so the ice rains down on...
DM: How, how much damage did you say? Sorry.
Delwath: 20, 21.
DM: Okay.
DM: Rains down on these two chimeras.
DM: This, just we're gonna remember, one, two, three, four is the chimeras.
DM: Um,
DM: as
DM: now they move
DM: 120 feet closer, but Wellby gets a shot.
Wellby: 27 or 28.
DM: Yeah, 15 AC on the chimeras.
Delwath: Oh, that was your second-
DM: That's his readied action
Unknown: ...
Delwath: which is what? Via your haste?
Wellby: Yep.
Wellby: 31, 37.
DM: 37. The first chimera is bloodied.
Delwath: Then why can't you just take two shots at them?
DM: Because then he doesn't get sneak attack.
DM: It's only once per... You can only get sneak attack once per turn.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: What about Milo?
Wellby: Oh, and Milo gets a shot.
Delwath: Yeah, why can't he-
DM: 270. He can get a shot too.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Cool.
Wellby: Uh, Milo takes steady aim
Wellby: and, uh-
DM: Reroll the 1..
Wellby: Plus 10 is 17.
DM: 17'll hit a chimera.
Kenzo: Nice. AC 15.
Wellby: No, I'm sorry. Plus ni- nine, but it still hits.
Wellby: Uh, so his sneak attack is 5d6 plus 6 is 66.
Kenzo: Yeah, they're nasty.
Wellby: Plus-
Delwath: We haven't... Yeah, we've barely done anything
Wellby: ... five.
Kenzo: I mean, it's just like [dice clattering] just, just Wellby.
Wellby: Okay. It was not great. I'm not yet the druid.
DM: I know.
Wellby: There's 10-
Unknown: Druid
Wellby: ... 16, 17-
Delwath: Tilly got some weather damage out
Unknown: ... plus five is 22.
Kenzo: I totally did not realize that Milo-
Wellby: 22
Unknown: ... until we were, like, 10th level-
DM: I know
Kenzo: ... and we're like, awesome and-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... what are we do-
DM: Um-
Kenzo: Like, why the fuck have they not been with us this whole time?
Unknown: Like
DM: ... they have their own agenda.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But killing a dragon, I mean...
Unknown: Yeah, this is pretty sweet.
DM: Um, okay. Um,
DM: let's see. What's... What is...
DM: Okay, so that, that was...
DM: That would've been the end of the last round then, 'cause Milo was the last in initiative.
Kenzo: Okay. Now we're round, round five.
DM: So now we're round, beginning round-
Unknown: Five
DM: ... five.
DM: They're now 120 feet away from the edge.
Kenzo: Come on. I'm gonna fly closer to the soul site.
Delwath: Yeah. Should we, should we move in?
Delwath: I mean, I'm just-
Kenzo: I'm... I, I, I wanna stay...
Kenzo: I'm, I'm not gonna-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... engage yet, but I'm just gonna get close enough to soul site.
Wellby: All right. I'm gonna make my... I'm up first?
DM: Uh, yep, you're up first.
Wellby: Same chimera.
Wellby: [dice clattering] Uh, that hits.
Unknown: That hits.
Wellby: [dice clattering] And that is a bunch of numbers.
DM: Wellby's arrow kills the first chimera.
Unknown: Come on. [imitates arrow whooshing]
Wellby: Cool.
Unknown: Where's the dragon?
Delwath: Yeah, I know. Exactly.
DM: That, and that's Kenza's out.
Kenzo: All right. So now they're 120 feet-
DM: 120 feet, yeah.
Kenzo: Ah, man, I mean, I could f- I could fucking just go engage, engage them.
Kenzo: I mean, uh, for a first... Let me... I'm gonna move, um, 30 feet just to get...
Kenzo: What, was one, each one of these squares is how much?
DM: 10.
Kenzo: Okay. I'm gonna move, um, close enough now that I'm in range to soul sight, um-
DM: One of the chimeras
Kenzo: ... one of the chimera. Yeah. Just moving-
DM: Um, they are CR 6. They're immune to frightened.
Unknown: That's it?
DM: They're-
Unknown: Their weakest save?
DM: Weakest is intelligence, strongest is strength.
Seeker: It's good that their weakest is intelligence.
Unknown: Yep.
Unknown: Sweet.
Kenzo: Oh, you know what? Actually,
Kenzo: um, funny enough, um, I've got a 90-foot acid arrow.
Unknown: I'll shoot that.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Ow.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: So what is this? This is D20 plus 5?
Unknown: I think so.
DM: Uh, yep.
Kenzo: Oh, wait. All right.
Unknown: Plus.
Kenzo: So now... Yeah, okay. Okay, now it's gonna get interesting.
Kenzo: So now, uh, do I have, uh, advantage from anything?
DM: No.
Wellby: No, 'cause the one you would've is dead, so nothing.
Kenzo: Okay. All right. So then, um,
Kenzo: I roll these two for my attack roll
Kenzo: plus 5. Uh, 7...
Kenzo: Oh, wait. Oh, fuck, with acid arrow.
Kenzo: Yeah, shit. That's annoying.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: That's not a great-
Kenzo: 12. That misses.
DM: That misses.
Unknown: All right. Then I retreat back.
DM: Yeah. Acid arrow is not, like, your best move.
Unknown: Yeah, that's fine.
Delwath: But we're just... Wait, we don't wanna, we don't wanna, like-
Unknown: Yeah, we're not, we're not
Unknown: ... over-
Unknown: ... engaged yet. This is-
DM: Okay. Delwath?
Delwath: All right. Delwath is gonna fly...
Delwath: Wait, they're... This is 120?
DM: Those are... They're all... Just treat them all like 120 from here
Delwath: From the edge or from-
DM: From the edge
Unknown: ... the edge?
DM: Yeah, yeah. They'll close onto the map next round.
Delwath: Oh, they're 120 from the edge. Oh.
Unknown: They're 120 from the edge?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Oh, so how did you shoot the-
Kenzo: I have 160 move. I, like, went closer-
Unknown: Ah
Unknown: ... to them.
Unknown: So you went 80.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: You went... I see.
Unknown: 120 from the edge.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: I can't really get them. I don't think I want to spend a spell slot.
Unknown: Um-
DM: What is... Is Seeker just...
DM: Seeker is hiding right now in...
DM: So, so Seeker's in the doorway?
Seeker: Yeah. I'm gonna have to run up if I want to do that.
Delwath: 'Cause my best is 120.
Delwath: So when they hit the edge...
Delwath: Wait, can I ready an action?
Delwath: I'm gonna ready an action.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: They've been... I'm gonna ready an action to Eldritch Blast as soon as they're within 120 feet.
DM: Okay.
DM: So that's Delwath. Seeker?
Seeker: Within 120 feet of where you're standing?
Delwath: Yeah. I mean, I'm gonna fly.
Delwath: I'm gonna be like... What, is that Kenza?
Unknown: Where's Kenza?
Kenzo: That's Kenza, right, right here.
Unknown: Right there.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So 10, 20, thir- I'm gonna be like there.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: And so when they're 120 feet of me,
Delwath: Eldritch Blast. That, like any c- the first chimera that comes within 120 feet-
DM: Okay
Delwath: ... I'm just gonna do all my Eldritch Blasts on.
Seeker: So I, if I move up to where you are and use my range doubling, I could hit one of the chimeras with a Rune of Psychic Destruction.
DM: You could.
Seeker: So I'm gonna do that.
Delwath: So don't then... Well, the dragon's not here yet, but it could appear.
Delwath: Like I'm nervous about us bunching the battle.
Unknown: Well, how m- actually, how much, uh-
Delwath: That's... Do you have 30 regular move?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: You can only move three squares.
Seeker: Oh, I may not be able to do this then.
Kenzo: So I can go there- Do you want to start it closer or...?
Unknown: Well-
Unknown: 16
Delwath: ... it's 16.
Kenzo: 'Cause you could have been moving this whole time, too, all these rounds.
Unknown: One, two, three, four, five-
Unknown: True
Seeker: ... six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12.
Unknown: That's true.
Delwath: It's 12... From there you're good.
Delwath: From there it's up, it's 12 to here and 100-
Kenzo: From, from here?
Delwath: Yeah. It's 12 to the edge and 12 to the edge.
Seeker: So that's, that's right at my range.
Seeker: Okay. So I cast, um,
Seeker: a double distance Rune of Psychic Destruction at-
DM: Okay
Unknown: ... at the fifth level.
DM: Chimera two, the one that's wounded?
Seeker: Yeah, chimera two.
Seeker: Uh, so it makes a,
Seeker: uh, INT 18 save.
DM: Oh, they're terrible at INT.
DM: That's a five.
DM: [dice rolling]
Seeker: So that's 7d6 psychic damage and incapacitated-
DM: Okay
Seeker: ... at the start of my next turn.
Delwath: Oh, so does it fall?
Unknown: 7d6, if you want. It falls.
DM: If it's incapacitated, it falls.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Nice.
DM: It lands on the ground. They're flying about 50 feet up, so roll an extra 5d6 for fall damage.
Seeker: Oh, okay. So that's, um-
Delwath: 15, 22
Seeker: ... 22 plus an extra five you said?
Unknown: Yep.
DM: Yep.
DM: [dice rolling]
Unknown: That's, um-
Unknown: 60, 18.
Unknown: 18.
Unknown: 8, 40.
DM: 22 and 18?
Unknown: 40.
DM: Okay. That one's almost gone.
DM: The first one is dead.
Unknown: Smashed to the ground. All right.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Who's next?
DM: Um, after Seeker is Tilly.
Delwath: Tilly is going to...
Delwath: Tilly's job... Wait, we said Till- I mean, Tilly's like, yeah, I'm gonna burn slots.
Unknown: Tilly's gonna burn slots.
DM: Tilly can burn slots, for sure.
Delwath: Yeah. Oh wait, that's Delwath though.
Unknown: Tilly can't use Delwath's slots.
Delwath: Tilly is going to-
Unknown: The construct is-
Unknown: There's-
Seeker: ... getting excited stonily
Delwath: ... uh, I don't...
Delwath: There's nothing with-
Unknown: I should-
Delwath: ... wait, 120.
Unknown: Should they just like-
Delwath: Sorry, I don't know how characters-
Unknown: ... hit her?
Unknown: ... keep that well.
DM: That's fine. Just go for it.
Unknown: I think another ice storm.
DM: Just use another ice storm.
Delwath: Yeah, I think another ice storm on this one.
DM: Just like knockout, ma- or hit the two-
Delwath: Yeah, yeah. Ice storm on those two chimeras.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Yeah. [dice rolling]
DM: Uh, fail. [dice rolling] Fail.
Delwath: 17. So that's-
DM: So that's chimeras three and four.
Delwath: Uh, 4d6 and 2d10.
Delwath: [dice rolling] Ah, crap damage though.
Delwath: 5, 10, 14 damage.
DM: Eh.
Unknown: It's awful.
DM: It's not nothing.
DM: Um, that ends Tilly's turn, so they're all moving now.
DM: You have a readied?
Wellby: Yep. I have a shot on the guy who fell to the ground.
DM: Okay. [dice rolling]
Wellby: That is 16.
Wellby: 16.
DM: Um, that hits, although because he's prone, you have disadvantage on ranged attacks, which cancels your advantage.
DM: So
DM: that's not gonna work.
DM: I mean, you're not gonna sneak attack on him.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: Pr- you have disadvantage on prone creatures if you're further than five feet from them.
Wellby: Oh, well, got it. Sharpshooter doesn't negate that.
DM: No.
Unknown: That's just cover.
DM: That's just cover and range.
Wellby: Uh, I rolled both these simultaneously.
Unknown: Should I roll again or-
DM: Well, it, I mean, you can hit.
DM: I'm just saying you're not gonna get sneak attack and advantage.
Wellby: Can I shoot a different one instead?
DM: Uh, the readied actions has to be specific.
Unknown: All right. So I-
DM: You, you can hit. It's fine you hit.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: But just roll your strength damage.
Wellby: This is useless. Yeah. All right. That is a mighty
Unknown: seven. [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: It's bloodied.
DM: Um,
DM: Milo can take a shot.
Wellby: Uh, cool. He's gonna hit that same one on the ground.
Unknown: [dice rolling]
Delwath: But he also has the same problem.
Unknown: N-
Unknown: Yeah, he shouldn't shoot the one on the ground.
Unknown: He should change. Yeah.
DM: Go at one of the others.
Wellby: Seven was the higher plus-
DM: Plus
Wellby: ... nine, 16.
DM: That hits
Unknown: ... to
Wellby: hit. 2 more d6s.
Delwath: Yeah, we can s- I mean, it's better to knock two out of that actually.
Wellby: So 12, 18, 20, 30 altogether.
DM: Okay. That one's pretty wounded too.
DM: That ends Milo's turn.
Kenzo: This is just like-
DM: An invisible dragon-
Unknown: Oh-
DM: ... turns visible
Unknown: ... this is just-
Delwath: Oh, man, I should have stayed invisible.
Unknown: Wait
Unknown: ... this is just, this is
Unknown: just-
Unknown: I...
Unknown: Didn't you have-
DM: That was a long time ago
Delwath: ... No, I used-
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Fair enough.
DM: And shoots a line of darkness.
Unknown: Darkness?
Unknown: Oh.
DM: And acid.
Unknown: Darkness. That's interesting.
DM: Let me see.
Delwath: Wait, this is a daylight.
Delwath: We're powering the thing with daylight-
DM: I know
Delwath: ... just so you know.
DM: Um.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: 90 feet long and 20 feet wide, so it's two squares wide and nine squares long.
DM: One, two, so one,
DM: one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, sorry, nine.
DM: Who's that in the door?
Delwath: That's Milo.
DM: Okay. So it's gonna hit everybody here.
Delwath: Wait, Kenza and me are supposed to be 30...
Delwath: Oh, if it goes in the middle, it's 30 feet.
Unknown: Huh?
Delwath: Kenza and I are supposed to be 30 feet apart.
Kenzo: We're 30 feet apart.
Delwath: Oh, but it's shooting in between us.
Unknown: Yep. Because-
DM: It's shooting in between you.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: It's 20 feet wide.
Wellby: Does that cover the vertical distances involved?
Unknown: Where are we vertical?
DM: Well, okay, it can go...
DM: Where are you right now?
Unknown: It's okay. We can move.
Kenzo: I think it can hit you.
Unknown: No, it definitely hits.
DM: It can definitely hit you because you're thir- I mean-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... you're 30 feet this way.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
DM: So all of you, everybody there.
DM: Fortunately, Milo has invasion, evasion, otherwise he would probably be dead.
DM: Make a dexterity saving throw.
DM: [dice rolling]
Delwath: Fail. Six.
Delwath: That's not even worth trying to save [dice rolling] on a fail.
Unknown: So
Seeker: the, the ladder rolls, uh-
DM: I need some more d6s
Unknown: ... an eight
DM: I need a... Well, I'll just roll auto.
Unknown: I need a one [dice rolling]
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: There's more d-
Unknown: You should roll auto in general. Just roll auto.
Seeker: Yeah, I'll roll auto. [dice rolling] Um.
Seeker: The stone construct [dice rolling] rolls a 17.
Unknown: 23.
Wellby: 18 for Milo.
DM: Uh, okay. So anybody who beats a 22 succeeds.
Unknown: Fuck.
Seeker: Oh, oh. Oh man.
Delwath: He uses Bardic.
Wellby: He's gonna use his Bardic.
Kenzo: Definitely use Bardic.
DM: What'd you get?
Unknown: 23. [dice rolling] Oh, fuck.
Kenzo: He still fails.
Wellby: He still only gets a 20.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: Half damage, but still.
DM: So that is, um, 32 points of acid damage.
Kenzo: To what?
DM: Um, hold on. Let me just roll.
DM: And...
Unknown: They're all gonna die.
DM: 38 points of necrotic damage.
Delwath: It's not that bad. That's its breath.
DM: That's his breath. So Milo takes half of that because of evasion.
Delwath: I mean, that's half my hit points, but...
DM: So-
Seeker: That is a total of 70.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: 70. Anybody who failed takes 70.
Wellby: You're tracking hit points for everyone.
DM: But unless you're Milo, in which case you take 35.
Delwath: But you're not in the range. Oh, the, those guys are though.
Delwath: Do they make their save?
Seeker: No.
Unknown: Are they dead?
Seeker: They didn't make it a 22 save. Like there's no possible way they beat that.
Delwath: Yeah. Yeah. Could've rolled 20. Are they dead?
Seeker: Um, the, the stone construct is, is.
Unknown: Oh, that's awful.
Unknown: Right at, hits zero.
Delwath: Oh no, it cracks.
Kenzo: Can I eat a goodberry or [laughs]
Unknown: The stone construct cracks.
Unknown: No, it's too... You can't. You can't bring it back.
Seeker: The la- the ladder is down to 15.
DM: And that ends-
Unknown: Wow
DM: ... the dragon's turn.
Delwath: Well, that's kind of sad. We never got to use the construct.
Unknown: Hold on. Hold-
DM: I mean, you can summon it again.
Delwath: You can cast it.
DM: You can summon it at sixth level.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Hold on, hold on, though. Wait, so...
Kenzo: But it was 30 necrotic.
DM: It was 70 total, but, uh-
Unknown: You made the save
DM: ... 32-
Unknown: I made my save
Unknown: ... so zero.
DM: So you take zero if you make your save.
DM: You have evasion. You don't take any damage if you make a dex save.
Delwath: Oh, wait. Was that acid? That was acid and-
DM: 32 acid, 38 necrotic.
Delwath: I'm gonna, I'm gonna...
DM: So you add 16 back.
Delwath: Yeah. [sighs] 'Cause that's gonna last till the start of my next turn.
Kenzo: Is evasion a natural ability or is it-
DM: Yeah, it's part of your monk. It's your monk ability.
Kenzo: I've always had evasion?
DM: Yeah, since seventh level.
Unknown: Sweet. [intense music]
DM: Uh, that brings up Wellby.
DM: [die rolling] So Milo's down to, like, half his health.
DM: Oh, uh, the drac- the...
DM: Oh, that thing's, it's not immune to acid, it's just resistant to acid, right?
Delwath: Yeah, summon draconic spirit, it is resistant to acid.
DM: How many hit points does it have?
Unknown: It has 50.
DM: How m- did it make its save?
Delwath: I didn't, I forgot to roll a save.
Delwath: [die rolling] No.
DM: Okay. So it takes
DM: 38 plus 16.
Delwath: 48, it's gone.
Kenzo: Is this, uh... Oh, that's, that's the ladder.
Seeker: It, it took out the draconic spirit?
DM: It took out the draconic spirit and it took out the summons.
Unknown: Damn.
Kenzo: Is it, uh... How, how, how many...
Unknown: How high up is it flying to?
DM: Yeah, it's flying, it's flying.
DM: It's about level with you.
Unknown: Okay.
Kenzo: How high are we?
DM: That ends its turn, so Wellby, you're up.
Wellby: Chimeras, right?
DM: That was your job.
Unknown: Stand close.
DM: So the chimeras, the chimeras now at the be- they move another 120 feet closer.
Seeker: Or just run away because...
DM: This one stands up and this one's lagging back, but let's put these guys on the map.
Kenzo: Yeah, the chimeras. Finish them off.
Delwath: So I still get my attack.
Delwath: I get my ready action.
DM: You get your ready action, yep.
DM: Uh, not if you use your reaction to...
DM: Your ready action takes a reaction, so if you-
DM: Wow.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: three shots on a chimera.
Delwath: I'm probably better not using absorb elements.
Unknown: Hm.
Delwath: I'll take the 16 damage back.
DM: Okay. [die rolling]
Unknown: [laughs] 13.
DM: On a chimera, 13 misses.
Unknown: [die rolling] 19.
Unknown: That hits.
Unknown: [die rolling] [laughs]
Seeker: This, this is not going well.
Delwath: I think we might... I mean, why did we stay to fight these guys?
Delwath: [die rolling] Three damage.
Delwath: I, totally, that was a awful decision.
Wellby: Dimitar guilted us into it.
Delwath: Yeah.
Unknown: It is what it is.
Delwath: But Dim, you know you can't, like, kill us, right?
Seeker: Dimitar has not-
DM: You forced us to fight the dragon.
Unknown: No, we, we, we, we, we're totally fine.
DM: You're... Come on, it doesn't get his dr-
Unknown: That's true
DM: ... it's not gonna get his breath weapon back for a while.
Kenzo: We're, we're, we're... I think we're in great shape.
Delwath: I think not.
Wellby: We have the upper hand.
Unknown: [laughs] You've taken out, like, a good chunk of its health.
Delwath: I know. I'm not worried about the minions.
Kenzo: Well, just wait for the dragonets.
Kenzo: We to... The, the, our dragonets are gonna show up.
Delwath: Nah, I think the effect of our...
Unknown: Well, we'll see.
Unknown: They're good. They're good. They'll show up in a bit.
DM: Who's turn is it?
DM: Uh, so that...
DM: So Wel- Wellby hasn't done...
Unknown: Uh, Wellby, have you done anything yet?
DM: Nope.
DM: It's Wellby's turn.
Unknown: All right. I'm gonna shoot-
DM: Kenzo's next
Wellby: ... chimera number three.
DM: Okay. [die rolling]
Unknown: That hits.
DM: Hits.
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: more sixes.
DM: Dragons are supposed to make a dramatic entry.
Delwath: Yeah, I know.
Kenzo: No, that was great.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: It was feeling too easy.
Unknown: It was.
Unknown: It was feeling like way too easy.
Unknown: It was way too easy.
Kenzo: I was just like, what's going on?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: We're just like-
DM: You're, you're over-
Kenzo: ... we're just slaughtering these, these...
Kenzo: We haven't taken any damage. We're just sitting here relaxed.
DM: Uh, the nice effect of his sunlight though is normally it would leave scars of darkness across the battlefield, but they're instantly dispelled by the daylight spell.
Wellby: Oh, awesome. I'm also gonna dump all four charges of the [dice rolling] fire into this one.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: Oh, that's not great rolling.
Wellby: So that's 15.
Delwath: We used all our good rolls against the fiend.
Unknown: 21.
DM: Yeah. [laughs]
Unknown: Eh, we'll see.
Wellby: 25, 28.
Unknown: And he's down.
Wellby: Plus 6 is 34.
Wellby: Um, so that's 34 to start and then...
Unknown: [dice rolling]
Kenzo: Your hay says you get another.
Wellby: No, this is for the fire.
Wellby: It's another 16,
Wellby: so that's 50-
DM: Okay
Wellby: ... all together.
DM: Nine... That one's looking almost dead.
Wellby: Oh, shit. Can I move?
Kenzo: You didn't, you are not in the breath weapon attack radius, so you're, you're fine.
Kenzo: Are you flying?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah, he's flying.
Unknown: Cool.
DM: Dimitaur-
Wellby: Actually I'm gonna move
DM: ... on telepathy says, "Don't worry.
DM: I got this guys."
Unknown: What?
Kenzo: He's gonna use fireball on the dragon?
Wellby: Tim, I wanna take... Can I take-
Unknown: Yeah
Wellby: ... one of those D6s off to use a withdraw?
DM: Yep.
Wellby: I will do that.
Wellby: I'll move 45 feet,
Wellby: what? Straight upwards.
Unknown: Up?
Wellby: Yeah. Why not?
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: And then I'll ready an action
Wellby: to shoot, uh, number three again
Wellby: with whatever move.
DM: Okay.
DM: Uh, that ends Welby's turn.
DM: Um, Kenzo is up.
Unknown: All right friends.
Kenzo: It is time-
DM: How much damage does a seventh level fireball do?
Unknown: Let's go do other stuff.
Unknown: Uh.
DM: 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th. 12 D8s, yeah?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: It's 8d6 plus fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh.
Delwath: Yeah, 12d6.
Kenzo: So wait, I, um, for bless I get a d4 on all of my...
Kenzo: So even for the-
Unknown: Every-
Kenzo: Right, so it's, it's, each one of these gets a d4.
DM: Yeah, yep. Yep, yep.
Kenzo: Great. All right, so these count, right?
Unknown: So who are you closing on?
Kenzo: Um, so I'm gonna go fuckin'...
Unknown: Let's go Ra'ghemdros.
Unknown: Fuck up the dragon?
Unknown: Fuck you. Let's go.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: Ken- massive double-sized huge f- Kenzo, still small compared to the dragon, but large,
Kenzo: flies over to engage the dragon.
Kenzo: [object clattering] Oh, shit.
Unknown: Sorry. [laughs]
Unknown: All right. [sighs]
DM: Five attacks.
Unknown: Here we go.
DM: Flurry of blows.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Langal's claw.
Kenzo: Giant jaguar claw starts...
Kenzo: Oh, I actually, I actually don't have to be, I actually don't have to be engaged.
Unknown: But-
DM: You can be 15 feet away.
DM: There's no reason to be that close.
Unknown: Yeah, actually I'm gonna pull back
Unknown: one square.
Kenzo: All right, um, I'm gonna do these separately as, um, my, uh...
Unknown: Right? Oh, no, I don't have advantage right now.
Wellby: You don't have advantage.
DM: You don't have advantage.
Kenzo: All right. So but this is plus 10.
DM: Right. A dragon's AC is-
Kenzo: Again, and then it can attack again
Unknown: 22.
DM: Dragon's AC is 20.
Kenzo: Okay, so 22 hits.
Delwath: You could resummon the construct.
Delwath: I could use a healing...
Delwath: If I'm gonna charge into combat with it, a healing word might be helpful.
Kenzo: Um, and then I do D6 from the claw-
Kenzo: It'll probably stay at 50 for one turn
Kenzo: ... D4 from the, uh, bl-, uh, from the enlarged-
Kenzo: I don't know if it can get to 50 in one turn
Kenzo: ... and then D10 plus five, right?
DM: Uh, yep, that's what you roll, plus five.
Wellby: For damage. [dice rolling]
Wellby: When you summon the construct-
Unknown: Is
DM: this a two?
Wellby: Like summon it on the dragon's back
DM: That's a two
Wellby: So four-
Unknown: That's what I was just reading about it
Unknown: ... eight plus five is-
Unknown: 90 foot range
Unknown: ... 13.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Okay, that's the first attack.
DM: First attack.
Delwath: The ladder is here.
Unknown: 13.
Delwath: The ladder's still there.
DM: Wait, when did it go anyways?
Unknown: Second attack. [dice rolling]
DM: Seeker's a- right a- immediately after you.
Unknown: The second attack hits.
Unknown: So goes when's Tilly?
DM: Tilly's immediately after Seeker, then the chimeras, then Milo.
Kenzo: Um, Tim, I'm gonna... Wait, is it, is he immune to stun?
Unknown: He-
Seeker: It's that or use catapults
DM: ... yes, he's immune to stun.
Kenzo: He's immune to all my, my tricks, right?
DM: He's immune to all your tricks-
Unknown: No, they're not
DM: ... except your-
Seeker: Hit him with it
DM: ... massive giant fists
Unknown: ... I'm 10 feet away.
Unknown: Yeah. All right.
Unknown: I would... [dice rolling] I mean, you could go stun a chimera.
DM: They would probably fall pretty quickly.
DM: Yeah, but that's-
Kenzo: 3, 7, 12.
Unknown: So that's-
DM: Second attack is a 12
Kenzo: ... second attack is a 12. [dice rolling]
Unknown: Hits.
Unknown: Still hits.
Unknown: Plus 10, right?
Unknown: Yep.
DM: Oh, no, what's going on?
Delwath: I think s- I mean, summoning the construct [dice rolling] is maybe not a bad move.
Unknown: Ooh, this was a good one.
Unknown: Um-
DM: I mean, you could-
Unknown: ... a special 15
DM: ... summon the construct onto the dragon's back
Seeker: ... that's what I was thinking, yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah. Uh, third attack is a 22.
DM: Just have to get-
Unknown: 22 damage
Unknown: ... yep
Seeker: ... a tiny bit closer. Oh, no.
DM: Just don't get dead.
Unknown: Natural 20.
Wellby: Natural 20.
Kenzo: Let's fucking go.
Unknown: Yay.
Unknown: All right.
DM: That's, that's your fourth attack, so you still got one more.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Oh, so, so I roll these damage twice.
DM: All of it, all of it's twice. Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Okay,
Unknown: all right.
DM: Kenzo's just like-
Unknown: I'm, I'm-
DM: ... "No, no."
Unknown: ... just fuck this dragon.
DM: I dodge and dash.
Unknown: Oh, fuck this bitch. So s-
Delwath: 17
Delwath: ... 17.
Kenzo: Okay, I'm doing a lot of fucking damage to this thing.
Delwath: So that's 20. [dice rolling]
Unknown: Wow.
Unknown: Nice rolling.
Unknown: 17.
Unknown: Plus three plus-
Kenzo: Hold on, hold on. 31 plus 5, that's 36.
DM: 36.
Kenzo: And I got one more attack, my fifth attack.
Unknown: [dice rolling] Hits.
DM: Nice.
Delwath: All right, I'm feeling better about this.
Seeker: Yeah, that was good.
Unknown: [laughs] Kenzo's revived my stellar spirits.
Unknown: Uh, 10.
DM: I mean, Delwath was spot-
Kenzo: That's another 15
DM: ... on the fiend fight.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: And then Kenzo-
Unknown: 15
DM: ... hit the dragon fight.
Unknown: Yeah. Delwath's like, "Kenzo-"
DM: That's another 15 damage
Kenzo: ... another 15 damage, yeah.
Unknown: What'd you do?
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Good damage.
DM: Kenza did 98...
Unknown: Oh, no, min- yeah, 98 damage in one round.
Seeker: Can we get a visual on it?
Kenzo: Uh, just giant, massive jaguar fist, just faster than you can even see, going boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, right into the dra- Like, the dragon's head's going uh, uh, uh,
Unknown: uh, uh, uh, uh. [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Yeah, your giant fist is, like, kind of the size of its head.
Kenzo: That was satisfying.
Kenzo: Please swap.
DM: Oh, yeah.
DM: Just gonna bring
DM: my... Uh, okay. That ends Kenzo's turn.
DM: The dragonets...
DM: Um, Welby, you moved 40 feet straight up?
Wellby: 45 feet straight up.
DM: Okay. Um, the dragonets are gonna split into two groups.
DM: One group is gonna dash
DM: and swarm Delvy, Welby.
DM: That's half of them. That's seven of them.
Wellby: I think that they can't close into melee with me this round unless they dash.
Delwath: Yeah, they dash.
DM: They dash.
Unknown: That's what I said.
Wellby: Oh, okay.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Wellby: So they can't attack.
DM: Yeah, they can't attack-
Wellby: Great
DM: ... but they can close into melee.
Unknown: So one, two, three, four.
Wellby: Does my readied action require my reaction?
DM: Yes.
Unknown: Yes.
Wellby: Okay.
Kenzo: So I'm just moving all seven of these together-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... into, like, a group.
DM: They're like around Welby. The other six, um, are looking for spellcasters.
DM: The only one they can see right now is-
Unknown: Tilly?
DM: ... Seek- oh, Tilly's on the roof.
Delwath: Tilly's on the roof.
DM: They're gonna move towards Tilly.
Kenzo: How many of them?
DM: [laughs] Um, all-
Unknown: Five?
DM: All five of them that are left.
Unknown: Oh, six.
Unknown: Wait, was, was Tilly... Tilly was unclear
Delwath: assignment. I think, I think draconic sp- oh, wait, can they close to her?
DM: Um, h- no, that's, like, five squares, right?
DM: That- They...
DM: No, they get within...
DM: They can dash. They close with her with a dash
Delwath: Okay, but they're surrounding her?
DM: They're surrounding her.
Unknown: Man, that's annoying.
DM: Go to it.
Unknown: And the
Wellby: chimeras move?
DM: No, the chime- chimeras are later in the initiative.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: I just wasn't keeping them separate while they were just all dashing.
Unknown: Good.
DM: That ends the dragon S turn.
Unknown: And what about the minions?
DM: Then... They're minions.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Del, what's up?
Delwath: I can close to the dragon.
Delwath: I'm just doing it.
Unknown: Yeah, let's fucking go, Del.
Unknown: Like, I mean-
Unknown: Let's just fucking go.
DM: Oh, sorry, I forgot. Um, oh no, not for Kenzo, but Delwath, when you
DM: start your turn,
DM: uh, Kenza is not within 30 feet, is he?
Unknown: No.
DM: Uh, when you start your turn-
Unknown: Oh, Kenza, you're supposed to stay within 30 feet of me
DM: ... within... Oh, well, how close are you to the dragon right now?
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Uh, it was like 80, 70 feet.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Or 60.
DM: You don't need to make your save till you get within 30 feet of the dragon.
Kenzo: Yeah, but then you'll be within 30 feet.
Delwath: That'll all get me 30 feet of Kenza.
DM: Yes.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: When you get within 30 feet of the dragon for the first time you have to make a save against fear.
Delwath: Okay. So, so I'm gonna close to here.
Kenzo: Nice. Perfect.
Delwath: But I'm within 30 feet of Kenzo.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So make your wisdom save with advantage.
Delwath: Well, hopefully I do better on my second roll.
Unknown: I need a different die. I'm not happy with this die.
Unknown: Nice.
Unknown: Yes. [clapping]
DM: And you are immune to its fear.
Delwath: Okay. So I close.
Unknown: Bonus action mark it.
DM: Good thing you had advantage.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: bonus action mark it.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: And then
Unknown: stab it.
Kenzo: Dragon claw came in handy.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Uh, 21.
DM: That hits. AC is 20.
Delwath: I need two D6 too.
Unknown: Here.
Kenzo: Actually, I want that.
Delwath: Okay, let's take two of yours. Okay, so this glowing...
Delwath: I mean, Delwath's glowing with bright light and when he attacks some of the light travels along his sword-
Kenzo: Ooh, that's good damage
Kenzo: ... and hits the dragon.
Kenzo: We like that.
Delwath: 10, 19 plus 5.
Unknown: 24.
Delwath: 24. Attack one is 24.
Unknown: Not crit.
DM: That's a 20.
Delwath: I'll do smite.
Kenzo: You can declare that after a crit?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah, it's after you hit.
Unknown: That's sweet.
Unknown: Oh man, that's a lot of damage.
Unknown: Uh-
Unknown: Look
Delwath: ... I'll do smite is eight, seven...
Delwath: Wait, how much did you say it was? Six, six, so 12.
DM: 12 D8.
Unknown: Six.
Delwath: Oops. So it's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Delwath: So it's eight, it's this doubled.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: Wait, be careful.
Delwath: Uh, 10, 20,
Delwath: uh, 10, 20,
Unknown: 30,
Delwath: uh, plus fi- uh, plus 5, 40, 48.
Delwath: That included my normal plus 5.
Unknown: Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: So yeah.
DM: All right.
Delwath: 15,
Unknown: 20,
Unknown: 30,
Delwath: 8, 9,
Delwath: uh, 45. Oh, I'm giving Kenzo a run for his money.
Unknown: Yeah, this is, I mean, this is-
DM: Yeah
Kenzo: ... this is how it should be.
DM: Um, after Delwath ends its turn-
Delwath: I'm not done. I got one more attack.
DM: Oh, you're... Oh, sorry.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Three attacks. Three attacks.
DM: Oh, you might surpass Kenzo then.
DM: You're gonna surpass Kenzo if you hit.
Unknown: You will.
Unknown: Yeah?
Delwath: That burns a spell. I knew I was saving my spell slots for a reason.
Unknown: That smells good.
DM: Mm.
Unknown: Oh, plus 5 more damage.
Delwath: I forgot I marked it.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Oh, I still crit on 19s.
Unknown: Nope.
Wellby: You crit on 19s?
Unknown: Uh, 17. That misses.
DM: That misses.
DM: So after, after Delwath's-
Delwath: With when I've marked the creature
DM: ... after Delwath's turn, um, you can see the dragon is angry and pissed.
DM: It wasn't quite expecting this much fight.
DM: Sort of shakes its wings and these,
DM: um, globules of acid fly out of its mouth.
DM: Um,
DM: let's see. Who's within nine squares?
DM: One,
DM: uh, one, two, three-
Seeker: Um, I'm not
DM: ... four, five, six.
Delwath: No. Nine is 100, nine squares is like 90 feet?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah. Okay.
DM: Two, three. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
DM: Uh,
DM: Wellby is not.
DM: Tilly is. Dimitar is hiding.
DM: Um, so everybody but Wellby has to make a dexterity saving throw.
DM: Dex plus seven.
DM: Tilly gets
DM: an 8.
Delwath: Tilly rolls a one.
Unknown: 24.
Delwath: Uh, Tilly has a pl- has a two.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Delwath has a 14.
Wellby: Milo rolls a-
Unknown: No, a 15
Wellby: ... 27.
DM: Okay. Anybody... Sorry, 27.
Unknown: 24.
Unknown: But I might-
DM: 24.
Unknown: Shit.
DM: What did you roll?
Unknown: 15.
DM: Okay. That fails.
Unknown: Okay. I think-
DM: You two succeed
Unknown: ... I'm going to-
DM: What did you roll?
Unknown: 13.
DM: You fail. Tilly fails.
Wellby: Does she have heroic inspiration?
Seeker: I can heroic inspiration that, right?
DM: You can.
Delwath: Oh, wait, she's a halfling.
Seeker: That's just re-roll, right?
DM: Oh, she re-rolls ones. Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: 8.
Seeker: All right. So I use my heroic inspiration to re-roll mine.
Unknown: 6.
Delwath: I actually get plus 7.
Unknown: That's a 2.
Delwath: I have 22.
Unknown: That's-
DM: Okay. You succeed
Seeker: ... 17.
DM: Um, so a globule-
Unknown: 18, 20
DM: ... of acid... Sorry, what did you get?
Seeker: 17.
DM: A globule of acid attaches itself to Seeker.
Unknown: Shit.
DM: Tilly.
DM: What did Milo roll?
Unknown: 27.
Unknown: 7. Yeah.
DM: Seeker and Tilly.
Unknown: Ah.
Delwath: Wait, Tilly got... I don't know.
Delwath: She only got an 8. She's not gonna make it even with bardic inspiration.
Kenzo: What'd you get?
Delwath: Uh, I got a 15, but I used my favor of the gods.
Unknown: Latanchi came down and blessed me and gave me a plus 7.
DM: Tilly, Tilly might have to run.
DM: Um, so Tilly and Seeker take, um, 14 points of acid damage and a globule of acid is attached to each of you.
DM: You can use an acid, an action to remove it, uh, from yourself or another creature.
Delwath: Tilly's gonna absorb elements.
DM: Okay. But if you don't remove it, you take 14 damage at the s- um, end of every turn.
Delwath: It's only 7 damage. That's not...
Delwath: I mean, she can absorb elements every turn.
DM: Yes.
Unknown: Yeah Okay.
Kenzo: So she's still all right.
Unknown: She's okay.
Unknown: How many hit points does she have?
Delwath: 81 right now.
Unknown: Ah, man. She's-
DM: So she wasn't hit by the breath weapon.
Delwath: No, she missed the breath. Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um.
Unknown: Did you get hit by the breath weapon?
Unknown: No.
Seeker: Oh, great. Great.
Unknown: So I could, I could take 14 damage all day long.
DM: It's Seeker's turn.
DM: Um-
Kenzo: All right, Seeker, let's do something awesome.
Unknown: I, I was-
Delwath: Summon the go one is back
Seeker: ... I was mad about that stone construct getting destroyed.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: And I just realized, if I cast it at eighth level, it can make four attacks.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: [laughs] Do it. Do it.
Unknown: And has-
Unknown: Just do it
Unknown: ... 100 points-
Unknown: Just... No, no
Unknown: ... of AC 21.
Unknown: That's absolutely.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: You, you need to give-
Unknown: And-
Unknown: You need to give Captain America a run for his money.
DM: That's fucking go. Yeah, let's fucking go.
Seeker: I can drop it... Well, it's still...
Seeker: Anyway, it'll be pretty good.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: I can drop it-
Unknown: Eight attacks
Seeker: ... basically onto-
DM: Four
DM: ... yeah, you can drop it onto its back.
Seeker: Onto the dragon's back.
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Hold on. Let, let me see if there's a way to balance it here.
Unknown: Go ahead and put it...
Unknown: [laughs] So-
DM: I don't think it's gonna-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Two four, two four and the sixes.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: Oh, yeah. There you go.
Unknown: So it-
Seeker: Can you do it like this?
Seeker: And it can attack right away, right?
DM: It can attack right away.
Unknown: Yeah. Um.
Delwath: Does its damage go up 'cause it's...
Delwath: No, it just gets more attacks.
Seeker: Yeah. Um,
Seeker: so its attack is...
Kenzo: How long does, before it can do its breath weapon again?
Delwath: It rolls every turn and if it gets a six, it can do it again.
Unknown: [dice rolling] That's usually how dragons work.
Seeker: Oh, actually no, it is more. It's-
Unknown: 'Cause you went down.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: That, that's really, that's actually really cool.
Unknown: 28 plus 12.
Kenzo: Yeah, it's creepy and scary.
Delwath: Yeah, another breath weapon would take Delwath down.
Seeker: And my attack roll is D20 plus two.
Delwath: But you're fi-... I mean, you...
Delwath: With evasion, it's so useful against dragons.
Unknown: It is.
Kenzo: It's pretty fucking amazing, yeah.
Unknown: So I have four of those.
Kenzo: You also have evasion, right? Yeah. Good.
Unknown: 19.
DM: Yeah, Milo-
Unknown: Did Milo get hit by the first one?
Unknown: Nope.
DM: He was out of the breath weapon.
Kenzo: Milo get hit by the first one?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Yes.
Unknown: Milo's the biggest, in the most danger.
Wellby: Milo also has evasion, though, as a rogue.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: So he took half.
Kenzo: Oh, he took half damage.
Wellby: Otherwise, okay. Being serious troll.
Seeker: Yeah. Um, all right.
Seeker: So I'll... The stone construct makes its four slam attacks.
Unknown: [dice rolling]
Unknown: Let's go.
Seeker: Oh, man.
Unknown: Oh, no.
Unknown: It's plus.
Seeker: So a 28, a 21.
Delwath: Those two of them hit.
Unknown: Two hits
Seeker: ... a 16 and a 11.
Unknown: Two hit.
DM: Two hit.
Seeker: So that's
Seeker: 2D8 plus [dice rolling] 24 damage.
Unknown: 2D8 plus?
Unknown: Uh, 2D8. I'm just talking D8s here.
Kenzo: 2D8 plus what?
Unknown: 24.
Unknown: Oh, nice.
Seeker: [dice rolling] So
Seeker: 27.
DM: 27. That's-
Unknown: Hey, man.
Kenzo: That's good.
DM: [laughs] Wait, does it have rider?
DM: Does it do something?
Delwath: Yeah. Decreased speed by...
Seeker: So stony lethargy.
Seeker: When a creature the constructs can see starts his turn within 10 feet of the construct, the construct can force it to make a wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC.
Delwath: Oh, it can use reactions.
Unknown: DC.
Seeker: That's good.
Seeker: On a failed save, the target can't use reactions and its speed is halved until the start of his next turn.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: I mean, it might make a save.
Seeker: A wisdom save, yeah.
DM: That ends Seeker's turn.
Kenzo: Did you roll a wisdom save?
Unknown: Uh, the ladder.
DM: No, that's when it starts its turn.
Unknown: Ladder.
Seeker: But ladder also has a move of 40.
DM: Is the ladder immune to fear or have we looked at this before?
Seeker: That's a good question.
Unknown: [laughs]
Seeker: The ladder...
Kenzo: [laughs] Well, once it's within 30 feet of me, it still gets-
Unknown: No
Unknown: ... it still gets a save.
DM: Okay. So ladder needs to roll a f- a save against the fright.
Unknown: Look.
Unknown: With advantage.
Unknown: Wait, wait.
Unknown: It's, it started with him.
Seeker: Immune to frightened.
Unknown: Oh, no, no.
Delwath: Yeah, it's immune.
Unknown: Sorry, sorry.
DM: La- Of course it's the heroic ladder.
Unknown: It's the ladder. [laughs]
DM: The ladder. It can't be scared.
Kenzo: Did, did the ladder give the fatal blow to the last dragon anyways?
Unknown: It was, it was-
Unknown: I think it did.
Unknown: It did.
DM: It did.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
DM: The last dragon, the ladder grappled it and held it down-
Unknown: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... for the most of the fight.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: And made it possible for you to finish it.
Kenzo: All right, so you're moving this closer?
Seeker: So the, the ladder is gonna go up...
Seeker: Should I try to grapple instead of slam?
Wellby: Totally, 'cause gr- grapple also neutralizes-
DM: Well, well you can't. It's too...
DM: This is an ancient dragon. It's gargantuan.
DM: It's too big for the ladder to grapple.
Seeker: All right. So it just makes its, its slam attack.
Seeker: [dice rolling] Uh, that's a 24.
Unknown: That hits.
Seeker: So hit. [dice rolling] And it's-
Wellby: It's just that, like, the ladder should get on its back or otherwise out of [dice rolling] its breath weapon-
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... direction.
Kenzo: Yeah. Getting on, on the, on it.
Seeker: It only has a 40 move though, so.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: Well.
Delwath: I mean, we want to be spread out so that...
Delwath: I mean, that's fine. It can't... I mean, it could move over here and get all of us with a breath weapon, but.
Unknown: That's just how it is. That's like how the-
Seeker: Um, so 1D10 plus five damage.
Unknown: Yeah, that'd be a two.
Delwath: Or move here and get all of us and Tilly, but.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: So that's... [dice rolling] It does,
Seeker: uh, 12 damage with its slam.
DM: Okay.
Seeker: Now Seeker should move probably.
Seeker: I, I only have 30 moves, so I can go like,
Seeker: I don't know, back over here, I guess.
Kenzo: That's pretty good.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Minions-
Unknown: Okay
Delwath: ... how many minions die if they fail saves?
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Okay.
Kenzo: Oh, you're gonna do like radiance or something?
Unknown: No, I'm not. Tilly.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Unknown: Uh, that ends Seeker's turn. [dice rolling] Tilly's up.
Delwath: Tilly is gonna cast-
Unknown: Come on, Tilly
Delwath: ... uh, so there's no point in... Is there any point...
Delwath: Oh, it's still worth up casting, 'cause if they make the save, they get-
DM: If they make the save, you have to pass their hit points.
Delwath: Tilly is gonna cast a second level thunder wave to clear out the mess.
DM: Oh, okay. Awesome.
Delwath: Exactly. [dice rolling] DC 17 con save.
DM: Okay. There's one, two, three-
Unknown: Good call
DM: ... four, five, six around there.
DM: Um, con?
Delwath: DC 17 con.
DM: Okay, so they have-
Wellby: Does it reach the closest chimeran?
Delwath: It's 15 feet.
DM: No, that's not gonna reach the chimeras.
Unknown: So it's not.
DM: [dice rolling] Yeah, it's plus, only plus two.
DM: Um,
DM: one
DM: succeeds. [dice rolling] And-
Delwath: Five damage for the one that succeeds.
DM: Okay. So one... Oh, sorry.
DM: Tilly starts her turn, when she starts her turn surrounded by these, she takes four points of acid damage.
Delwath: Uh, is that... She's resistant-
DM: Is it to the end?
Delwath: ... until the end, until the end of your next turn for sure.
Unknown: Then she takes two points.
DM: She takes nine points total.
DM: Two points plus another seven from the globule.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: And she kills all but one of these.
Unknown: Wow.
Unknown: Nice.
Seeker: Amazing.
Delwath: Oh, no, start of your next turn.
DM: Sorry, she's not resistant, so she takes 11 points of acid damage.
Unknown: Totally s-
DM: Sorry, 14 points of acid damage
Seeker: ... tied his Tilly turn. We had a little moment, but.
Delwath: Okay. And there's one left.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: Breath weapon's scary.
Unknown: [laughs] It's scary.
Delwath: She's flying, so she's gonna fly-
DM: We'd like you to review. She's got a 60 foot fly speed.
DM: She might want to just get out of there.
Delwath: Yeah. She doesn't actually care about the attack of opportunity.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: She's gonna go-
DM: One minion can't rip one
Unknown: ... to, let's see
DM: One, two, three
Kenzo: Uh, don't we like kinda wanna spread 'em out a little bit more and attack it?
Delwath: Yeah, I wanna get away, but I don't...
Delwath: She doesn't wanna fight towards the chimeras
Kenzo: How about over here? Up this way.
DM: If you can just like back that way.
Delwath: Yeah. One, two, three, four, five [sneezes] six.
DM: Like there. Okay, that ends Tilly's turn.
DM: Um, the chimeras are up.
Wellby: So first, the chimera-
DM: Reaction
Wellby: ... that I hit rolls a DC 13 CON save against the-
DM: Fire
Wellby: Yep.
DM: You hit the one... You hit three?
Wellby: Three.
DM: Um,
DM: that fails.
Wellby: Awesome. That is eight plus six is 14 points of fire damage, and it's still on fire.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um,
DM: sorry, that was... Which chimera was that?
DM: Four?
Unknown: Chimera three.
Wellby: Three.
DM: Three.
Unknown: Four's not been touched.
Wellby: Four's not been touched.
DM: Four's, four's been hit, was hit by...
DM: It's CON saving throw.
Unknown: Oh, the cone. Yeah
DM: ... was hit by the ice thing.
Kenzo: That's the ice thing. Yeah.
DM: Um,
DM: okay. So two is now just dashing to get onto the battlefield.
DM: these ones... So how...
DM: You're 45 feet up.
DM: Okay, they've got a 60 foot fly, so this one's gonna close onto you.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: And-
Wellby: I don't think it can close onto me this round
DM: ... it's two over and four up.
DM: It's 20 and 40, and the hypotenuse is shorter than the two sides.
Wellby: Yeah, but it started its turn two squares into the map.
Unknown: Mm.
Wellby: It s- it started with an extra 20 feet of move when it came-
Unknown: It was on the map
Wellby: ...
Wellby: onto the map.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Oh, if it's here, then it's like one, two, third...
DM: Well, it's still two 'cause of diagonal movement.
DM: We always just count that as-
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: I think it can close on you.
Wellby: Sure.
Unknown: Funny.
DM: The prone one can't because it...
DM: This one can't 'cause it's too far away.
Wellby: But as it's moving, I shoot it.
DM: Yes.
Seeker: [laughs] Naturally.
Wellby: And that is a 21.
DM: Okay. That hits.
Wellby: Uh, somebody's a lower 'cause I'm low on D6s.
Unknown: Yeah. The D6 has got a bit scattered.
DM: Well, this was-
Kenzo: Well, they're all... They're being used to indicate-
Wellby: It's terrible
Unknown: ... people, people flying and stuff
Wellby: Um, just 25
Unknown: ... their structural.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um, both chimera two and chimera three are looking pretty badly hurt,
DM: so that's the two non-prone ones.
DM: Oh, sorry. The chimera two was the prone one.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um, so chimera three is nearly dead.
DM: That's the one that just flew up to you.
DM: Um, chimera four is unhurt.
DM: The prone one is bloodied.
DM: Um, and the chimera now is going to-
Kenzo: Four's not unhurt. It's g- just got that little bit ice damage.
DM: Uh,
DM: four is a little bit hurt-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... but not very badly.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: It's going to make, um,
DM: two... It's gonna make three bite attacks.
DM: Um,
DM: uh, the first...
DM: Well, first it's gonna make two bite attacks against Wellby.
DM: Um, that's gonna be a 14 and a 20.
Wellby: Both miss 'cause I have plus two AC from haste.
DM: Ah, okay.
DM: [laughs] Sweet.
DM: And then-
Delwath: 20 AC's nice, isn't it?
DM: Um...
Wellby: Yes.
DM: [laughs] Uh, it is going to use its, um, roar.
DM: You must make a wisdom saving throw or be frightened.
Wellby: Wisdom saving throw-
Unknown: Nope
Wellby: ... is, uh, 14, which is not great and probably doesn't beat it.
DM: You are frightened.
Delwath: Do you have bardic inspiration?
Wellby: Do I have bardic inspiration?
Unknown: You do. You do.
Wellby: Did you give it to me?
Kenzo: I gave him a little.
DM: You haven't used it yet, have you?
Unknown: I don't think he has.
Wellby: I don't think I've used it.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Who's used inspiration?
DM: You have?
Delwath: No, I used-
DM: Tilly
Delwath: ... I used favor the gods. Tilly used inspiration.
DM: Tilly used inspiration.
Delwath: I used favor the gods.
Wellby: All right. That's 24 to save.
DM: [laughs] That succeeds. Wait, you only roll one.
Seeker: The original stone con-
Wellby: Uh, I rolled the 10 then
Delwath: [laughs] Okay. What was the other one?
Wellby: A three.
DM: Just roll it again.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: The original stone construct had one-
DM: No.
Unknown: Oh, wow.
DM: You succeed. You were only off by two anyway.
DM: You were not-
Kenzo: You used your heroic.
Wellby: Do I get anything in addition?
DM: You get nine temporary hit points.
Unknown: Oh, you can inspire yourself.
Delwath: Tilly gets temporary hit points.
DM: What did you roll?
Delwath: Uh, like a four.
DM: Okay. Give her... Just give her four...
DM: Well, yeah, just give her four temporary hit points.
Delwath: No, I'm just gonna give her four hit points back.
DM: Yeah, yeah, that makes sense. Okay.
DM: Um, and then it's going to, um...
DM: It... Does it care about those minions?
Delwath: The chimera?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Die.
Wellby: It has a very low intelligence.
DM: It's just gonna spit fire at you.
DM: Um-
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: This is the fourth thing it's done now.
DM: With so-
Unknown: Collaterally
Wellby: Oh, it has a bunch of heads.
DM: It has three heads and a bonus action.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: Um,
DM: so make a dex save.
Delwath: Yeah, what do you care if people spit fire at you?
Unknown: Dodge out of the way.
Wellby: Do I have a ring of fire resist?...
Wellby: I have a ring of fire resistance.
Unknown: You do have a ring of fire resistance.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah, and the most you can take is one quarter of the damage.
Wellby: All right. I roll, uh, something over 20.
Wellby: 24.
DM: So you take zero damage.
Unknown: Yeah. You guys-
Wellby: Awesome
Delwath: ... you two laugh in the face of breath weapons.
Delwath: You just dance around.
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: Um, and
DM: it's only a, it's only a 10-foot radius, and it's aiming a little off to the side, so I think it's just gonna hit that one minion-
Unknown: It's gonna hit Dimitaur
DM: ... that's closest to you.
Delwath: Oh, yeah. Wait.
DM: What?
Delwath: Did Dimitaur... What happened to Dimitaur?
DM: Dimitaur, he's like...
DM: He's waiting.
Kenzo: He's very excited to act.
DM: He needs the dragon not to be surrounded by people.
Unknown: Oh.
Kenzo: He's about to hit him with a fireball.
Delwath: Man, he should get meta magic so he gets high, like safe spell.
DM: Um, one minion also dies from the fire, the closest one to you.
DM: Um, that ends that chimera's turn.
DM: This chimera, um, is going to
DM: fly,
DM: um, also going to just fly, dashing, um, to get behind you, closing in on Wellby.
Delwath: Thanks for drawing all the other-
DM: Um-
Unknown: ... people
Wellby: No, no, this is the plan. This is good.
DM: Still has a bonus action-
Kenzo: This actually, this actually... So you're, you're excellent
DM: ... so it's also gonna roar
Wellby: Your axe did-
Wellby: It's also gonna roar
Unknown: ... quite well.
DM: But it dashes, so it can't attack you with its heads.
Unknown: Wisdom save.
DM: Wisdom save.
Wellby: Wisdom save is
Wellby: 17? 17.
DM: That makes it.
Unknown: All right.
DM: Man, that rogue, rogue level 15 ability is pretty good.
Unknown: Are you proficient in all saves?
Wellby: No, but I got wisdom and something else.
DM: Wisdom and intelligence, I think.
Wellby: Yeah. Wisdom, yeah.
DM: That saved you from the Feeble Mind, too.
Unknown: Oh, the Befuddle.
DM: The Befuddle.
Wellby: Although, in fairness, I still can't cast spells [laughs].
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: No, except-
Kenzo: You still can't what?
DM: Uh-
Unknown: Cast spells
DM: ... activating your armor is a magic action.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
DM: It made it so you can fly.
Delwath: Okay, okay. Whose turn? I forget the order.
DM: So that ends-
Unknown: This is crazy
DM: ... the chimera's, Milo's turn.
Unknown: The dragon is after Milo.
Unknown: Oh, fuck.
DM: Uh, Dimitaur says, "Get ready."
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Um, Milo's gonna shoot number three.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: Who's the closest to death, right?
DM: Number three is very close to death.
DM: That's the one that attacked you.
Kenzo: That's the... This is two. This is thir- This is three.
DM: Three is this one.
Unknown: Three is this one, yeah.
DM: This is two. This is three.
DM: That's four.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: How close to death is two?
DM: Two is, like, just past bloody.
DM: All right.
DM: Three is, like, one strike.
Kenzo: Three. He's gonna take a hit.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, negative 20.
DM: It only has eight hit points left, so three is dead.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: [coughs] That ends-
Unknown: [sighs]
DM: ... Milo's turn. Now it's the dragon's turn.
Unknown: Oh, fuck.
DM: It looks around. It's pissed.
Seeker: So now does it have to make that wisdom saving throw because of the-
DM: Oh, it does. It does.
Kenzo: Yes.
Unknown: It's-
Delwath: It hasn't used a lot of legendary actions.
DM: It used the gobbles.
Unknown: Oh, yeah, it did use the gobble.
DM: Um, that is a...
Seeker: It's against Milo, so it's-
DM: Uh, 25
Seeker: Yeah, so it succeeds.
DM: It is pissed at this light that is messing up all of its darkness actions.
Unknown: Oh, shit.
DM: So it is going to-
Unknown: Oh, no
DM: ... destroy the light.
Wellby: We have a second drift globe.
DM: First-
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: ... it is going to-
Unknown: Another drift globe
DM: ... bite at Delwath.
DM: Um, that's a...
DM: Oh, that's only a 19.
DM: That misses.
DM: That misses. It's gonna slash at you with a claw.
Delwath: Delwath again?
DM: Delwath again. That is a 24.
Delwath: I will cast Shield.
DM: Okay.
DM: Uh, Delwath again. Uh, that's a 30-
Unknown: Battle
DM: ... 2.
Unknown: [laughs] 32.
DM: An attack over 30. Um, wait, sorry.
DM: Delwath is that one right there, the, in the way.
Delwath: No, that's Delwath.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: That's Delwath, okay. So Delwath takes,
DM: um,
DM: 15 points of slashing damage, and it's gonna just shove you out of the way with its claw, moving you 15 feet this way.
Unknown: That's great.
Kenzo: But the ladder is still in front, and then the clay golem, the golem is still on top of him, right?
DM: Yeah, and then it's gonna fly
DM: up.
Kenzo: With the golem?
DM: Yep. Golem on its back,
DM: and land right there.
Kenzo: Do I get an opportunity attack?
DM: No, 'cause y- none of you are within-
Seeker: So it's... And I was. I'm on the-
DM: It pushed. It pushed you.
Kenzo: But I'm with the... I get an attack
DM: Oh, you have the lion guard's claw.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So you're, you get an opportunity attack.
Kenzo: Thank you.
Wellby: The ladder was not in melee with him?
Seeker: The ladder is in melee.
DM: Uh, it-
Kenzo: Yeah, the ladder-
DM: The ladder does as well.
Unknown: So that's-
DM: And it lands on the top of this thing, and you hear Dimitaur-
Unknown: Hold on, hold on, hold on. Let's, let's do this. Let's do-
Kenzo: Yeah, do your opportunity attack
Unknown: ... let's do our opportunity attacks first.
DM: Sure.
Unknown: Crit. Fuck, does this fucking go?
DM: The ladder.
Unknown: The ladder.
Unknown: Let's fucking go ladder.
Wellby: Fucking ladder.
Seeker: So that's, um...
Seeker: So what do I, what do I double? It's a 1d10 plus 5.
Delwath: So roll the d10 twice, two d10.
Unknown: Thank you.
Seeker: S- six, I guess.
Delwath: Plus five, so 11.
Unknown: So 11. All right.
Kenzo: And then opportunity attack with its claw.
Kenzo: That definitely hits.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: So 26, and then I do, uh- So how, how much did the ladder do?
Delwath: 11.
Unknown: Okay. And then I do, uh,
Kenzo: 10, thir- eight, uh, 18.
DM: 18 damage, okay.
DM: Um-
Unknown: Great
DM: ... Dimitaur says, "Now's my chance."
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: He's been holding an action to cast a 7th level fireball from his wand-
Kenzo: Let's go
DM: ... for a long time.
Kenzo: Let's go, Dimitaur.
DM: And you see-
Seeker: Oh, and the stone construct is gonna get hit by it.
DM: Oh.
Unknown: That's fine.
DM: Yeah, well.
Unknown: Well.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: The dragon is big enough. Can't he just get the left, right side of the dragon?
DM: Oh, yeah, he can hit... He can just hit it.
DM: He aims it right below the dragon.
Unknown: There's a huge empty space right here.
DM: So the stone golem is shielded-
Unknown: By the body of the dragon
DM: ... by the body of the dragon from...
DM: Uh, so that is four-
Unknown: 12
DM: ... 12 D6.
DM: Somebody want to roll for damage on that?
Unknown: 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13.
DM: It's a 12 D6es.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: All right. Let's go, Dimitaur.
DM: Does it fall?
Unknown: This is 12?
DM: Uh, I don't think so.
Kenzo: One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
Unknown: 10.
Unknown: All right, 11 total.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: That's all of his charges on his wand of fireballs.
Unknown: Yep. Thanks, Dimitaur.
Kenzo: Channeling rise. Visualizing lots of fives and sixes.
Unknown: Let's see.
DM: All right. Not bad.
Delwath: Let's see.
Delwath: Not... But not bad.
Unknown: Okay, 10,
Unknown: 20,
Kenzo: uh, 30,
Unknown: uh,
Kenzo: 35-
DM: 40
Unknown: ... 40, 45.
DM: 45.
Unknown: 45.
DM: Wait.
Unknown: Did I kill it?
Unknown: Didn't kill it.
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: But that was, that, that was... We, we appreciated that.
Unknown: It was a good shot, though.
Unknown: Yeah, it was a good shot.
DM: And now it's gonna use its object interaction to knock one of the two drift globes.
DM: It can't knock both without using an action.
DM: Just
DM: use a giant claw to just knock it,
DM: toss, rolling down into that temple right there.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: So the light radius reduces to 300 feet.
Seeker: 300. So it's all the way at the top of the tower, which is how high?
DM: It's like, it's like-
Unknown: I mean, we were flying.
DM: Oh. You were flying pretty high.
Kenzo: Wait, the lion guard's claw, I also get push.
Kenzo: I can push him 15 feet.
DM: He's too big.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: Can't push gargantuan creatures.
Unknown: Mm-mm.
DM: You're o- you're only large. You need to be huge to push.
Unknown: Yeah. Okay. Probably need another push on-
DM: All right. Who's up? So that ends the dragon's turn.
DM: So Wellby.
Unknown: Ugh.
DM: Wellby is fucking fucked [laughs].
Delwath: Can, can you escape?
Delwath: I mean, you could... Couldn't you bonus action disengage, fly up, and then...
Delwath: I mean, then you don't get sneak attack, though, so.
DM: Well, you get it on the last one you hit from Vax.
Wellby: Who's the last one that I hit?
Unknown: Didn't you... Oh, no.
Wellby: Uh, it was the one that was dead.
Unknown: Oh, it's dead. It's dead. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wellby: Shit. Um.
Delwath: Wait. You could hit...
Delwath: Fight the drag- Disengage, fly up, and attack the dragon.
Unknown: You'll get sneak attack. The golem's on his back.
DM: It's true.
Wellby: Yeah, sure. I'll cunning action disengage.
DM: Oh, sorry. You start your turn in front of the minions.
DM: You take, uh, four points of,
DM: um, acid damage.
Wellby: What?
DM: From the little guys? Um, because they're all, like, a- dripping with acid and they're, like, spitting it across among them.
Wellby: Oh.
DM: And so you're just caught in the crossfire.
Delwath: He's fine. That's Tilly. She...
Delwath: Yeah, she's fine. Yeah, yeah.
Wellby: Um,
Wellby: all right. Cool, cool, cool.
Wellby: I'll cunning action disengage.
Unknown: Nice.
Wellby: I'll fly up 90 feet.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: Uh, which is great because then they can't attack me next round.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Although maybe they all swarm to you, and that's not good.
Delwath: Nah, it's a... Yeah, take the sneak attack on the dragon.
Delwath: It's okay.
Unknown: Why is it okay? [laughs] Uh.
Unknown: Oh, actually, I gotta think about this for a minute.
Kenzo: Don't, don't we want to be able to, uh, deal, like, 100 points of damage per round against the dragon?
Wellby: I have 127 hit points right now.
Wellby: I can probably withstand a round of being swarmed.
Unknown: Okay. Just...
Unknown: Yeah, sure. Or bait.
Wellby: I mean, it keeps-
Unknown: Fly, fly up and then shoot
Wellby: ... I mean, it keeps everybody else off-
Unknown: Yeah
Wellby: ... of you guys.
Delwath: Yeah. Bait, bait's a good move, too.
Wellby: So I think I'm gonna stay right there.
Wellby: I'm gonna take steady aim at the wounded one.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: And shoot it, and then ready an action to shoot it again.
Unknown: Yep.
DM: They're both wounded, but you mean the one that's badly...
Unknown: That's bloody.
Wellby: One...
Wellby: Fuck. That's a 15 with advantage.
DM: That's the AC.
Wellby: Oh, holy shit.
Unknown: Wow.
Wellby: Okay.
Unknown: Nice.
Wellby: I mean, let's roll some D6s.
Unknown: Thank you for your service. We'll- You're killing that...
Kenzo: You're killing the f- the formerly prone one?
DM: The formerly prone one, yeah.
Wellby: 35 on the formerly prone one.
DM: That's gotta be dead. Okay, that one's looking... That's not quite dead.
DM: It's not dead? The fuck? They have 130 hit points.
Unknown: Wow. [sighs] Okay.
Delwath: You can't create a lower level pact slot than your pact slots, right?
Delwath: No, I can't even create a pact- No. Yeah, okay.
DM: I can't create a pact slot with sorcerer points. Not with sorcerer points, no.
Wellby: All right.
DM: That ends your turn. What your reaction is to?
Wellby: Ready an action to shoot that same one again.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: And I'm just gonna take whatever they decide to do.
DM: Okay. So that ends
DM: Wellby's turn. The dragon...
DM: Oh, you fuck. Oh, that's a legendary action.
DM: Yep. I forgot about that.
DM: Um, is going to, um,
DM: turn shadowy and incorporeal,
DM: gaining resistance to all damage until the start of their next turn.
Unknown: The fuck?
Unknown: Well, it's fair that it gets cool things, too.
Wellby: Wow.
Kenzo: Well, at least we know that. [laughs]
Wellby: Sure. We're like, hey, look.
Unknown: Thanks.
Wellby: Look at that.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: I
Wellby: didn't know dragons could do that.
Delwath: Uh, whose turn? Uh- That was Wender, then...
Kenzo: Uh, Kenzo is next. Well, I guess, uh, since I can't attack it, I'm just gonna come over here and kill this.
DM: I mean you can attack it, it's just all your attacks do half damage.
DM: Yeah. Resistance just means damage is cut in half.
Wellby: It means he'll only do, like, 50 points of damage instead of 100.
Delwath: But its dex saving throw is pretty bad, right?
Delwath: Yep. If it failed a save, that would make it fall...
Delwath: Go prone. Would it fall off that?
DM: Right now it's perched on top of the- Yeah ...
Unknown: lighthouse. Mm, grease.
Delwath: If it failed its save with grease, would it fall off the top?
Unknown: Still attack the dragon? It might.
Kenzo: I'm thinking about here to kill this thing and then still attack the dragon probably, huh?
Wellby: This one definitely can't be killed over a round.
DM: It would probably use a legendary resistance to-
Wellby: Yeah
Unknown: ... keep itself from falling.
Wellby: This one still has, like, 130 hit points.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. But still, you're burning a legendary resistance with a personal slot.
Unknown: Yeah. It's a pretty bad trade. Yeah, that's a great trade.
Kenzo: Um, what do you guys think? Still attack the dragon even though that's half damage?
Wellby: You have enough move to go down, grab the drift globe, run back up, put it in, and turn it back on again.
Unknown: Yeah, it takes an, uh, it takes an action to turn it back on.
Unknown: Oh, wait, it's not turned off.
Wellby: Well, that would... It turned off. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: It's not turned off. Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Do you have enough... I also have a drift globe.
Unknown: No, both of them are in there.
DM: Yeah. That's how it could only knock out one.
Unknown: There's two drift globes in there.
Wellby: Were both of the drift globes-
Kenzo: Was my... Was it my drift globe in there? Yeah, your-
Wellby: Okay
Kenzo: ... and Vax's. Oh,
Delwath: okay. I mean, does my spell count as a s- it counts as its leveled spell for emanating light.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: I mean, I don't... I wouldn't be as worried, like, I'll be a beacon.
Delwath: You can still see the dragon to fight.
Delwath: I wouldn't waste your action on the restoring the drift globe.
Wellby: All right.
DM: It wouldn't be his action, it would just be his move.
DM: Oh. As your free object interaction to pick it up.
Delwath: Well, I'd waste your move on it.
Wellby: Huh?
Delwath: If you can run ahead-
Wellby: Yeah, dude, I have 100-
Unknown: Move
Wellby: ... I have 160 move.
DM: Well, you'd have to put it back in your next turn.
DM: You can fly down, pick it up, punch him, next turn put it back.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. Do that. All right, fine. I'll do that.
Kenzo: So I'll go down over here, pick up the, pick up the drift globe.
Unknown: Well, that might make you a target.
DM: If you're holding the drift globe, it's probably gonna attack you.
Unknown: You should be.
Wellby: Well, it's gonna-
Unknown: No
Wellby: ... attack somebody no matter what.
Delwath: Yeah, that's good because I have almost no hit points right now.
Wellby: It's not gonna not attack anybody.
Unknown: That's fine. It's fine.
Kenzo: Okay. You, you should, uh- So now it takes half damage if, uh, if I hit.
DM: It takes half damage from all your hits.
Unknown: All right. Let's fucking go.
Kenzo: And I don't have advantage.
Wellby: Correct.
Kenzo: No. 20 to hit, right? Yeah.
Unknown: Okay. That hits.
DM: And that, the first attack does- Oh, I forgot to mention, the last turn you passed it over to Bloody.
DM: I forget exactly where. Who did?
Unknown: Well over Bloody. Which? The dragon.
Kenzo: The dragon. The dragon is? Oh, holy fuck.
DM: I mean, not well over Bloody,
Unknown: but... Uh. I mean, you've done 300 hit points of damage.
Kenzo: It better ... 11. Attack one.
DM: 11. That's, so reduced to half, it's five.
Kenzo: Yep. Attack one. Attack two.
Kenzo: Oh, fuck. I think I miss
Unknown: Um
Delwath: It's 20 AC.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: You miss.
Kenzo: That's, that's a miss. 14.
Kenzo: Do I bardic inspiration or do I save that?
Unknown: What if I save that?
DM: No, save that. You have five attacks.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: Save it for a six.
Kenzo: That's my first miss. All right.
Kenzo: Third attack. [dice rolling] Natural 20.
Kenzo: Crit. [sighs] Okay, crit.
Kenzo: So I do on the crit [dice rolling] literally like this.
Kenzo: Uh, what is that?
Kenzo: 12, 16, 21.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Hold on, hold on. 21 plus, [dice rolling] uh, plus, uh, 11 is 33, plus 5 is 38.
DM: Yeah, so-
Kenzo: 19
DM: ... 19.
Unknown: All right. Attack-
Wellby: You're still doing some meaningful damage.
Unknown: I am.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Attack number four. [dice rolling] Ooh.
Kenzo: Uh, 19. That misses.
Unknown: Fuck.
DM: That misses, yeah.
Kenzo: And attack number five. [dice rolling] No.
DM: That misses.
Unknown: Damn.
Unknown: Oof.
DM: Distracted by holding the light gl-
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: With your hand.
DM: Well, at least you missed on the round it's invulnerable.
DM: It's resistant.
Unknown: Yes, exactly.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: Right, right, right, right. Yeah.
Unknown: Yep. All right. That's all right.
DM: That ends Kenza's turn.
DM: The dragonettes.
DM: You didn't move-
Kenzo: And every time you say... Every time you say that...
Kenzo: Uh, he, he went up. Oh, no, he did not move.
Unknown: No.
DM: You didn't move, right?
Wellby: Who didn't move?
Unknown: You didn't move.
DM: You didn't move. Wellby didn't move.
Unknown: No.
DM: Uh, okay. So-
Kenzo: This is like a good soldier moment.
DM: Yep. Um, the dragonettes, there's what, five of them remaining?
Kenzo: Dude, are any of the fucking other...
Kenzo: Like, nobody's getting any gold right now.
Unknown: Six, six now.
Kenzo: Like, none of the, none of the fucking, like-
DM: Well, you have no idea what's going on outside the radius of darkness.
DM: Maybe they stopped 50 other dragon-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... dragonettes from coming to help.
Wellby: Certainly they will claim to have done so.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
DM: Well, maybe they're just looting the lair right now.
Unknown: We should go over there.
Wellby: No, they would-
Delwath: Nah. [dice rolling] [laughs]
Delwath: They're not that hard to kill. If they loot the lair, we'll just take them in the back.
Unknown: That's, uh, that's true.
Wellby: If they try to loot the lair, the lair will kill them.
Kenzo: Yeah, the lair will kill them.
DM: I feel like that usually.
DM: 27.
Unknown: Kind of a gamble for that.
Wellby: 27.
DM: Uh, it's a hit.
Wellby: Hits me.
DM: So you take 20...
DM: So there, there's five of them by you.
DM: You take, um, 20 points of acid damage.
Wellby: Is this one attack or all of them?
DM: Yeah, one attack. They have minions make a group attack.
Wellby: Okay, okay.
DM: So it's the whole attack, all the minions.
Wellby: Awesome. I don't know if there's gonna be five more of those.
DM: No, no, no.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: That's why they get, like, such a big plus to hit is because you add all their pluses together.
Wellby: Okay.
DM: Um, and you are...
DM: Uh, you have to make a dex saving throw.
Wellby: I have advantage on dex saving throws because [dice rolling]
Unknown: Love that.
Wellby: And that is 20.
DM: You are not coated in acid.
Wellby: That's good.
DM: Um, that ends the minions' turns, but the chimeras
DM: now are both going to...
DM: Wait, are... Did you fail... You didn't fail your frightened save, did you?
Wellby: Did not. It succeeded.
DM: Um,
DM: you're im- so you're now immune to both of their roars till, for the next 24 hours, so they're not gonna waste their time doing that again.
DM: Um, one of them is gonna...
DM: The first one is gonna start by trying to grab you with its lion's mouth and toss you.
DM: [dice rolling] Oh, that's only a 10 to hit.
DM: That misses.
DM: Um, it'll just bite you with the...
DM: Ugh, that's a 15 to hit.
DM: That misses. [dice rolling] That is a 22 to hit.
Wellby: That's a hit.
DM: So you take
DM: five, nine points of piercing damage.
Wellby: Awesome.
DM: Now, the second one is gonna attempt to toss you.
DM: [dice rolling] Um, that is a 22 to hit.
Wellby: That is a hit.
DM: Um, dex or strength save.
Wellby: Ooh.
Wellby: Strength save.
Wellby: [dice rolling] [laughs]
DM: Oof. Not a good save.
DM: [dice rolling]
Wellby: That's a six.
DM: Okay. It throws you, like, 15, 20 feet up, just with its mouth.
Wellby: That's not a bad thing
DM: ... out of the way of the minions and then shoots you with fire.
Wellby: Oh, that's less good.
DM: Make a dex, but it's a dex save, so.
Wellby: All right. Dex save with advantage is 28.
DM: Yeah, you succeed. Um, so you take half da- or you take no damage 'cause you have evasion.
Wellby: It tosses me up 15 feet?
Wellby: Sorry, this is the second one now?
DM: This is the second one.
Wellby: All right. Yeah.
DM: Tosses you up, then-
Wellby: Good
DM: ... drag you back.
Kenzo: Don't you get a reaction now to shoot somebody?
DM: He's using his reaction for haste.
DM: He's not going.
Wellby: Oh, wait, wait. When the second one moves, I shoot it.
Unknown: He can get that reaction-
DM: Okay. Yeah, roll, roll that
Unknown: ... to close with me first.
DM: Roll that. Yeah. [dice rolling]
Wellby: That's a natural 20.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Okay.
Wellby: That is,
Wellby: uh-
Kenzo: That's gonna kill that front one
Wellby: ... surely death, but that's gonna be 17, these-
DM: Yeah, the second one's dead.
Unknown: 46.
Wellby: I rolled terribly. I don't... That's only 51.
DM: Yeah, it's still dead.
Kenzo: This one's dead?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Awesome.
Delwath: There's only one chimera left.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: Plus minions.
Unknown: All right.
DM: So that ends the chimeras' turn.
DM: Uh-
Seeker: Wellby's fighting a entire war up here
DM: ... oh, sorry. I think I skipped [laughs]...
Unknown: This is... I'm good right now
DM: ... sorry, guys. I skipped... I kind of got out of order there.
DM: I moved the... It's okay.
DM: Dalweth, Seeker, and Tilly are all next.
Unknown: All right.
DM: In that order. Dalweth, Seeker, Tilly.
Delwath: How badly hurt is that chimera?
Unknown: Did the dragon-
DM: That chimera is pretty-
Kenzo: The dragon, the dragon is what?
DM: It's-
Wellby: It's only had 14
DM: ... 14 damage, so.
Wellby: You should ignore the chimeras. I'm-
Kenzo: The dragon is what?
Wellby: ... just fine.
Unknown: What's his hit points?
Wellby: It's still at 98 hit points.
Delwath: Well, I was just wondering-
Kenzo: Oh, 'cause the dragon is all health
Delwath: ... it's resistant to all damage.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Is this the turn to do something else?
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Kenzo: I mean, I still did a bunch of damage.
Unknown: That's true. That's true.
Unknown: Half of 100's still 50.
Delwath: Half of 100's still 50.
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: I mean, we're not even 300 points-
Unknown: We have a point. We have a point [laughs]
Kenzo: ... we're down, we're down th- like, I did, like, 40 points of damage to the thing.
DM: Um, uh-
Wellby: Dragon. Do the dragon. I don't need it.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: No. Okay, hold on. Uh, I know what I'm gonna do.
Delwath: All right. I'm gonna close with the dragon,
Delwath: just come up behind it.
DM: Yep.
Delwath: And I will attack it.
Kenzo: You're still within 30 feet of me, right?
DM: Well, no, he's already made the sneak attack.
Delwath: I've already made the sneak attack on the-
Unknown: No, you have to make it once. If you succeed once, you are done.
Delwath: Uh, 17 would miss.
DM: Miss, yeah.
Delwath: Uh, should I bardic?
Wellby: Uh, not this round. Not this round.
Delwath: That also misses
Kenzo: It's all right, I missed three times. Save the, save the math
Wellby: I like the flavors right there, though. That it's like misty and incorporeal and-
DM: Misty and incorporeal
Delwath: That also misses. Three misses
DM: ... misty and incorporeal.
DM: Your slashes can't-
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... get purchase on it
Delwath: But, but, but I'm gonna cast a spell.
Delwath: Um, Somnatic
Unknown: Static.
DM: Nice, nice.
Delwath: Uh, that is a 20-foot radius, so can I get all the minions and that guy?
DM: Yeah.
DM: Uh, 20-foot radius is four squares.
Unknown: Uh, yeah.
Unknown: 20 foot.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Okay. So I will...
Unknown: Oh,
Delwath: no I can't use two meta magics on the same turn, so I probably shouldn't do that 'cause then...
Delwath: Wait, Wellby's... Is Wellby above them?
Unknown: Wellby's-
Kenzo: Wellby's ab- Wellby got thrown up in the air
Unknown: Wellby's above them
Delwath: Oh, he got thrown 20 feet up.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: So I can get them without hitting Wellby.
DM: Yes.
Unknown: Um.
Wellby: Is it a sphere or a cylinder?
Delwath: It's a sphere.
DM: So you-
Kenzo: Totally can
DM: ... yeah, I mean, because of where you put it, yeah
Kenzo: They were all around Wellby.
DM: They were all around Wellby
Kenzo: And then they got thr- Wellby got thrown up.
Delwath: As long as Wellby's even five feet up, I can just put it further down
DM: Well, but it's a sphere so if he's...
DM: But actually he's 20 feet up, so you're pretty-
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah
DM: ... I think you can still get them all.
Delwath: Okay. Uh-
Kenzo: That was perfect to get thrown 20 feet in the air
Delwath: ... that is a-
Wellby: That was the ideal, really
Unknown: It was completely ideal
Delwath: ... yes. So that's two sorcery points, the bonus action.
Unknown: Cast it
Kenzo: You got out of, uh, you got out of, uh, melee with the, the fucking things-
Unknown: And, um-
Unknown: ... and then you didn't get hit with the thing, so
Delwath: ... and, uh, DC 19-
Unknown: Sounds like you had a good turn
Delwath: ... DC 18, uh, int checks, insights.
DM: Well, the chimera can't succeed.
DM: It's got a minus four.
DM: Um,
DM: and the minions...
Seeker: It's not always the case that three heads is better than one.
DM: [laughs] The, the minions-
Unknown: Holy shit. Nice
DM: ... could technically succeed
Unknown: 10,
Unknown: 20.
DM: Ooh, natural 20. Oh, natural 20
Delwath: How many hit points do they have?
DM: Uh, it's probably not gonna matter
Delwath: It does 10, 20,
Delwath: 33 points of eight...
Delwath: No, wait 28.
DM: They have 18 hit points
Delwath: It does 32 da- uh,
Delwath: 10, 20, uh, 10, 20-
Wellby: Yeah
Delwath: ... 28, 29.
Delwath: It does 32. Ah, that's not quite enough
DM: So that two of them survive with two hit points left
Unknown: Okay. Um-
Kenzo: So there's only two left?
DM: There's only two left
Delwath: A- and the chimera has D6, um, minus on all of its-
DM: Yeah, so it ha-
Unknown: ... tackles and
DM: ... it's 32 damage, so the chimera takes 32.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Nice.
Unknown: Nice. Great.
DM: And it's minus D6.
Delwath: All right. Tilly's turn?
DM: Tilly's, uh, Seeker and then Tilly in either order.
DM: Okay
DM: And Seeker is Seeker, golem, ladder.
Seeker: Yes. Um,
Seeker: I could hit that chimera with a catapult.
DM: That's a good idea
Seeker: Actually, can I? What's the range on that?
Unknown: Um-
DM: I mean, you could move
Seeker: Oh, the range is 60, actually.
DM: That's six squares.
Wellby: It's like 11-ish squares.
Wellby: 10, 11
Seeker: So if I, I can move as far as here, that would be one, two, three, four, five, s- oh.
Seeker: So actually I cannot hit it with the catapult.
Kenzo: Wait. You're... Where are you? Oh, you're back there.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah. I'm back there.
Kenzo: You could hit the dragon with it. Oh, right.
Unknown: No, you can't hit the dragon.
DM: Um, by the way, you do notice on Seeker's turn the dragon, despite being distracted by the lights, is puffing in
DM: its chest.
Kenzo: Oh, fuck. Breath weapon.
Seeker: Oh, God.
Unknown: Um,
Seeker: well, okay. I will, I will hit the...
Unknown: [banging]
Unknown: What was that noise? Huh.
Wellby: It's the house shifting.
Unknown: Um.
Wellby: Tenure.
Kenzo: Dragon puffing its chest.
Unknown: Um,
Kenzo: I mean, if I were the dragon... Well, I guess the golem's on its back, so it would probably go someplace secure and try to hit all of us like this.
Unknown: Um, and the breath-
Delwath: Wait. Is this, this dragon not immune to restraint, is it?
DM: Nope
Seeker: The breath weapon's damage type was-
DM: Necrotic and acid
Unknown: And acid, yeah.
Unknown: Um,
Seeker: all right. I will hit the dragon with a catapult at,
Seeker: uh, fifth level.
Kenzo: That's Milo, right?
Unknown: Mm-hmm
DM: That's Milo, yeah
Seeker: But I will use my final-
Kenzo: So right now he's probably gonna like go here and try to hit us all like that
Seeker: ... glove charge-
Kenzo: You're fucking safe
Seeker: ... to use the earth-
DM: Milo's turn is after Tilly's, so Milo could move
Unknown: Milo could move
Unknown: All right.
Seeker: So I cast a fifth level catapult with the earth elemental.
DM: Okay
Unknown: We'll get opportunity, that's-
Unknown: Um, so that's-
Delwath: I mean, I'll die if I get hit by the breath again.
Delwath: Oh, but Tilly could heal me
Seeker: ... a dex save.
Unknown: You got a good barbarian in pocket
Unknown: DC 18.
Unknown: Well, I'm at a hit point, one.
Unknown: Hmm?
DM: As a, uh, who?
DM: On the dragon?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: DC what?
Unknown: 18.
DM: Um, that is not good.
Seeker: So it's-
DM: That's a...
DM: Yeah, that's a, that's like a 12
Seeker: So 78 and then I'm just gonna-
Delwath: It's not using legendary resistance.
Delwath: I should remind you.
DM: Not on the, not on just the damage.
DM: It's sa- it saves its legendary resistance for conditions
Seeker: So that's-
DM: It's not... It still has over 100 hit points, so it's not too worried
Seeker: 78, that's 10, 20.
Delwath: Wait. Remind me the initiative, who goes?
Unknown: 33.
DM: It's Tilly, Milo, then the dragon
Unknown: Okay
Seeker: Uh, so that's 33.
DM: Okay
Seeker: And it takes half of that.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: No, it failed.
Seeker: No, but the-
DM: Oh, it takes half of that. Yeah. The shadowing
Unknown: Yeah. The shadowing. Yeah
Seeker: 'Cause of the shadowing.
Seeker: So 16.
DM: So 16
Seeker: Um, and then I will be, because of the earth elemental charge on the glove, immune to-
DM: That still puts it under 100 hit points.
Unknown: Um-
Seeker: Just barely
Seeker: ... is the necrotic or the acid worse?
Seeker: Oh, definitely-
Wellby: Acid. There's a breath weapon spell
Seeker: ... do the acid. Yeah.
DM: Oh, yeah
Wellby: Breath weapon
Unknown: And then-
DM: Oh, and you still take damage from the athach globule
Seeker: ... before that, which is 14
DM: Yeah. 14
Seeker: Um, okay. So now it is
Seeker: ladder, which will just make its attack
Seeker: It fails.
Seeker: And then the stone construct makes its four attacks
DM: Four attacks, yep.
Kenzo: Hell yeah.
Unknown: Um...
Unknown: I mean, it still has res- its resistance doesn't go away
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Not till it's started its turn.
Unknown: Um... [dice rolling]
Kenzo: Hell yeah. They all hit.
Unknown: I think put this...
Unknown: Plus 10, right?
DM: They all hit.
Unknown: Yep.
DM: It has 20 AC [clapping] so they all hit.
DM: Good job, Stone Giant.
Unknown: Let's go. Let's go.
DM: Stone Golem.
Kenzo: So that's, um...
Kenzo: Stone Golem breaking our, our...
Seeker: Each of those is a D8 plus 12.
DM: Oh, that's a good plus.
DM: Plus 12? That's a lot.
DM: Oh, 'cause you cast it at eighth level.
Unknown: I did, yeah. [laughs]
DM: [laughs] Seeker, Seeker wants to get in [dice rolling] this baby competition here.
DM: Oh, yeah.
Seeker: Oh, that's a good roll.
Seeker: That's, um, 16-
Seeker: 26 plus...
DM: 48
Seeker: ... 48. [laughs]
DM: Right, so it's 13 plus 24.
DM: It's getting done.
Seeker: But still that's... Yeah.
Kenzo: That's great.
Seeker: 37, yeah.
Unknown: That's great.
DM: All right.
Unknown: Good job-
Unknown: Tilly
Seeker: ... stone construct.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Tilly and then Milo.
DM: And then the dragon.
Delwath: Okay. Tilly is going to...
Kenzo: It's gonna breath weapon again.
Seeker: Oh, and I can move.
Delwath: It... Yeah. And it can-
Seeker: Should I just step back inside here maybe?
Kenzo: Yeah, you should step back. Yeah.
Delwath: Unfortunately it's gonna be able-
Unknown: Watch your
Delwath: ... it can move about and breath weapon.
Kenzo: It's gonna breath weapon me and you.
Delwath: Yeah. And I only have 40 hit points.
Kenzo: Do we get opportunity attacks on it? We do.
Delwath: If it moves.
DM: If it moves.
Delwath: It can't breath weapon both of us-
DM: Without moving
Delwath: ... without moving.
Kenzo: Yeah. Or it might just go for me.
Delwath: Tilly... I'm gonna tell Tilly I could really use healing.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: One, two, three, four...
Delwath: Oh, she has a 60-
DM: 60-foot fly speed
Delwath: ... five.
Unknown: One, two, three, four, five.
Delwath: Okay.
Delwath: So, uh, let's see.
Delwath: A 3rd level healing word.
Delwath: She has 21 damage.
Kenzo: I mean, it might just go all in on a breath weapon on me.
Delwath: That's a... I should be able to survive a breath weapon hopefully with that.
Delwath: Um, I still have my bardic in- I did not use my bardic inspiration yet, so.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: it... Did the temp hit points come before the saving game?
DM: N- no. If you're knocked unconscious by the, the save, the temp hit points can't help you.
Delwath: And then Tilly can still use her action
Delwath: to cast a cantrip I guess is the best thing she can do.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: She will cast, uh-
Kenzo: There's still like one minion over here randomly, by the way.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: Oh, I forgot about that minion.
DM: Let's just say he closed with...
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Yeah, why not?
Unknown: It's all good.
Unknown: Right? Uh...
Seeker: On average,
Seeker: [laughs] creatures in this battle are closing in death.
Delwath: Um, ray of frost against the chimera.
DM: To the dragon. To the dragon.
Delwath: Nah, ray of frost against the dragon.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: Everything on the dragon.
Unknown: Everything on the dragon. The dragon's almost-
Delwath: Plus nine. 11 or better.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: Oh. [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: That's actually a decent amount of damage.
Unknown: Yeah, 48.
Delwath: I mean, it still has resistance, but...
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: We're, we're...
Kenzo: We just need to survive this, this breath weapon
Delwath: ... 10, 16, 21.
Kenzo: That's another 10.
DM: So that's another 10.
DM: Yeah. It... Basically if you survive the breath weapon you should be able to kill it.
Unknown: All right.
Wellby: Milo's up?
DM: Milo's up.
Wellby: He's gonna move one, two...
Wellby: And telling action, move-
DM: Okay
Wellby: ... two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Wellby: And then he's going to-
Unknown: He should shoot the dragon
Wellby: ... shoot the dragon.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Fuck yeah, let's go. [dice rolling]
Wellby: He... That is a...
Wellby: What is that?
DM: Pretty good roll.
Wellby: It's not good enough. Rolled a four.
DM: No, that's not good enough.
Unknown: That is-
Wellby: 14. But, uh-
DM: He's got bardic
Wellby: ... he's got heroic.
DM: He doesn't have, he doesn't have bardic.
Unknown: Oh, he doesn't have bardic.
Wellby: But he has heroic.
DM: He has heroic.
Wellby: He's gonna use his heroic.
Wellby: [dice rolling] And then
Wellby: he's gonna...
Unknown: That hits.
DM: Yes. [laughs]
Wellby: Yeah. All right. That is, uh,
Wellby: 66 plus something.
Wellby: All right, that's 27 plus 5 is 32, is 16 then.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah, we're, we're, we're light.
Kenzo: We're... The dragon is very fucked up.
Seeker: We're money.
Kenzo: Yeah, when the dragon is very fucked up.
DM: Okay.
DM: The dragon,
DM: puffing up its chest,
DM: is going to
DM: first of all kick this drift globe with its free object interaction, rolling down to there.
DM: So the
DM: light goes out from the-
Delwath: But Kenzo's still holding it
DM: ... Kenzo is still holding some.
Delwath: There's 40 foot light from me and s- 120 foot light from Kenzo.
DM: Yes. But it's just Kenzo as a glowing beacon now in the darkness.
DM: [laughs] And it's g-
Delwath: And Delwath
DM: ... And Delwath is a glowing beacon in the darkness.
DM: And it's gonna fly.
Unknown: Can we... Are we both-
Kenzo: We're both gonna get opportunity attacks
DM: ... still both get opportunities.
Unknown: But if I, if I upright-
Wellby: Stone Golem, is it incorporeal still or no?
DM: It, uh, nope. Start of his turn it's not incorporeal.
DM: But if you use your reaction-
Delwath: I know, I know, I know, I know
Seeker: ... Oh, it, [laughs] it has to make a wisdom save again.
DM: Oh.
Unknown: It's an easy one for it. It is DC 18.
DM: Yeah, it's definitely gonna use a leg-
DM: I wonder if it-
DM: It needs its... It's definitely using a...
DM: Ooh.
DM: What is the to- what is it?
Seeker: 18.
DM: Oh, no, it succeeds.
Unknown: Okay. [laughs]
DM: It would've used a legendary resistance on that though.
Seeker: That's the stony lethargy.
DM: So you guys decide-
Delwath: Well, can Kenzo... Can I see if Kenzo does a ton of damage before I decide?
DM: Yeah. Kenzo can go first.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: So it flies straight up.
Kenzo: Hold on, hold on. But if I, if I, I, if I use my opportunity attack then does that impact-
Unknown: You can't use your reaction
DM: ... No, no. You can't use your reaction so you can't-
Unknown: Use evasion?
DM: No, no. You can't use your deflect attacks, but it hasn't actually attacked you with attacks yet.
Unknown: Can I-
DM: It's breath weapon
Unknown: ... oh, yeah. D- d-
DM: But if you...
DM: But you get your reaction back on your turn, but if you opportunity attack and then it decides to hit you with a claw or something, you can't deflect it.
Unknown: I see.
DM: It's both your primary reactions.
Kenzo: I see. I see.
Kenzo: I think it's better for me to do that 'cause it's still got three attacks, right?
Kenzo: It's g- it's gonna do-
DM: Well, if it breath weapons it doesn't get its...
Kenzo: Oh, it doesn't have any attacks.
Delwath: It could lege- it might have a legendary.
DM: It might have a legendary attack.
Wellby: I think we wanna pour as much damage as quickly as possible.
Kenzo: Yeah, I'll fucking attack it. Let's go.
Kenzo: I'll attack it. I'll attack it
Delwath: I mean, you still have huge... You don't have to worry about his breath weapon, because you only take half no matter what.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: I'll be fine. [dice rolling] That hits.
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: And that does another [dice rolling] 10 plus one.
Kenzo: Another 16 damage.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: And that's real 16 damage.
DM: That's real 16 damage, yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, it is going to-
Kenzo: Wait, does the, the golem get an opportunity attack?
DM: Uh, well, the golem's not leaving its, its-
Unknown: No.
DM: No.
Unknown: Okay, yeah.
DM: Because it has to be within its reach.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: But-
Delwath: I'm gonna save my reaction
DM: ... it's gonna try and flip over and dump the golem onto the
DM: tower,
DM: which I think is a strength...
DM: Just make a strength check for the golem.
DM: What is its strength stat?
Kenzo: Oh, uh, probably very strong.
DM: It's probably pretty strong.
Unknown: 18.
DM: Okay, so roll a D20 plus-
Unknown: Four
DM: ... four.
DM: [dice rolling] It was a 15, and it stays on.
Seeker: 17.
DM: Okay, so it holds on.
DM: The golem's holding on upside down, its arm wrapped around the wings of the dragon as it turns upside down in the air, tries to dump it off, but then flies up
DM: like this. The ladder can also get an opportunity attack.
DM: The ladder's right there.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Yep.
DM: And where you're like in...
DM: You're there. Okay.
Seeker: Ladder's opportunity [dice rolling] attack is a 25.
Unknown: That hits.
DM: Okay, that hits.
Seeker: So that's [dice rolling]... Let's see, D10 plus five.
Kenzo: Yeah, you're so close to killing it.
Unknown: [dice rolling] Is the ladder gonna kill it?
Seeker: That's a nine.
DM: No.
DM: Nine damage?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: All right.
DM: And breath weapon is gonna hit Kenzo, Delwath, and the ladder.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Ladder.
DM: Make your dex save.
Unknown: Seeker-
Unknown: Do I-
Delwath: ... do you take damage? [laughs]
Seeker: Why, why would I? [laughs] I'm currently covered with a shiny chest to protect me.
Kenzo: [dice rolling] 27.
Delwath: Oh, I'm gonna use Heroic Inspiration.
Kenzo: Yeah, you do.
DM: Okay. You haven't already used it?
Unknown: No.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Oh. [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Fuck yeah.
Unknown: So wait.
Unknown: Oh.
Seeker: So the... And the ladder needs to roll a save as well?
Unknown: Uh, is a 22 good enough?
DM: Uh, 22 is the DC.
Unknown: What, what-
Delwath: I mean, I still have Heroic Inspiration.
Delwath: I bardic, too.
Seeker: Sorry, what's the save?
DM: It's a 22 dex save.
Seeker: A dex save.
Unknown: And the ladder-
Delwath: 22. [laughs] I can only beat it by rolling a 20.
DM: The ladder has plus two.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: You got it.
Seeker: The ladder, same, only has plus two, so it needs a 20.
Seeker: [dice rolling] No.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Okay, so that's, um-
Unknown: Ladder's going down
DM: ... 42-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... plus 37.
Unknown: Yeah, the ladder's down.
DM: Okay, the-
Unknown: Wow
DM: ... 79 total damage, um, half on the success.
DM: Um-
Delwath: Which one's the acid?
DM: 37 acid.
Wellby: And zero.
DM: Zero for Kenzo.
Delwath: So wait, hold on. How much total damage was it?
Wellby: Crazy.
DM: 79 total.
Unknown: So 40?
DM: So 40, half.
DM: You would save yourself eight damage with
DM: your reaction.
Delwath: Ah. I should have attacked it.
Delwath: Oh, well. Uh, I'm gonna save myself eight damage.
DM: Okay. And it's moving back, so it, it moves, it moves up,
DM: like, it... Just, like,
DM: a tiny bit so it can get past you, and then it's moving back so that it's gonna end.
DM: Uh, it shoots its breath weapon, and then it's gonna keep moving.
DM: It shoots its breath weapon from here.
Unknown: Yep.
DM: And then it's gonna keep moving a total of one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, 80 feet.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Is it running away?
Delwath: Wait, Kenzo, how much damage was it total?
Delwath: You said it was 40, but I would save eight.
Unknown: Total.
Delwath: So 32 total?
DM: 32 total.
Kenzo: Is it running away?
DM: Uh, it doesn't look like it's running away.
DM: It looks like it's, like, repositioning.
Wellby: How many feet away from you is it?
Wellby: It's still in the glow of you, right?
DM: It's trying to get out of the light is what it looks like.
Wellby: But currently it is still in the glow of-
Delwath: No, it's only 40 from me.
Unknown: Why would you think it's in the glow of you?
DM: It's in the darkness now.
Delwath: But if I drop the drift globe into the thing.
Delwath: No, it's not. It's in dim light.
DM: Oh, it's in dim light from the-
Delwath: Dim light from the drift globe
DM: ... um, but...
DM: Ah, except there's a line.
DM: Through the dim light of the drift globe, there's a line of darkness.
DM: Where does the dr- It's...
Unknown: Sorry, it's 60 feet each?
Delwath: 60 foot, yeah.
DM: 45, 60. Okay, so basically right here
DM: is dark.
DM: Pure black darkness.
Delwath: Is the dragon inside that? Okay.
DM: The dragon is inside that.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: The dragon is completely contained within a line of darkness?
DM: Completely contained within a line of pure darkness.
DM: Turns dim light into darkness.
Seeker: So it does... Okay, yeah.
Unknown: Well.
Wellby: Where are you in the initiative order?
DM: And that ends its turn.
Kenzo: Uh, second after you.
DM: Wellby is next.
Wellby: And I'm gonna hold my action until you reactivate the drift globe in the, in the this guy, on the theory that that's gonna dispel the darkness, and then I'm taking steady aim at the dragon from
Wellby: where I am.
Unknown: Perfect. Perfect.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: You don't get both haste attacks, though.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: But.
DM: You can't u- you can't do two o- two held actions.
Wellby: That's okay. That's worth it.
DM: But you can-
Delwath: Why don't you attack the chimera?
DM: You can still attack the chimera and hold your action for the dragon.
Wellby: Oh, I can do that.
Wellby: I will
Wellby: do that then, but I don't get advantage on the chimera,
Wellby: right?
DM: Uh, no, you... Yeah, you won't get sneak attack on the chimera.
Unknown: Dude cuts.
DM: Uh, what did you hit last time?
Unknown: He is ready.
DM: You didn't hit that, did you?
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Finish him.
Wellby: Uh, wait. Uh-
DM: Yeah, no, you did hit it last time.
DM: You get vexing.
Wellby: Awesome. I'm vexing, and then I'll steady aim on the dragon.
Wellby: [dice rolling] So here comes the first vex attack.
Wellby: It's a 27.
DM: That hits.
Delwath: Wait, so it goes Wellby, Kenzo, chimera.
DM: Wellby, Kenzo-
DM: I'm gonna kill the chimera
DM: ... chimera, Delwath, Seeker, Tilly, Milo.
Wellby: That's-
Unknown: I'm gonna kill the dragon
Wellby: ... 40 on the chimera.
Kenzo: Unless it does something crazy, like heal up to capacity.
DM: Okay. Chimera is, um,
DM: past bloodied now.
Wellby: But reactivate the light, and I'll hit it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: Okay. Um, at the end of Wellby's turn-
Unknown: Oh, fuck
Unknown: Um, surrender
DM: Like a surrender.
Kenzo: [laughs] Wait, just, uh, tell that, tell him that we said that [laughs]
DM: What did he say?
Unknown: No, just s- s- Surrender Well- well- well- Surrender or be destroyed [laughs] Yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: That's his, that's his favorite thing to say.
DM: Okay. You're, you're there. How high up are you guys flying?
Delwath: We're, like, at equal to the top of the t- we were like- Yeah ...
Delwath: parallel to the top of the tower.
Unknown: Yeah, it's about-
DM: Okay. So like-
Seeker: 50 feet something like that ... we could offer it an, an entry level position on Vindristjarna, you know.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: the dragon? Start, start fresh, you know?
Kenzo: Dude, totally start fresh. Like, why?
Kenzo: Why- why go through all of this, you know?
Unknown: Mm-mm.
Wellby: Yeah, he's gotta go. Gotta rethink his life choices.
Delwath: Oh, the golem's still on it.
DM: Yeah [laughs].
Unknown: The golem is still on it.
Kenzo: Does it influence its move, having a giant fucking golem falling on it?
DM: It's actually pretty small compared to-
Delwath: It keeps making the save Ah, okay.
Unknown: It keeps making the save for the-
DM: And the golem's small compared to the dragon
Kenzo: Relative to the dragon. Yeah, yeah.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: I don't like him with all this, this, these, these...
Unknown: what is all this?
DM: Um-
Unknown: Counting
DM: ... it is going to use its-
Unknown: I know
DM: ... legendary action to create
DM: two pools of black acid.
DM: One
DM: right on the roof here,
DM: one right here.
Unknown: Huh. Fair enough.
DM: There's, like, grasping tendrils claw- crawling out of them.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um-
Delwath: Does anything happen of-
DM: Nothing happens unless you start your turn or move within 30 feet of them.
Kenzo: Oh, great. Perfect.
Delwath: I'm within 30 feet of them.
DM: No-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... you're 50 feet up.
Delwath: Oh, 50 feet up. Okay, got it.
DM: But if you fly to the dragon, that one's on the roof.
Seeker: Yeah. I can't get out of that building.
DM: But Seeker is within 30 feet of that.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: [coughs]
Unknown: Okay.
DM: So that ends the d- dragon's action.
DM: Kenzo is up.
Kenzo: I have 160 move, so I'm gonna grace- artfully get around all of this fucking shit.
Unknown: You're lighting... are you not lighting the way? First I'm lighting...
Kenzo: I, I... okay. First, first Kenzo flies over and even though he's never seen American basketball- [laughs] Um, he s- dunk, does like a reverse dunk.
DM: Okay, that-
Unknown: Drops like, drops smoke
DM: ... reactivates 300 feet of light and dispels the darkness.
Wellby: Okay. So- Does that trigger
Wellby: the held action?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Should.
DM: Do you have advan- oh, 'cause you're steady aiming on it.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Yeah, yeah. Um-
Unknown: Do it
DM: ... steady aim's a bonus action.
DM: You can't hold a bonus action.
DM: Oh, I guess we've been letting you do that the whole time, right?
Unknown: You know, it's about yeah.
DM: So that's fine then.
Unknown: You know, it's about-
Unknown: You're really not supposed to have advantage.
Wellby: That's a 30.
DM: Okay, so it doesn't matter.
DM: You hit.
Delwath: It matched for... oh, no, it doesn't matter for sneak attack 'cause he has an ally.
Unknown: That doesn't... it doesn't matter for sneak attack.
Delwath: Oh. 'Cause the golem-
DM: Golem
Delwath: ... is there. You're right, you're right. The golem's, like, distracting it so you can get its-
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: That's 39 damage.
Unknown: Does it kill it?
DM: Nope.
Wellby: Ah, I was trying to snipe it out from under you.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Man. All right.
Delwath: Yeah, Kenzo deserves the kill. That one's got the last hit.
Kenzo: Kenzo, Kenzo fucking, you know, artfully, like-
DM: Okay. Make a strength saving throw.
Unknown: Who?
DM: You.
Kenzo: Why me? I'm fly- I have 160 move.
Kenzo: I'm flying well over, around it.
DM: Oh, you're flying around it. Okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: You're still-
Kenzo: Up and over it. I'm fucking...
Kenzo: I can do the, a whole big ass move.
DM: Yeah. You've got a crazy amount of move.
Kenzo: And I will get over within 15 feet and I'm gonna fuck this guy up.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: [grunts] All right.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: okay, here we go. [grunts] [die rolling] 17.
Unknown: 17 misses.
DM: That misses.
Kenzo: Do you still have your- I'm, I'm gonna use my bardic inspiration ...
Delwath: I was gonna say, I think you still have your bardic.
Kenzo: Why not? I do. Uh, it's D12.
Unknown: Here.
Unknown: [die rolling] That hits.
Unknown: 21.
DM: Yep, yep.
Delwath: And you do extra damage, right? You do four extra damage.
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Okay. [die rolling] So this one is 12, uh, 14, 19, 23.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: First punch, first attack.
DM: Still standing.
Kenzo: Second attack. [die rolling] That definitely hits.
Unknown: [die rolling] And-
Delwath: I like this enlarged Langus claw Kenzo
Kenzo: ... dude, with, with fucking blessings-
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: ... it's pretty, pretty nasty. Oh, this one is quite good.
Kenzo: This is, uh- 20, right? 20.
Unknown: It's gotta be-
DM: Still standing
Delwath: ... almost dead though. It's gotta be, like, next one should kill it ...
Kenzo: that's second attack. I got three more attacks.
Kenzo: Come on, let's go. [die rolling] Right on the nose.
Unknown: Oh man, 14.
DM: That misses. That misses.
Kenzo: Ah, heroic inspiration.
Delwath: Did you already use it? No.
Kenzo: No, what? Oh, you used bardic.
Kenzo: I just used bardic. I just used my bardic.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: And you can only roll, roll one die.
Delwath: Okay.
Delwath: So it's the one from the other one plus.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Yeah. So one plus 10.
Unknown: [die rolling] Damn.
Kenzo: Oh. All right. All right, fourth attack.
Kenzo: [die rolling] That hits.
DM: Big job.
Kenzo: Come on.
DM: This can kill it.
Kenzo: Fucking die. Fucking die. Fucking die.
Unknown: Come on. Fucking die.
Unknown: [die rolling]
DM: That's a lot of damage.
Unknown: That's-
DM: That's gonna kill it, right?
Unknown: Yeah. This is, uh...
Kenzo: what is that? 13, 16, 21.
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: Kenzo flies in.
Unknown: Boo, boo, boo.
Unknown: Fourth attack.
DM: [laughs] You hit it and this scar along its side-
Unknown: Oh, I should have punched its scar.
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... cracks open and it's, like, begins to peel out and suddenly
DM: the sun rises and there's, like,
DM: an entire sunset in a 360 degree circle around you
DM: as the dragon falls, crashes through the roof of the tower,
DM: and lands in the middle of the temple of the Night Queen,
DM: dead.
Kenzo: We forgot to shoot the, uh, shoot the sun spot.
Unknown: The, the spell. We did.
DM: It turned out okay.
Unknown: [laughs] Yeah. You can do the thing.
DM: You, you kind of did for the last one.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. For the last one.
Unknown: Uh- Does Chimera run away? Huh?
DM: Chimera runs away.
Wellby: Uh, well, opportunity attack it.
DM: [laughs] Okay.
Kenzo: Kenzo immediately starts looking around for dragonets.
Unknown: All... where, where is Gresh?
Kenzo: Where is, like, where-
DM: Um-
Wellby: 'Cause all those motherfuckers will start- And then I'm, I'm gonna kill it as it's flying away.
Wellby: Like, there's no way that I don't kill it as it's flying away.
DM: Yeah. It, you kill it as it's flying away.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um, there are, um, you can see what looks like an ongoing battle about three miles away.
Unknown: No way. Okay.
DM: There's about 40 dragonets- That are, seem like they've, like, nearly won,
DM: um,
DM: about against a n- slightly smaller force, maybe 25 dragonets.
DM: Um, and you can't recognize anybody from this distance.
Unknown: Right.
DM: You don't know who's won.
Kenzo: [laughs] Oh, this is gonna be chaos.
Wellby: [laughs] Dimitaur, can you use your booming voice to tell them the dragon's dead?
Kenzo: Or then Dimitaur, can you help figure out, 'cause we're gonna have to do this, you know, he know, Dimitaur knows.
Kenzo: Dimitaur, Dimitaur's gonna be the arbiter of who gets stuff.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: That, that's gonna be the, his, his-
DM: Yes. Dimitaur, there's a, there's a huge booming voice that rings out from the light and it echoes, like, for miles-
Unknown: Oh, fuck yeah, Dimitaur
DM: ... from the-
Unknown: Thank you.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: The dragon is dead.
DM: Meet
DM: at the villa for your rewards
DM: at sunset, which you can see, a sunrise, which you can see is now.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Oh, Dimitaur. Dimitaur has some, some work to do on being a truly benevolent leader.
Unknown: [laughs] He's like-
Unknown: Yes
Wellby: ... which is now, so, so I'll, I'll see you there.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: As soon as I can get there.
DM: No one go in the lair before us.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: There's probably still traps.
Seeker: Let's make Dimitaur the new emperor of Hkar, I guess.
DM: I mean, he might claim the throne because-
Kenzo: Oh, Dimitaur is gonna be the new-
DM: ... he definitely made The Wizard of the Oz his own
Unknown: ... yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Oh my God.
Kenzo: Dimitaur is for sure the new emperor of the Circular Island.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Which is now only dragonets.
Wellby: The last emperor of Hkar.
Kenzo: He is the last emperor of Hkar.
Unknown: Holy fuck.
Unknown: [laughs] Congratulations.
Kenzo: And he's, and he's gonna take away part of his title.
Kenzo: He can be the freer of the, uh, forever sunset.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: What's else his title?
DM: So
DM: you make your way over the course-
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: ... of the next couple of hours
DM: down
DM: to
DM: the lair.
DM: You manage to deal with all the acid traps that-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
DM: ... it was pointless to point out 'cause it'd be anti-climactic.
Kenzo: Yeah. Thank you.
DM: Um.
Seeker: That, that was a big fight.
Unknown: That was.
Kenzo: That was crazy.
Kenzo: That was good.
Kenzo: That was really fucking good.
Kenzo: Uh, hey guys, Kenzo did not take any damage that whole fight.
Unknown: Seriously, [laughs] took zero damage that entire fight.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Wait, that's ridiculous.
Kenzo: Kenzo, Kenzo is like a fucking dragon, like, just like fucks up dragon-
Unknown: Dragon slayer
Unknown: ... that, that, that is, that is the shit.
Seeker: Wait, how did you... You were in the path of the breath weapon.
Delwath: Yeah, I, I have a vision.
DM: He saves. He's on the save. He just-
Kenzo: My saves are fucking crazy.
Kenzo: The, the bless was so awesome.
Kenzo: Like, fucking extra D4 on every D20, that was massively helpful.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: I mean, wide positioning really helps you a lot against a dragon-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... because, like, it, it can only, it can't get everybody.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Its best move was the surprise when it took out the servants.
Kenzo: Oh, that was very... Yeah, yeah. That's very good.
Kenzo: That was it though, man.
Unknown: That was well fought.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: That was very calm.
DM: So you-
Delwath: How many... You took, like, 50?
Wellby: I... No, I'm 10 points below.
Wellby: I took 25 total.
Unknown: Ah, man.
Wellby: And I have 15 extra hit points.
Seeker: Well, I got the acid blob on me, which, um...
Seeker: Actually it's still there. [laughs] So it kind of hurts, so.
DM: You could kind of clear it off.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: But again, like, the zombies absorbed a ton of damage.
Unknown: Well, Delwath also took 140 points of damage.
DM: Delwath absorbed a lot of damage.
Unknown: How much, how much hit points do you have?
Delwath: Well, I got a heal. I got a 35 point-
Unknown: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Delwath: ... healing word boost.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Wow.
Delwath: Well, now let's see.
Delwath: 30, yeah, like I have 30 hit points left and I got, I had 160...
Delwath: Yeah, I took 130 points of damage.
Seeker: And the stone, initial stone construct got one shotted-
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: By the first breath weapon and the ladder went down.
Unknown: But the-
Wellby: Oh, another ladder for the Hall of Records
DM: ... another ladder dies fighting a dragon.
Unknown: It's tragic.
Unknown: Wow. Wow.
Seeker: That's right.
DM: The ladders don't really-
Wellby: We'll have to recover the little ladder.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: They don't really survive dragons.
Unknown: The next time the ladder's gonna be like, "No."
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: It'll refuse to stay up.
Unknown: "I didn't do that." [laughs]
Unknown: Not a dragon. [laughs]
DM: Anything else-
Unknown: I heard about all these other ladders
DM: ... not a dragon.
Seeker: But the second stone construct didn't get a scratch on it, so.
DM: Well, positioning on the back of the dragon.
DM: I mean, that was probably the right move to begin with is to summon it on its back.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: We forgot to use scatter. We never used scatter.
Unknown: We didn't have to.
Unknown: Well, we didn't have to.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: We didn't have... I was, I thought about it on the turn
Delwath: that the dragon w- had resistance to all damage.
Delwath: I was thinking I could scatter all of the
Unknown: k-
Kenzo: All the minions away
Delwath: ... minions away and I could try and scatter the dragon to move it away from the thing so it couldn't knock out the light.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Delwath: But it didn't seem-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... worth it.
Wellby: Repairing the lighthouse was instrumental.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Absolutely.
Unknown: Like-
Unknown: That was, that was massive
Kenzo: ... it would've been a very different fight.
Kenzo: That was massive.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah, it would've been very difficult not, without the light.
Kenzo: It turns out this was the precise exact place to fight the dragon.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Like, the best spot on the entire fucking island to fight the dragon.
Seeker: Yes. We had... And Dimitaur's fireball.
Delwath: Dimitaur's fireball helped.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: Everybody played a role.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So you make your way through the lair.
Unknown: Dragon treasure. I can't wait.
DM: There's, like, a giant eight lake of acid.
Unknown: Dragon treasure.
Wellby: We'll leave, we'll leave that.
DM: That you just fly over.
Unknown: Dragon treasure.
DM: There's, like, shadowy tendrils and things.
DM: You come to the lair itself with massive acid geysers which have stopped erupting.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: And from the lair you can see into the main, like, the room of the main horde,
DM: and you have never seen anything like this before.
DM: There must be
DM: well over a million coins here.
DM: There's thousands upon thousands of, um, items of jewelry that are all...
DM: It's all laid out like a museum.
DM: It's like-
Unknown: Wow
DM: ... there's, like, one wall that has, like, 400 earrings just hanging on the wall.
Delwath: Holy shit.
DM: There's a, um, there's, like, a, a rock that's been carved into, like, a wavy serpentine circle and there's about
DM: 200 rings just kind of laid out- S- like, c- by color, right?
DM: From like the fancy-
Seeker: It's a very organized hoard.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: It's not just a pile of stuff.
DM: Oh, yeah. She spent like hours and hours every day.
Unknown: She... Years and years.
DM: Years-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... just organizing the hoard. There's necklaces, there's broaches, there's, um, there's a whole wall of holy symbols.
DM: There's...
Unknown: Rubies?
Unknown: Um, well, you'll have to search around a little bit.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Um, there's, uh, about 1,000 lockets of various kinds that are laid out like on the bottom panel of a wall.
DM: Um, and then there's a, a waterf- an waterfall of acid that separates this room from another room.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Uh, Dimension Door?
Wellby: Is there anything magic in this room?
DM: There's nothing magic in this room.
Unknown: Dimension Door?
Unknown: I, I guess we could, uh, we could short rest.
Delwath: I, I guess probably we short-
DM: You would have short-
Delwath: Or I could Prayer of Healing at least.
Kenzo: No, we would have short rested before we decided to come to this part of the dungeon.
Wellby: Dispel Magic on the waterfall?
Unknown: Is that a...
Unknown: Is it a magical effect? It must be an acid.
Kenzo: There's no like natural acid waterfall here.
DM: There's probably no natural acid waterfall here.
Kenzo: Dispel Magic.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: So I'll try Dispel.
DM: Okay. What level?
Seeker: I'd have to look at my-
Unknown: High
Seeker: ... what I've got left here.
Delwath: But I could also just Dimension Door.
Unknown: It's fine.
Delwath: But Seek would have to Dimension Door as well.
Seeker: And, and just turn the switch off on the other side.
Unknown: Um,
Kenzo: so we leave Dimitaur in charge of the treasure hoard.
Kenzo: I mean, we can't take, obviously, we can't take this with us which is a shame.
Wellby: We can take a lot of it with us though.
Seeker: I could do it at fourth.
DM: Well, the portable hole is pretty full.
DM: You've got the Cloudspinner in there.
Unknown: Yeah, but we-
DM: I mean, you can dump a bunch of coins around her.
Wellby: Right. We can do like all the-
Wellby: And gems
Wellby: ... gems and jewelry and like...
Kenzo: Yeah, the most valuable stuff.
Wellby: Yeah. We can leave the coins.
Seeker: All right, I cast Dispel Magic at fourth level.
DM: Okay. Um,
DM: uh, I'll just say it. Make a, make...
DM: Well, no, that just dispels it.
DM: There's no point. Um,
DM: past the acid waterfall you see this looks like a, the like special room.
DM: Um, wait, where did I, where did I have this written down?
Delwath: We gotta get Ghesh and-
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah
Delwath: ... Luxune to come in here and like offer-
Kenzo: Yeah, no, we're gonna, we're gonna role play that scene.
Unknown: We're gonna role play-
Wellby: Give them like a coin and they'd be like, "Oh, this is amazing."
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah, we can pick one thing.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Any, any one thing we want.
DM: Um, there are 18
DM: what seem to be particularly valuable or fine items arrayed in a row.
DM: Like sort of... There's like, so there's actually a total of, um...
DM: Oh, I, I lied actually. There are actually a large number of magic things in the other room.
Unknown: Hmm.
Kenzo: A large number of magic things.
DM: But they're all common items.
DM: They're like
DM: rings of cleaning.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Or like necklaces of healing.
Kenzo: Ring of cleaning, we could use that on the Vindristjarna.
Wellby: We've got the cleaning stone already.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yeah. Um,
DM: there are...
DM: 18, 19, 20.
DM: There are 30
DM: pedestals arranged at different heights, um, in the...
DM: I mean, it's all dark, but you know, she could see in the dark.
DM: Arranged at different heights sort of outlining 30 of what seem like her favorite items.
DM: There's, of which 12 are magical.
DM: There's a gold encrusted ceremonial cup.
DM: There's a sapphire and diamond necklace.
DM: There's a small, um, intricately carved marble-
Unknown: Wait, the gold...
Delwath: Okay. Uh, what was the next one?
DM: A small intricately carved-
Delwath: No, after the cup
DM: ... a sapphire and diamond necklace.
DM: There's an intricately carved marble statuette of a dragonette with this incredible detail and tiny little emerald eyes.
Delwath: Which ones are magical?
DM: None of these are magical yet.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: There's a dagger, um, set in a, with a hilt of rubies.
Kenzo: Is there like an Adventian, um, dagger just lying here?
DM: Nope.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, there's a-
Unknown: 'Cause we know what that is
DM: ... intricately designed silver plate, um, clearly very old, um, with scenes of pastoral human life.
Unknown: There's a elaborately designed-
Unknown: Hkar?
DM: ... scepter made from gold and adorned with sapphires.
Kenzo: Hkar artifact? I mean, this is a, the treasure hoard of a-
DM: Yeah, maybe that's from Hkar.
Kenzo: Yeah, a Hkarian artifact.
Unknown: Wow.
DM: Um.
Kenzo: That would be extremely rare.
Wellby: We should look for like Hkarian coinage too while we're here.
Kenzo: There's just, there's a, there's gotta be a Hkarian somewhere in here.
DM: Um, there is an ornate shield crafted from, um,
DM: steel and featuring, um, vivid colors and a elaborate design that shows like a army of Stoneborn fighting against a demon.
Delwath: You know what we need is we need some magic items to give to the Philosopher's Guild.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Oh, yeah. There's
DM: a fine gold necklace.
Kenzo: I mean, [laughs] we've got plenty of stuff now.
DM: That has, um,
DM: it's made of a, of a gold chain, um, that has three, um,
DM: uh, like teardrops, um, each, uh, set with a diamond.
Kenzo: There needs to be some kind of a communication technology in here so we can stay in touch with Dimitaur at all times 'cause we need to like check in.
Kenzo: 'Cause he's, he's our, he's our, our master of coin, you know?
Kenzo: He's our, uh,
Kenzo: AKA the last emperor of Hkar.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: But also our master of coin.
DM: Um, there is another gold medallion with a, um,
DM: intricate relief, um, depicting a strange city.
Unknown: A strange city.
DM: Um.
Unknown: Strange how?
DM: What's particularly strange about it is it's depicting a city with a bunch of dragonettes flying around.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: It's Hkar.
Unknown: Wow.
Kenzo: Or is it like of the future and it's a picture of them?
DM: Um, there's an imperial signet ring.
Wellby: Of what emperor?
DM: Um, one of the emperor of Imridal, one of the Drankorian empires just before the civil war.
DM: There's a gold ring that's shown that is very intricately designed with two dragonets sort of flying, um,
DM: next to each other, um, with, uh, eyes
DM: of rubies.
DM: There's a gemstone brooch, brooch.
DM: Another... There's two more rings, one with silver and diamonds, one, um, a platinum ring set with an emerald.
DM: There's a coronation crown, an imperial coronation crown.
Kenzo: Ooh, we gotta save that for Dimitar.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Um, there's an enameled, um,
DM: serving platter set with, um, again, uh, depicting a scene of ships sailing, like away from a coast.
Unknown: These are all from Hkar.
DM: Um-
Wellby: If we have time, we should show some to the mirror.
Delwath: Yeah. That's gonna have to be like-
DM: Well, in your six month-
Unknown: In our six month downtime
DM: ... Seeker is making the
DM: fancy magic items.
Delwath: Hey, they can all be here. Even if we don't take them, we can borrow them to show them.
DM: Right. Um, there's a beautiful sword, um, with a, um, hilt inlaid with precious stones.
DM: Um, and there's o- like a flagon.
DM: Like, not like a drinking flagon, but like a, I don't know what the word for it.
DM: It's like a punchbowl. There's some medieval word for it.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Um, engraved with gemstones,
DM: and then the magic items.
Seeker: Oh, those are all just the non-magic items.
DM: None of those are magical.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um,
DM: there, uh, so
DM: there are
DM: two potions.
DM: Um,
DM: there is a...
DM: Hold on. Sorry. [coughs] I need, I have 12 items.
DM: Um, there is a necklace-
Unknown: Of fireballs
DM: ... um, with seven small rubies on it.
Delwath: Of fireballs.
Unknown: I like it. I like it.
Delwath: We get to re- rectify our mistakes.
DM: Um,
DM: there is, um, there, there are, there's like a, a silk pouch that's been carefully opened, and inside the silk pouch there are five
DM: gems, each of which...
DM: Five like small, like small diamonds, each of which have been painted with an eye on it, like etched and engraved in the stone.
DM: Um,
DM: there are, um,
DM: um, there is a great sword,
DM: um, with a etched design of mountains along the bottom.
DM: [clears throat] There is
DM: a short bow.
Unknown: Um, it's made of, it's, it's made of wood, but it's
DM: quite a strange wood.
DM: It seems to almost be vibrating and humming with some inner energy.
DM: [clears throat] It does not have a bow string.
DM: Um, there is a-
Delwath: Didn't you just get a short bow from...
Delwath: But maybe a better one
DM: ... there is a belt, um, with a buckle that's decorated in dwarven runes like a, like a, um, probably like dragon hide or something like that.
DM: Uh-
Unknown: One, two, three, four, five, six.
DM: That's seven. Okay.
Unknown: I've got a few more on here.
DM: Um,
DM: uh, there is a,
DM: a small
DM: figurine of a s- of a, it's like an emerald figurine of a strange animal that Kenzo recognizes.
DM: Um,
DM: it's a triceratops.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Oh my God.
Wellby: A small figurine of a triceratops?
DM: Yep.
Wellby: Holy fuck. That's gonna be friends with the fly too.
Kenzo: No. Triceratops. I gotta give that back to the fucking, um,
Kenzo: the, the jungle. I fucking like hung out with dinosaurs and trained with them and shit
Kenzo: during my solo.
DM: Um, there is a,
DM: uh...
DM: Where are my notes? I have note- I have more notes.
DM: That's... Um, there is a, um,
DM: what looks like a fine, um,
DM: spri- like a, it looks like diamond dust.
DM: Um, a powder collected like diamond dust.
DM: [sneezes] Um, that's in a very fancy wooden box.
DM: Um-
Unknown: You said there was 12 of them. Should be three more.
DM: Um, and then there's three more items.
DM: That's all I wrote down.
Delwath: Three more cool things.
Delwath: We can each make one up.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um, I can send you the details later.
DM: The only one that you have to know about is the painted eyes.
DM: So you can, you can place an eye anywhere you want,
DM: and it fades invisibly into the wall,
DM: and anytime you want, you can use an action to see out of the eye.
Wellby: Perfect.
Wellby: That's so cool.
Delwath: Asa can put one in-
Unknown: Right here.
Delwath: Yeah. Here?
Delwath: No, in Dimitar's...
Delwath: Not in the lair.
Kenzo: Why not in the lair? Don't we wanna keep track of our shit?
DM: Nobody's gonna wanna live in the ass lair.
Unknown: That's too tricky and yucky.
Kenzo: Yeah, but then the people, people wanna come and...
Kenzo: Oh, just, but can we comm- like what we need is a communication method Dimitaur
Delwath: Yeah, we need a two-way.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Well, he can write messages to you.
Unknown: How?
DM: You can see out of the eye.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: We can't like commune with him, but,
Unknown: um,
Delwath: so let's, let's, um-
DM: Oh, actually let's say
DM: there's another one of the items
Wellby: Sunny stones?
DM: A, a paired bag of mouths.
Kenzo: Paired bag of what?
Wellby: Uh, mouths to go with the eyes.
Unknown: Oh, so we can talk to each other.
Wellby: And ears.
Kenzo: Thank God. Thank you.
DM: No, you don't need to be able to listen.
DM: You can always write.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Well, okay, let's say the... let's say the eyes can also hear.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: So we don't want to show the dragonets this place.
Delwath: We made a deal. Let's just... Let, let Ghesh and-
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah, but um-
Unknown: Let them in.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Delwath: No. Everybody except Ghesh and...
Delwath: I keep forgetting her name.
DM: Miragen.
Delwath: Miragen. Ghesh and Miragen get to come-
DM: Inside
Delwath: ... get a tour, right? We're gonna go find them.
Delwath: We're gonna thank them for their help.
DM: I mean, you go out and there's like 200 dragonets.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
DM: Dimitaur's like, "Okay.
DM: One at a time."
Kenzo: Wait, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. [laughs] Dimitaur's gonna give a-
DM: They just said it was safe.
Kenzo: [laughs] Hold on. Di- Dimitaur, Dimitaur has to announce himself first.
Unknown: Hold on.
Kenzo: I w- I wrote a whole thing for Dimitaur.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Okay. Can you, can you still do booming voice here?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: As a cantrip.
Kenzo: Does he have a... Does he have like a, you know...
Kenzo: I- is he like the, the son of anything in or is he like the, you know...
Kenzo: What's this like-
DM: I mean, he'd be happy to make up a genealogy.
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: Yeah, so he, he's, he's the son of what?
Kenzo: Like, what's some like, like legendary dragonet that like they would know?
DM: Um.
Kenzo: Or would just be like, "Oh my God," like, you know.
Seeker: Son of the legendary father of Dimitaur.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: [laughs]
Unknown: Okay, that's good. [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: [laughs]
Unknown: Okay. Let's go with that.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: Okay. So for... So Dimitaur, Dimitaur announces him- himself.
Kenzo: He fly- and he flies up.
Unknown: "Behold."
Kenzo: [laughs] "It is I, son of the legendary father of Dimitaur.
Kenzo: I am the light giver and the first fire, the devourer of Ra'ghemdros, the last emperor of Hkar, known as the eternal radiance and liberator of the secret sunset, His Highness
Kenzo: Dimitaur."
Kenzo: And he, and he, and he just kinda stands there and waits.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Pauses for applause.
Kenzo: Pauses for applause.
DM: Everybody is slow, but then-
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: ... they start clapping.
Unknown: Slow clapping.
DM: And then like the voice comes out, "Where's our treasure?"
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: "You promised us gold."
Unknown: Okay.
DM: "Bring it out."
Kenzo: All right. Well, now, now we, we can, we can take to Dimitaur and then, uh, we, we get Gresh and, uh-
Delwath: So Dimitaur, Ghesh, and Magin- M- Maged-
DM: Miragen
Delwath: We're gonna... Those three only can come in first.
Unknown: Yeah. Those three can.
DM: Dimitaur is like, "I will check it out for you."
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: "Just be patient." There's like more flying in
DM: like every minute.
Unknown: Flying into the thing?
DM: No, no. Flying to gather around him.
Unknown: Oh, to ga- yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: There's gonna be like 500 dragonets here by the time you come out.
Unknown: Great.
Delwath: Yeah, that's like almost the whole population.
DM: That's almost the whole population.
Unknown: Wow.
Unknown: Fine.
Delwath: We have to come up with a little quiz, like-
Kenzo: Hmm? Oh, if, if, if they bought, if they bought our-
Delwath: Like a little quiz, right? Like, like
Delwath: what happened at the battle?
Unknown: I mean, you don't actually know what happened at the battle.
Unknown: No. We'll ask Ghesh.
Kenzo: Yeah. Ghesh, what, what happened?
DM: Uh, we won. You didn't see?
Kenzo: No. Did you, did you see what we were doing?
Kenzo: We were killing the dragon.
DM: It was... I mean, I saw the glowing light.
Kenzo: Yeah, you could see our whole battle.
Delwath: It was all bright and lit up.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It was awesome.
Kenzo: Yeah. You saw me punching the thing?
DM: Well, I was a little far away.
Kenzo: Ah, you missed it. It was great.
Wellby: I saw you punch the thing. Good job.
Unknown: I mean, it was great.
Unknown: So
Kenzo: you guys wanna see the treasure?
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: We, uh, we f- we, uh, you know, kind of slowly get the...
Kenzo: Uh, I guess how do we... Do we turn off the acid water first?
Delwath: Yeah, we just thought might-
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: We turned it off.
Seeker: It's gone, yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah, we, uh, we, we bring them into the room, and then, you know, what's, what's their, what's their reaction?
Kenzo: What's Dimitaur into? [laughs]
DM: Dimitaur's like-
Wellby: Money signs
DM: ... "I'll take the throne."
DM: And then he's like, "I am the king.
DM: Wait, no, that's not right. Let's try."
DM: He goes and he walks around a little bit.
DM: Um, "I am the throne of Hka- no.
DM: What should we be? Emperor?
DM: That sounds a little, you know..."
Unknown: Protector.
DM: "I am the protector of Hkar."
DM: I like that one. "This throne,
DM: the voice of the th- man, the gods.
DM: There's something about the gods.
DM: I'll, I'll figure it out."
Unknown: I say just work on it. Keep working, keep working on it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Keep working on it. You'll, you'll get it.
Unknown: You'll get it.
DM: I need something to sit on the throne.
DM: What about your, uh...
DM: What about your golem? Can you leave that behind?
Seeker: Oh, it's, it's gonna fade away pretty soon unfortunately.
DM: Oh, that's too bad.
Kenzo: You can sit on it. Why can't you sit on it?
DM: [sighs]
Wellby: It's a little statue of you.
DM: Hmm?
Wellby: It's just a little statue of you.
Unknown: We, we could... No?
DM: Like little or like-
Wellby: No, it's the... How big was the thing?
Wellby: Oh, yeah, no, that's too small, never mind.
Unknown: We could make you a-
Delwath: I mean, take a look around. There's like...
Delwath: Can you find a... Is there anything here that would be good for sitting on a throne?
Seeker: We could make you a booster seat so you could s- be a little higher up on the throne.
Seeker: It's too big for you, but we c- you know.
DM: Maybe.
Wellby: A cushion.
Unknown: A cushion. [laughs]
DM: A nice pillow.
DM: A nice pillow. I could take a nice pillow.
Kenzo: Oh, there's a lot of fancy pillows in here.
Unknown: You can find, find a-
Wellby: There's a whole pillow wing.
DM: No, there's no pillows-
Unknown: There's not
DM: ... 'cause they don't go through acid very well.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: There's no cloth, books, except for magic items.
DM: There's nothing that's-
Unknown: Ah.
DM: Everything's metal or stone.
Kenzo: Except for a magic pillow.
Wellby: Stone.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Maybe-
DM: We'll figure it out
Delwath: ... maybe, um, maybe you could ask one of the trees to, to
Delwath: make a little seat for Dimitaur.
Kenzo: Yeah, we can do that. I can carve you a seat.
Kenzo: We can, we can, we can, uh, they can make an elven seat for you.
DM: Oh, yeah. That's good.
Kenzo: Elven wood seat.
DM: I like that.
Delwath: Like a little throne inside a throne.
Kenzo: [laughs] It's like a, it's like a little baby seat.
DM: Yes. Could we get three thrones?
Kenzo: Three?
DM: Well, for the little statuette
Unknown: And what's the third one?
DM: I have a little stone carved wood and stone to sit on the arm of the throne for the statuette that Wellby just told me about to sit next to me.
Delwath: The big throne.
DM: The big throne.
Unknown: Ah, yeah.
Unknown: The little throne.
DM: The little throne.
Delwath: The little, little throne.
DM: The wooden throne.
Kenzo: All right. All right. I mean, is this...
Kenzo: Are we like... Is this like the start of some, like, kind of fascist empire that we're, like, gonna end up, like, you know?
Kenzo: Anyways, okay. Yeah, we can make that happen.
Kenzo: We can do that.
DM: Okay.
DM: That's good.
Delwath: I- is that the treasure you'd like, the, the little statuette?
Unknown: Come see.
DM: Oh, I'm sure I'll get a few other things.
Kenzo: What about Dimitaur, right?
Unknown: Yeah, take whatever you want.
Kenzo: Well, D- you're, you're, you're... I mean, I mean, I think we gotta go do stuff, but we're...
Kenzo: We got a little... I mean, you're, you're gonna help us here, right?
Kenzo: This is, this is... You gotta keep an eye out on this stuff for us.
DM: Oh, yeah. I mean, keep an eye on it?
DM: What's the point? If there's rot and hassle, just, you know, scatter it around, put it back where it belongs.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: I mean, take what you want first.
Unknown: All right.
Wellby: We can, we can fill all the remaining volume of the portable hole.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: I, I think we look for diamonds and rubies.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Or anything precious.
Delwath: No, no, no. Diamonds and rubies.
Unknown: Resurrection.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Some rockrum.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Magic items.
DM: And magic items.
Delwath: We'll take the 12 magic items.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: But none of the common ones.
Unknown: I mean, we can take a couple common ones.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: There's gotta be a few, like, fun rings and stuff.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Interesting common ones to be named later.
Delwath: I think we spend, like, a little while.
Delwath: Like, what, what are, what are the...
Delwath: What do Ghesh and what do they want?
DM: I mean, they poke around a bit.
DM: They find some stuff. Milo and Tilly are kind of-
Unknown: They can take something.
Unknown: Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: Looking around.
Wellby: Yeah, help yourselves.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: [laughs] Help yourselves.
DM: Seriously.
DM: I mean-
Unknown: Can
DM: ... do you want this bow?
Wellby: Maybe. But if I do, I'll give you mine.
DM: It's a deal.
Delwath: Uh, does Tilly want anything? [laughs]
DM: I mean, Tilly wants one of the cool things that's hasn't been made up yet.
Delwath: Yeah, that's fine.
Delwath: They deserve it.
Wellby: We should take, like, some art objects from Hkar also.
Kenzo: Oh, definitely.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Any Hakarian like stuff.
DM: They, they just want some coin.
DM: Th- um, and Milo says, "What we actually want..."
Wellby: Do you want us to review your boat for you again?
DM: I want your boat.
Wellby: The folding boat?
Unknown: Well,
Seeker: I mean, they did s- significantly repair it, didn't they?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I mean...
Wellby: We don't really need a boat.
Wellby: This is like the second time we've ever used it.
Seeker: I think it's a f-
DM: I mean-
Seeker: Considering the service they did, they did for us
Delwath: ... yeah, I think we should be investing in this
Unknown: ... I think it's a fair trade.
Unknown: Fair trade.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: What'd they do for us?
Delwath: Sailed us here.
Wellby: Oh, yeah. No, that's important.
Delwath: And helped us kill the dragon.
Wellby: Also important.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Although
Delwath: they did... I mean, actually Tilly kept Delwath from dying.
Delwath: That was useful.
Unknown: Also important.
Unknown: They helped us.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah. It was-
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Kinda helped.
DM: I mean, we gotta sail out of here, right?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But we were talking, I think we might take some of this coin
DM: heads south.
Unknown: You know what?
Delwath: Take one of the eyes.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: So that way we can-
Delwath: We can see what they see.
DM: How many have we got of them?
Unknown: Two eyes.
Delwath: We got five. Yeah, take an eye and a mouth.
Delwath: I think you should just... I think actually the mouths seem weird.
Delwath: I would just make the-
DM: Yeah, make the eyes
Delwath: ... I mean, if you want, just make 11 items instead of 12.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: But make the eyes be able to just communicate.
Unknown: That's better.
DM: Yeah, the mouths are weird. But yes, they should be able to communicate.
DM: It's a, it's a little bit annoying if they can't.
DM: But just they can... Yeah, they can hear and see.
DM: No, they can speak and see.
DM: While you're looking through the eye, you can speak from the eye.
Kenzo: But so are they like sending stones but you can see?
DM: Um.
Seeker: They're smart sending stones.
DM: They're kind of like smart sending stones.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But they don't... You have to put them in a...
DM: They don't-
Delwath: They're permanent.
DM: They're-
Delwath: You install them
DM: ... you can uninstall them.
Unknown: Right
DM: So you can move them around.
Delwath: Is there like a-
Wellby: Minimum size of thing that can swallow it?
Delwath: No. Is there like a
Delwath: visualizing? Is there another piece that we have to use or-
DM: No, no. You, you use your action.
Delwath: But who uses their action?
DM: Whoever installed it.
Delwath: As only one of us can use it?
DM: Whoever installs it can use their action to see through it.
Wellby: So like you would install it on the boat and potentially s- one of us would.
Unknown: Hmm.
Wellby: And then it would just be there.
DM: I mean, your best bet is to have Seeker use it so that he can teleport to all sorts of strange places.
Seeker: Oh, yeah. Of course.
Unknown: What?
Delwath: 'Cause if he sees it, he can teleport.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Right, to, to weird places.
Unknown: Yeah. Holy fuck.
Unknown: Actually, yeah.
Kenzo: So we can put these eyes all over the place-
Unknown: Put... Actually, like-
Unknown: ... and then see all kinds of weird shit
Unknown: ...
Delwath: I, I don't know if this is worth it, but we could, in theory, use two on Milo's boat.
Delwath: Put one on the prow-
Unknown: Mm-hmm
Delwath: ... and one, like, in his cabin or something like that.
Unknown: Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Unknown: Is that not what we want?
Seeker: We just, we just need the one on the mast or whatever.
Unknown: Yeah, I guess I'll put it on the mast.
Unknown: On the mast. Yeah, yeah. Put it on the prow.
DM: It can see out and it can see him.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Wow. Anything that they see we can teleport to.
Unknown: Yeah. That's-
DM: Well, not with scene one, so there's a chance you fail.
Unknown: Yeah. Right. Okay, fine.
Unknown: But still.
DM: Still.
Seeker: But it's possible.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Yeah, actually this is a good trade.
Delwath: Milo, take the boat, sail to strange places.
Unknown: Maybe we'll drop by sometime.
Unknown: Use the eyes. [laughs]
Kenzo: Yeah. Show, show us... Go, go, go look at as much cool stuff as you can.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Um.
Kenzo: Show the mast of the boat as much cool stuff as you can.
DM: So the only thing, how do you remove them once you install them?
Kenzo: Are you... Is that the DM side?
DM: Milo, Milo's asking Seeker.
DM: I mean, Seek... You can take them out and move them, but then it would be a new person.
DM: Because we're not gonna keep this boat forever.
DM: It's a little small.
Seeker: I see
Wellby: I mean, can you just put it,
Wellby: put it on like a little-
Unknown: No, no, no
Wellby: ... little piece of wood?
Delwath: Isn't the mast that the tree built for you something you wanna take onto a new boat?
DM: Oh, yeah.
DM: We'd definitely keep that.
Unknown: Perfect.
DM: Put it on the mast.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: We made the mast.
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: Easy enough.
Unknown: Plus, this boat-
DM: That's what I wanted to know. If you take the thing off, does it break?
Kenzo: You can. We're, we're, we're, item-
Seeker: Well, it'll be, it'll become-
DM: No, if you move the item, it's installed to...
DM: No, it won't break.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: But there's a minimum size. You can't just put it in a little stone.
DM: It has to be like a, a wall or a solid stru- I mean, you could put one on Vindristjarna so you could always keep track of what's going on.
Kenzo: Right.
Kenzo: That's great.
Delwath: Also, don't forget the boat does fold up.
Kenzo: There, it's literally a nest camera.
Unknown: So you should bring it with you.
Wellby: It's literally a nest camera.
DM: Yeah, but I think we gotta find an artificer.
DM: I don't think it's gonna fold with this new mast.
Unknown: Ah, yes.
Seeker: Oh, fair point.
Unknown: Well, um...
DM: But that's our quest.
Seeker: So maybe it's an unfolding boat now, yeah.
DM: No, no, it's gonna be...
Unknown: Oh.
DM: They're gonna sail off. They're like...
DM: They probably level up.
DM: They just killed a, kill a dragon.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: They'll sail off. They'll find somebody who can fix the boat, and you'll, you'll have a little eye on the mast-
DM: Perfect
DM: ... of the halfling ship exploring the Southern Ocean.
Wellby: Oh my gosh.
Wellby: Pretty cool.
DM: So the dragonets are eager to
DM: decorate their homes and return all the treasure that they found on Hkar and gave to...
Unknown: Right
DM: ... found on the Circular Island and gave to Ra'ghemdros.
Delwath: So I think we take like an hour or two and, like...
Delwath: I mean, this is pretty well organized, right?
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: I mean, we don't even have... We don't have to put stuff in the portal hole.
Delwath: Like, take a backpack and fill it with gems.
DM: That's... There's not a ton of gems.
DM: It's mostly jewelry, coin-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... and coins.
DM: Um.
Wellby: But we should take as much value in coins as we can because, like the-
Unknown: It's just always useful
Wellby: ... outfitting costs-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah
Wellby: ... that we got quoted for, like, building up the ship are insane.
Kenzo: I mean, this was everything but.
DM: No.
Wellby: It's-
Kenzo: Just like airship owning, you know what I mean?
Unknown: It's just like-
DM: It's like maintenance costs
Kenzo: ... the insurance.
Wellby: Yeah.
Kenzo: You know, all of it. It's just-
Wellby: It's a money pit.
Kenzo: I mean, it's just, you know, once you start going in there, you know.
DM: We should take, take what we can in coin.
Kenzo: Every contractor, and they're like double, triple quoting us.
Unknown: I mean, it's a-
Wellby: 'Cause they see how nice your airship is.
Kenzo: It's just, I mean, it just...
Kenzo: The whole thing is just a racket.
DM: [coughs] I mean, you can take a fair bit of coin.
DM: The more... You know, it's just a trade-off between fancy art.
DM: Like, take all the, like, selected items from the collection-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
DM: ... that are, like, the ancient Dracorian artifacts.
Delwath: I just wanna look around for, like, ge- diamonds and rubies.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: Well, I mean, so diamonds and rubies were precious for magic back in the Dracorian days too.
Unknown: Right.
DM: So they're not typically used in common jewelry.
DM: There's some. Not gonna be a huge amount.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Um.
Delwath: I mean, a- anything that looks super old that...
Unknown: I mean, that-
DM: Well, she curated the oldest stuff.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Your sense is that everything in that
DM: room was, like, carefully curated either 'cause it was connected to the Dracorian imperial line or 'cause it predated Dracoria.
Delwath: So who-
Seeker: But, but nothing relating to Shammut?
DM: No.
Unknown: Huh.
Unknown: Where's Shammut's stuff?
DM: I mean, Shammut probably kept his own stuff.
DM: She hasn't left the island the way-
Kenzo: Where's, where... But where is Shammut's stuff?
Wellby: Somewhere out there in the world, right?
Delwath: Shammut's hoard.
Kenzo: Ooh, that's another good side quest.
DM: Well, it's probably in Limbo.
Kenzo: That's a great side quest, though.
DM: It's probably on another plane.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Could go to Limbo once you get Vindrist...
DM: That's a good 20-level one shot.
Kenzo: Ooh, that's a great, that's a great-
Unknown: Ah, yeah
Kenzo: ... that's a great one shot. Go find Shammut's hoard.
Wellby: I wonder if there are other-
DM: I mean, it's definitely not on this plane.
DM: Shammut's hoard is for sure not somewhere on Tal'dorei.
Seeker: Are there any other siblings?
DM: There could be.
Seeker: Right. Was this an only child?
Kenzo: Wait, so who's the... If Shammut's the...
Kenzo: Is there a mom? It's like who the hell are the fucking dragons?
Kenzo: Do we need to figure that out?
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: You, you have the impression that they, that they reproduce magically.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Like, they turn a stone into an egg or something like that by magic.
Unknown: Wow.
DM: Right? 'Cause there were seven dragons that were born from the-
Unknown: Oh, yeah
DM: ... dead body of Shammut by some weird magical process.
Unknown: Right.
DM: And Grimmuskull was one of them.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: So over the next couple of hours, you sort out the, like, most valuable stuff.
DM: You manage to get, like, a, a small collection of rubies and diamonds.
DM: Um, you know, enough for at least a few castings of Smackum.
DM: Um,
DM: take what seems the most valuable of the art objects and then just, like, pour coins until it fills the space.
Delwath: Once we, um, once we free...
Delwath: Once we liberate Chardin, we should have, like, a big auction in Chardin of all of our...
Delwath: 'Cause coin is a lot more useful than all this jewelry.
Kenzo: Anyway.
DM: Um, and then close up the portable hole.
DM: Say goodbye to Dimitar.
DM: Install an eye on his throne.
DM: Like, where do you want to put the eye?
Kenzo: Uh, where does he think is gonna be the most, uh...
Unknown: Like, where's he, where does he hang out?
Delwath: Where is he putting the throne?
Wellby: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: How's he getting the throne out?
Wellby: We'll, we'll animal shape and put the throne somewhere for him.
Delwath: He does have an 8th-level spell.
DM: Well, he's got, he's got-
Unknown: That's true
DM: ... 400 dragonets with ropes.
Unknown: Right.
Delwath: Yeah. He can solve this problem.
Unknown: It's like, look.
Kenzo: Well, where are you, where are you putting the throne, Barry?
DM: I'm not sure yet.
DM: I'm kind of curious if this heals.
Kenzo: What heals?
DM: He points to the, like, spongy acid moss.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Seeker: Oh, yeah. Probably.
DM: 'Cause, like, the villa's got a pretty nice view.
Kenzo: Stay right in this area. Yeah.
Delwath: I mean, we could just put the eye at the, like, top of the throne.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Right?
Wellby: That's a good idea.
Seeker: Dim- Dimitar has a tough task.
Seeker: They've just had such a massive influx of treasure.
Seeker: It's, like, unprecedented.
Unknown: Everything's changed.
DM: But there's nothing for the-
Seeker: Shiny infla- shininess inflation.
DM: Well, yeah, but also-
Seeker: So he needs to reinvent the entire-
Wellby: You can't buy anything with it
Seeker: ... dragonet economy because they've nothing to do
DM: ... but there is no economy because you just go fly to an arcane circle anytime you need food or water.
Seeker: So what he... So basically he has to provide entertainment
DM: It's enter- entertainment and real estate, but there's only 500 of them.
DM: There's plenty of real estate and not-
Unknown: Hmm. We've also opened up-
Wellby: Dimitaur's cornered the market on entertainment
Seeker: ... we've also opened up the Half Island by-
Delwath: Now that all got plugged because of, because the plague
Seeker: ... the west side.
DM: Somebody, one day somebody might come back and clear the plague cursed areas.
Unknown: Hmm.
Kenzo: The next time we come back there's gonna be like 30,000 dragonets.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: And there's gonna be like elaborate like fucking-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... crazy games and shit.
Unknown: Bubble condos everywhere.
Unknown: Yeah, like just-
Unknown: Space age cities
Unknown: ... yeah, just...
DM: Maybe they'll figure out how to get the island to move again.
Unknown: Hmm.
Seeker: What's Dimitaur's [laughs] vision for his...
Kenzo: He's, he's the last dwarven empire.
DM: Well, he has... I mean, he probably doesn't have that much longer to live.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: He's like super old.
Seeker: So he'll find a successor.
DM: He's like, "Yeah, I gotta see who's the
DM: most interesting or..."
Kenzo: Okay. Before, before we go also, Kenzo gives Gresh a look like,
Unknown: like
Unknown: you, you-
DM: Come back and visit.
Kenzo: Yeah, but just you... It's like...
Seeker: We'll keep an eye on you.
Kenzo: Yeah, but just he's... You know.
Kenzo: Remember that first dice game. Let, let you have those couple but, you know, worked out in the end for you.
DM: Oh, I won fair and square.
Kenzo: You did. You did, but it worked out well for you in the end, right?
DM: Oh, no question.
Kenzo: You chose the right team, right? There you go.
Unknown: There you go.
DM: So you sail back through the storm.
Unknown: Hmm.
Delwath: Why don't we just... I thought we were just gonna Rainbow Bridge.
Wellby: Sail the Rainbow Bridge?
Delwath: Uh, I guess we should save it.
DM: I mean, Milo and Tilly have to sail through the storm one way or the other.
Delwath: That's true. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Seeker: So they can give us a ride in their boat.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
DM: Um, the boat now equipped with a magic elven,
DM: uh, mast, handles much better and you manage to make it through without too much damage
DM: and see Vindristjarna.
Seeker: Ah. Finally.
Kenzo: Nice to be back.
Unknown: So good to be home.
DM: Return
DM: to, I think, I need to check with Kate, Rizwin and the oppressive eye of Apollyon watching your every move.
Unknown: What?
Seeker: How do we know that's happening?
DM: 'Cause of just meta game.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Kate's on Vindristjarna right now?
DM: Rizw- I, I'm pretty sure Rizwin was planning on coming back for the last
DM: fight against Apollyon.
Unknown: Nice.
DM: 'Cause she's off dealing with the like Rizwin doppelganger.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Delwath: Yeah. So Apollyon is going to be watching our every move.
Delwath: That's fun.
Unknown: Hmm.
Kenzo: Yeah. So what? What the fuck is he doing?
Kenzo: It's like I just... I'm not that scared of Apollyon.
Delwath: He's just like whatever.
Delwath: [laughs] I mean, guess our private sanctum comes in handy.
Unknown: Hmm.
Delwath: But we can only use it once, right?
Unknown: We have a scroll of private sanctum.
DM: Yeah, a scroll of private sanctum.
Delwath: How does that, that, uh... Does that...